family what's up
familiar qué pasa
what's happening
qué pasa
Well, you know what happens, how do I raise 18 thousand?
pues sabéis qué pasa cómo subo 18 mil
millions of videos
millones de vídeos
18 billion videos are uploaded
18 mil millones de videos se carga la
notification Javier Oliveira but oh well
notificación javier oliveira pero bueno
nothing happens nothing happens
no pasa nada no pasa nada
encouraging people to raft back
alentando a la gente balsa de vuelta
there I will download the images
ahí voy a descargar las imágenes
I'm going to download the images
voy a descargar las imágenes
to see it ourselves, what better and not have
para verlo nosotros que mejor y no tener
to react to others
que reaccionar a otros
videos
vídeos
thinks I had downloaded that I have
cree que me había descargado que he
made lose image
hecho perder imagen
download well good family because we have
descarga bien bueno familia pues tenemos
the
los
confirmed participants for the tournament
participantes confirmados para el torneo
From the squid game everyone had
del juego del calamar todos tenían
I really want to know who I would be
muchas ganas de saber quiénes estaría yo
I was also very eager
también yo también tenía muchas ganas
because although in the discord group
porque aunque en el grupo de discordia
in which they have put us because they can
en el que nos han metido pues se pueden
see more or less you can see a lot
ver más o menos se pueden ver un montón
of names
de nombres
What happens to a fake account?
qué pasa que para una cuenta falsa de la
olive is worth it
oliva le vale
always in the youth live shows
siempre en los directos de chavalería
among all kinds of specimens
entre todo tipo de especímenes
I'm really going to send you to the Lordship
de verdad os voy a mandar con la señoría
a little while to educate him and that you
un ratito a que se eduque y que os
teach us how to behave with people
enseñen a comportarnos con la gente
Welcome to Andrea, a big kiss
bienvenida a andrea un beso enorme
Thank you so much for being part of
muchísimas gracias por formar parte de
I hope the family stays with you for a long time
la familia espero que te quede por mucho
more time alexa one day I have to suck
tiempo más alexa un día tengo que chupar
Alexa, I think it's in the studio.
alexa yo creo que queda en el estudio
We plugged it in again and it's worth it.
nuevo la enchufar hemos vale
Javi is worth what you pay on the internet.
javi es en el internet vale lo que tú
you want I don't know what you mean but
quieras no sé a qué te refieres pero
Well, let's see
bueno vamos a ver
I say it in the group of records
es que lo digo en el grupo de discos
there are many youtubes there are many
hay muchos youtube hay muchas
influences
influencias
toilet paper toilet paper in the
papel del váter papel del váter en el
Twitter group in the record group
grupo de twitter en el grupo de discos
sorry in the group of records to throw
perdón en el grupo de discos de echar
the participants
los participantes
more involved in the group of records no
más metido allí en el grupo de discos no
for the standards for information
para las normas para las informaciones
not for games
no para juegos
Julio Herrera
julio herrera
pau I can teach you the game that is the
pau le puedo enseñar el juego que sea la
main screen no no
pantalla principal no no
BBVA is going to screw me.
bbva me van a
Well, I don't do it just in case we don't go
bueno no lo hago por si acaso no vamos a
take a look at the contestants
echar un vistazo a los concursantes no
We haven't put the intro and the post.
la intro más el post no lo hemos puesto
We have not put the intro because the
la intro no la hemos puesto porque la
privacy we are live we can't
intimidad estamos en directo no podemos
No Paula, we can't, okay?
no paula no podemos vale
Paula today we are going to train today we are going to
paula hoy vamos a entrenar hoy vamos a
do the training pure and hard
hacer el entrenamiento puro y duro
today we are going to do the
hoy vamos a hoy vamos a hacer el
Paulo's ultimate training
entrenamiento definitivo paulo último
training before entering this
entrenamiento ya antes de entrar estor
Freddy, a huge kiss, King, many
freddy un beso enorme rey muchísimas
thank you
gracias
then check if others put it to see if
luego revisa si otros la ponen a ver si
Others have taught it, I have taught it too.
otros lo lo han enseñado yo también lo
I got
conseguí
Let's see, we have Hayden over here.
a ver hayden tenemos ahí de por aquí
is still
está todavía
then we have air
entonces si tenemos aire
and not being here yet is not good
y de no estar aquí todavía no bueno
Paula and we have to see if there is anything we have
paula y tenemos que ver si hay de nos ha
already made the square and we are going to do it
hecho ya el cuadradito y lo vamos
putting
poniendo
You calm down, I'm nervous with this
tú tranquilo yo nervioso con este
training wins okay paulo let's go
entrenamiento gana vale paulo vamos a
the participants do not look like you
los participantes no se os parece no
Let's go to the participants if you like.
vamos a los participantes si os parece
Uncle South is Uncle South is the
el tío sur está el tío sur está el
straight
directo
There were many thanks, king
hubo muchísimas gracias rey
the shot is on the right
el tiro es un está en derecho
air
aire
just turned off in sight but turned off
acaba de apagar a la vista pero apagarse
turned off
apagados
I'll see if it just disconnected
voy a ver si se acaba de desconectar
just connected to a long time ago
se acaba de conectar a hace mucho hace
minutes do not endorse these lines online
minutos no avale estas líneas en línea
so if you want to come with me to
así que si quiere entrar conmigo a
comment on the participants
comentar los participantes
A minute ago no, he wasn't answering me.
hace un minuto no no me está contestando
he is answering me
me está contestando
we start tomorrow
empezamos mañana
Okay, don't want to come in, do you want to have dinner?
vale no quiere entrar quieres cenar
Do you want to have dinner? The bastard doesn't want to come in?
quieres cenar el cabrón no quiere entrar
I just finished straight dude I'm going to
acabo de terminar directo tío voy a
dinner ha ha ha son of a [ __ ]
cenar ja ja ja hijo de
and on top of that he insults me
y encima me insulta
Lady Thatcher
lady thatcher
Lakers, do you want to come in with me on the call?
lakers quieres entrar conmigo en llamada
to react to the participants
para ir reaccionando a los participantes
that I don't know half of them for sure and
que no conozco a la mitad seguramente y
He told me that I'm eating
me ha dicho que me estoy comiendo
serving is happening well let's see
sirviendo está ocurriendo bueno a ver
family
familia
matte ryder no idea mat ryder later
matte ryder ni idea mat ryder después
We'll see, then we'll see.
vamos a ir viendo pues vamos a ir viendo
Here someone is worth each one
aquí alguien son cada uno vale
if your body
si tu cuerpo
[Music]
[Música]
Okay, there's going to be a lot more people, Ryder.
vale va a haber mucha gente más ryder
southern light
luz sur
everyone knows or has the green light gamer
todos saben o tienen luz verde gamer el
cousin of
primo de
and Aiton's cousin gameplay
y el primo de aiton gameplay
Arcor's name sounds familiar to me but I don't know
arcor me suena el nombre pero no sé
who evidently form that no
quiénes forman evidentemente esa no
has light is a boy who does little
tiene luz es un chaval que hace poco
It came out in one of our videos and it's in black
salió en un vídeo nuestro está en negro
They are flying it, he got angry with him who
la están volando se enfadó con él quien
It was who was there in which less
fue quien fue ahí de en que menos
the principal who got angry with him
mandante el que se enfadó con él
Well, let's put in Pau, let's put in Paulo
bueno metemos a pau le metemos a paulo
paulo do you want to come in to comment on the
paulo quieres entrar a comentar los
participants
participantes
you want to enter by voice
quieres entrar por voz
Alfano is here, Alfa is not here because I called him.
alfano está alfa no está porque le llamé
by phone and I called Bayern today
por teléfono y le llamé hoy bayern
grandfather when he went to ask him if
abuelo cuando fue a preguntarle si
was come on okay will go in for
estaba venga vale va a entrar para
Paula comes in to comment on the
entrar paula para ir comentando los
course participants are worth it
participantes de cursos vale
we will give away the second one we put it in
regalaremos el segundo lo metemos
from the south has left us
desde el sur nos ha dejado
hello
hola
Hello, hello, hello, hello, hello
hola hola hola hola hola
paper
papel
papo
papo
the truth is he ran [ __ ] because he didn't
la verdad corrió porque no
they invited alpha
invitaron a alfa
don't just ask the guest
no le preguntase al invitado simplemente
He asked him if he was in the grade
le preguntó si estaba en nota
Well, now when will Paulo talk about that?
bueno ahora cuando eso hablará paulo
when I can
cuando pueda
papo
papo
If I'm talking about having
si estoy hablando de haber
been the culprit for sure that tomorrow the
sido el culpable seguro que mañana la
road to see paulo
vialidad haber paulo
Okay, okay, well, mattress, yes, I listen to Luis.
vale vale pues colchón si escucho luis
great to defend Luis Gracia de
grandes para defender luis gracia de
escort
escolta
but we have a lot
pero tenemos mucho
Hey, calm down, okay? Friends, near the sea.
oye te calmas vale amigos cerca al mar a
see Pablo Luque such Willy Naves have
ver pablo luque tal willy naves tienen
a and then cannot be first a
un y después no puede ser primero una
sphere but shares doctor or good 602
esfera pero comparte médico o buenos 602
names lu lu lu lu is too good
nombres lu lu lu lu es demasiado bueno
or rather exaggerated, I say that this one
o sea exagerado coreo yo digo que éste
the best are within the tournament place
los mejores está dentro del torneo lugar
so you would have to be careful but
así que habría que tener cuidado pero
listen to me 69
escúchame 69
but appearances are deceiving
ya pero las apariencias engañan para q
Okay, we already know Arcore, no.
vale forman ya sabemos a arcore no
I will continue, the name hard core sounds familiar to me.
seguiré me suena el nombre hard core es
a rap
un rapeo
but he doesn't play or anything
pero no juega ni ná
Well, I guess it wasn't a little bit ha
pues supongo que no fuera un poquillo ha
done for a while but no
hecho un rato pero no
it
lo
we know
sabemos
sharp
sharp
thank you
gracias
[ __ ] 94 million views
94 millones de visitas
I slipped a song behind Maxi's back
el atrás de maxi me deslicé una canción
Vegeta's too
a la de vegeta también
I made him a song, little bee, in honor and
le hice una canción abejita honras y
knowing who is worth a lifetime
saber quién es vale de toda la vida
from this
de esto
test or sprint from sst 3
test o de sprint des de sst 3
no idea
ni idea
silversmith is very high there is work
platero está muy alto hay trabajo
nor low-level downs even in the bit ber
ni bajas de baja mismo en la bit über
exact
exacto
are
están
It won't be much either, no ...
no será mucho tampoco no no no juega
a lot of silver
mucho silver
Silver does play Minecraft but I don't know.
silver si juega minecraft pero no sé
to what extent it is good listen to me
hasta qué punto es bueno escúchame
Fernn Flow
fernán flow
Fernando will play it I suppose but I will never know.
fernando lo jugará supongo pero nunca se
have you seen my heart play tomorrow we are going to
ha visto jugar my heart mañana vamos a
playing with the putt and Ximo Fernando
jugar con el putt y ximo fernando
Tomorrow we are going to play with the very little one
mañana vamos a jugar con el poquísimo
Fernando Flow
fernando flow
Robbins
robbins
I didn't see any idea
no vi ni idea
God is heard super loud, let's see
dios es escuchado súper fuerte a ver
three of the work a little
tres del trabajo un poco
now you crash
ahora el chocas
and be careful with that very good paper
y cuidadito con ese papel muy bueno a
see is not that it is very good but in
ver no es que sea muy bueno pero en
general is good for games so
general es bueno para los juegos así que
It's what we train, it's yours now.
es lo que entrenamos es tuyo ya te
They surpass you 10 times, it will not be and it was not
superan 10 veces a ti no será y no fue
Well, for me they surpass me 10 times.
bueno para mí me superan 10 veces
surely a digital game today
seguramente uno digital el juego hoy
clear clear
claro claro
It happens that in the shot I don't know why they are
pasa que en la toma no sé por qué están
there in shots there but today when the
ahí en tomas allí pero hoy cuando la
presents the blond d auro they don't know no
presenta el rubio d auro no saben no
They know why they are there in this take
saben por qué están ahí en toma este de
'Operation Triumph' 1
'operación triunfo' 1
I don't even know who he is, so this is one
no sé ni yo quién es o sea este es uno
from 'operation triumph' one
de 'operación triunfo' uno
that is, it will prescribe, see how it is
o sea prescribirá fíjate tú cómo es la
stuff
cosa
that there are some who have the one who does not
que hay algunos que tienen el que no
They have skin that Kinder has
tienen skin que tiene la kinder
video game but maybe that's because
videojuego pero a lo mejor eso es porque
They don't like the original for example
no les gusta el original por ejemplo lo
ready plays minecraft and has a
listo juega al minecraft y tiene una
original that is not but precisely lolito
original que no pero precisamente lolito
Now he is the one who plays Lolita and has
ahora es el que toca a lolita y tiene
let's see
vamos a ver
no no no no no no no no
no no tiene otras no tiene otras no
has another one is the same one that I painted
tiene otra es la misma que la pinto
recreated on high
recreado en lo alto
in the original yes
en la original sí
Jesus Zeron
jesús zerón
no idea
ni idea
d freese grill
d freese grill
no idea either
ni idea tampoco
It didn't come to me, they made a mistake, they came to me
me lo no venía se han equivocado me lo
He didn't come, he put it on me today because he couldn't
no venía me lo puso hoy que no podía
come
venir
If they have made a mistake, he has announced the
si se han equivocado ha anunciado el
jet blonde to melo
rubio jet a melo
I have seen the whole thing but if you say that
he visto completo pero pues si dices que
you have made a mistake in the museum group, I don't
se ha equivocado en el grupo museo yo no
Bobby Craft Pubic could come tomorrow
podía venir mañana bobby craft púbicas
that is very good too if there wouldn't be
ese es muy bueno también si no habría
that you have to be careful with that one
que tener cuidado con ese tiene
that's a minecraft player ha
ese es un jugador de minecraft ha
participated in Elite Kraft and similar series
participado en elite kraft y series así
in front when you see that it has craft in it
delante cuando ves que tiene craft en el
name to be careful type whose axis
nombre que tener cuidado tipo cuyo eje
It means that it is used has a name
es significa que se usa tiene un nombre
from user who puts craft
de usuario que pone craft
His internet nickname has to do with
su apodo en internet tiene que ver con
minecraft clear literally is his life mike
minecraft claro literal es su vida mike
stratus grain
grano stratus
extra
extra
It's the one that's in fog but I don't know
es ese que está en niebla pero no sé
to what extent with the Aurum Play microphones
hasta qué punto con el micros aurum play
I don't have it but I can play with this one
no se tiene pero aurum play con este
blonde lock there on top are more for
mechón rubio ahí en lo alto son más para
the file but they put it in for
el archivo pero que lo metieron para
tell me what we put streamers in that don't
decirme en qué metemos streamers que no
have views to give it a little fame
tengan views para darle un poco de fama
it is not clear at all from aqualand
no está claro para todo de aqualand
agent pact and don't be fooling yourself no
pacto de agentes y no esté juégatela no
He is with many people from Chano
está con mucha gente de chano
Yes, I think this is tortilla duck.
sí creo que este es pato de tortilla no
I'm sure
estoy seguro
16 I don't know who decided more than
16 no sé quiénes decidieron más de
tortilla
tortilla
that he lives together again and all that now but
que vuelve a convivir y todo eso ya pero
It's in an omelet, it doesn't make you good but
está en tortilla no te hace bueno pero
still went to the bus because it must be from
aún así fue al micro pues debe ser de
sense worth carola
sentido vale carola
Carola
carola
desert health in health and it is bad
deserte health in health y es malo
because I've seen it in a series of
porque lo he visto en una serie de
Teacher Pig is average, tending to bad.
maestra pig es es regular tirando a malo
The champion is the father of the Tanzanian
baja al campeón es el padre del tanzano
Of course, the capons are the champions
claro al capones al campeón es la
right is very bad in real life and
derecha está malísimo en la vida real y
In the micro also there has been no care
en el micro también no se ha cuidado
but in majors
sino en majors
no idea but he has a style
ni idea pero tiene un estilo
Note that it does not have to be that 15
fíjate que no tiene que por eso esas 15
call steve steve
llama steve steve
the street must daddy art I don't know
the street mosto papi arte no sé
he's not a bastard
no está cabrón
is that we saw it
es que lo veíamos
They're going to cancel directly because of you
van a cancelar directo por tu culpa
bye
bye
[Music]
[Música]
and Berlin
y berlín
website I don't know website
web no conozco web
This topic is from lol I think wherli but
de este tema es de lol creo wherli pero
Minecraft I don't know, okay, it's the other way around.
minecraft no lo sé vale revés es del
also us reverse is the friend of and byron
también nos revés es el amigo de y byron
burst
reventó
really if they don't reveal the reverse to us
de verdad si no nos revelan el revés
but I don't know if that's it
pero no sé si sea ese
I don't know, it doesn't have an oak ending either.
no sé tampoco tiene un final robles
Oak is the yes I think he is a good player
roble es el sí creo que es buen jugador
from Minecraft
de minecraft
their children
sus hijos
no idea
ni idea
sweet
sweet
sweet and I think it is a good suite but
sweet y creo que si es buena suite pero
No, I don't see it, Manu, it's messing with your head.
no no la veo manu te jode la cabeza de
manu you normal but if it were this
manu te normal pero si fuera esto lo
we would need two lost ones or so
necesitaríamos dos perdidos o sea
wasteland to which it has
páramo al que tiene
debris moderator here is a
moderador de derrubios aquí es un
moderator of the blonde yes but it is also
moderador del rubio sí pero también es
extreme as javi did not discard the first
extreme como javi no desechó el primer
then of course okay billy and
después claro vale billy y
the other one that they put in to give it use
la otra que la metieron para darle uso
be it worth it
sea vale
Javi Oliveira is hot, I don't know.
javi oliveira nos está buenísimo no sé a
who looks at what is handsome there is already
quiénes se mira lo que es guapo ya hay
something imaginary install that does not me
algo sea imaginarias instales que no me
I want to imagine in real life if in the
quiero imaginar en la vida real si en la
real life weapons some some pills
vida real armas alguna alguna pastilla
of rooster no longer some knee but but
de gallo ya no alguna rodilla pero pero
good rum
bueno ron
but very bad, surely not that has been the case
pero malísimo no seguramente no eso sido
very bad, very handsome but very bad manu
malísimos muy guapo pero malísima manu
Kraft had bad Kraft could see why
kraft tuvo malo kraft pudiera ver porque
she has to do in the name like this
ella tiene que hacer en el nombre así
that we are going to say that it is quite good, it is obvious
que vamos que es bastante bueno es obvio
the thumbtack is great for
el chincheta chinche está buenísimo para
pose to follow these points of the
pose a seguir este los puntos de los
books if together with lights of which more
libros si junto con luces de los que más
you must be careful what happens that
debes de tener cuidado lo que pasa que
I was leaving from no
salía de no
I don't know
no lo sé
yes lopez
si lópez
I don't know him but he has a style
no lo conozco pero tiene un estilo
angry so be careful but it's that I
enojado así que cuidado pero es que yo
I think this is the blond one who when he has
creo que este es el rubio que cuando ha
gone to the presentation and got to
ido a la presentación se ha puesto a
paint the dolls that's why there is the one of
pintar los muñecos por eso está el de
The cute ones look easy and clear I think
los lindos pinta fácil y claro yo creo
that he started painting it when
que él se ha puesto a pintarlo cuando
He was such a Ronnie
estaba tal ronnie
I don't know
no lo sé
to whom
a quienes
I don't know any macho people either
tampoco lo conozco a gente macho
no idea to the FBI
ni idea al fbi
al herbish well yes it is quite good and
al herbish pues sí es bastante bueno y
Okay, and if not, then a powerful Levy.
vale y si no si a levy potente al
spur to the plunger they are all going to kill me
espolón al émbolo me van a matar todos
Here, I mean, I'm already seeing the list here.
aquí o sea ya estoy viendo aquí la lista
and these people go there for me but I love them not
y esta gente van allá por mí pero amo no
I'm going to be able to sleep off that idea you have
voy a poder dormir esa idea que tiene
the days on pills this is
los días a base de pastillas esto es
Of course they're going to take you out in the ring at least
claro te van a sacar en el ring mínimo
look on the bright side well that's it
mira el lado positivo bueno eso sí eso
Yes, the good thing is that you are going to take out the rival from me.
sí lo bueno me vas a sacar el rival el
next year so that I don't criticize him
año que viene ya para que no lo critique
so much but what chaves that goes I'm not going to
tanto pero que chaves que va no voy a
be able to sleep so literally I'm going to be in
poder dormir tan literal voy a estar en
the
la
night awake the night awake with
noche despierto la noche despierto con
a knife for a fork or something green
un cuchillo por un tenedor o algo verde
is that they are literally made from
es que literal sea hechas a base de a
Red Bull base
base de red bull
Of course you can't beat them if they are good.
claro no puedes con ellos si es buena el
micro
micro
Moscow
moscú
I don't know him
no lo conozco
today has been good no but churra siro
ar hoy ha sido buena no pero churra siro
Lopez is already a sports commentator
lópez es comentarista de deportes ya
will have more than 50 we mentioned siro
tendrá más de 50 hemos mencionaba siro
Lopez
lópez
Siro Lpez, I don't know, the firefighter no less.
siro lópez no lo sé el bombero no menos
Calm down Javi, even if we see you fall
tranquilo javi que aunque te veamos caer
in English hide and seek' the first test
en escondite inglés' la primera prueba
We will continue to support you in the slam
te seguiremos apoyando en el slam del
Salsa's first of next year is
primer del salsero del año que viene es
'Go for them' joke, titan, funny churra
broma 'a por ellos' titán gracia churra
They have not been referred to as their own but as
no se les ha referido a su sido sino lo
that didn't come out here if not but we have
que no salió aquí si no lo pero lo hemos
mentioned you know mouth
mencionado sabéis boca
pine tree
piñeiro
sigh
suspiro
Peter
peter
that we made the video of I recognize what I am
que hicimos el video de lo reconozco soy
and Peter will recognize Peter Schey and
and peter lo reconocerán peter schey and
Peter is a good person
peter es buena gente
888 gift
888 de regalo
no it's not that good straight to regular
no no es tan bueno directo al regular
Manning I don't know if it's very good I'm going to
manning no sé si es muy bueno voy a
put a cow's head on
poner una cabeza de vaca
Of course he's talking about the cra Scheherazade, I have no idea.
claro habla de la cra scherezade ni idea
and wanes
y mengua
how do they have to
como tienen q
without the idea either
sin la idea tampoco
what nonsense
que
What nonsense sounds like this to me but I don't know if he plays
que me suena pero no sé si juega
to the microphone
al micro
barbecue
barbecue
barbecue is a friend of ibai too
barbecue es amigo de ibai también nos
This is what Juve won.
sirve este la juve ganó
with the micro 109 it was ciro to 109 where
con el micro 109 era ciro a 109 donde
109 is Ciro Lpez and the one who had the
109 está ciro lópez y el que tenía el
that the man from the beach bar is not
que es el hombre el del chiringuito no
the commentator of this sport and this
el comentarista este deporte y este
river that now goes to the side
river que va ahora por lado
Well, here it is in topics for me
pues aquí es en temas para que yo
Ciro Lpez Haya, it's already clear, damn it
ciro lópez haya ya se tiene claro
but we have mentioned it lightly
pero lo hemos mencionado así a la ligera
yes yes yes no stick it okay okay okay okay
si si si no lo pega vale vale vale vale
Okay
vale
so that I would listen
para que yo escuchaba
like
like
I don't know who Israel is
no sé quién es israel
neither Gomez
tampoco gómez
voice x yes no
voice x sí no
Well, look, I don't know who that is either.
pues mira ese tampoco sé quién es
lousy
malísimo
Nani, if you don't love yourself but you have types
nani si no te quieres pero tienes tipos
from to
de a
who loved that here there are 150 people
quienes amaba que aquí hay 150 personas
but in the middle we think of the gray
pero a la mitad nosotros pienso al gris
when going to the oven and twitter
al ir al horno y twitter
I'm not a coconut
no soy coco
The Inca's idea is bad and York is bad
la idea del inca es mala y york es mal
Elias 360 stress sounds familiar to me but it's not
elías 360 el estrés se me suena pero no
I know unequal micros mass symphony
sé desigual micros misa sinfonía
I don't know how good Misano is, Palma.
el misano no sé qué tan bueno sea palma
or lake or labor yes yes it is good it is good
o lago o labor sí sí es bueno es bueno
Labor has nothing against me.
labor no tiene nada en contra mía el
another day was the mystic spoke of me in
otro día fue la mística habló de mí en
a live and in the end you didn't send me or
un directo y al final no me mandaste o
approaching the end of the books
abordar el final libros de ti
at the end of the band
al final de la banda
rich and 23
rico y 23
hello
hola
There are no Pokmon here, so don't worry.
no hay pokemones aquí o sea tú tranquilo
Bonilla distinguished himself as a Semite
bonilla distinguirse semita
I don't know how powerful this is.
se me está no sé qué tan potente este
the doubts
las dudas
plays a lot half and half was there for
juega mucho mitad y mitad estaba ahí por
me too, of course, of course
mí también claro claro
that being careful now has not passed
que tener cuidado ahora no se ha pasado
it is already forgotten
ya está olvidado
you would have to hide to
habría que esconderse para
enter another name
meter otro nombre
you've become a grandfather
te has puesto el abuelo
volcano
volcano
I don't know but it has a style, so it will be seen
no sé pero tiene un estilo o sea se verá
de greve
de greve
efe
efe
director
director
toxic that tomorrow itself
tóxico que mañana mismo
heist
robo
no idea they are granville gramling
ni idea andan granville gramling
anagram
anagrama
Oh, of course, that's not what you want either.
ah claro eso no se quiere tampoco
to surrender
de rendirse
my idea put more here
mi idea meten aquí más
But because there you are, to [ __ ] with me, listen
pero porque ahí por pues escucha
It is not easy to get into these things
no es fácil entrar en estas cosas
If I had the number of people who wanted to enter
si tuviera la de gente que quería entrar
We continue, I think there are two pages, no, yes
seguimos creo que son dos páginas no si
There are two pages, Comanche is worth it.
son dos páginas vale el comanche
organizer with stain because it is the
organizador con mancha pues es el
organizer for why you want me to
organizador para por qué quieres que te
say or rather I don't think it's that good
diga o sea no creo que sea tan bueno
but the motto or
pero el lema o
I also don't know how good elevated ACN is.
tampoco sé qué tan bueno es elevado acn
soccer
soccer
and I don't know who it is or if you have the
y no sé quién es o sea si se tiene el
pain I don't know how good as ander
dolor no sé qué tan buenos como ander
Ander, VAT ISR's friend, is also
ander el amigo de iva isr es también
true Ander is Ibai's friend of course and
verdad ander es el amigo de ibai claro y
It must not be as good as they say
no debe ser tan bueno tan dicen
If I see it more or less wine at 5, it's me.
si lo veo más o menos vino a cinq soy yo
so that it's you I don't know who it is
tan que eres tú no sé quién es
China no chain ATV
china no chain atv
no idea
ni idea
Javier MT Z Javier M
javier mt z javier m
I think it's from the group of Shiites more or
creo que es del grupo de chiíes más o
less good you know it is decent
menos bueno lo sabes decente
I saw those
a esos vi
no idea
ni idea
yapur
yapurá
I don't know who God is when he creates, there is the cry
no sé quién es al crear dios está el cry
this could be could be colleague
este podría ser podría ser colega
separated for this team left them the
separada para este equipo les dejaba la
tomorrow he recorded free
mañana grabó libres
crowley see and a-rod is him
crowley ver y de a-rod es él
rohde that surrounds cel
rohde que rodee cel
Rhodes
rhodes
I don't know how good it is to be degut
no sé qué tan bueno ser degut
nor rigor
tampoco rigor
the rigor and I would say that it is bad and I never
el rigor y diría que es mal y yo nunca
I've seen him play micro unit but
lo he visto jugar al micro unidad pero
The person who is more lax is not mine today
persona que es más laxa es en día no mía
It is one of the best ones in the
es de las más buenas que está en el
tournament has been achieved and this sharing
torneo se ha logrado un y este compartir
the other fact the assertion time idea I hope
el otro hecho el aserto vez idea espero
I hope you win something and make it to the end, Javi.
que ganes algo llegues al final javi
good luck, tasty old man, you have a lot
mucha suerte viejo sabroso tiene mucha
I sent you watermelon
fe envié sandía
He's going to kill me, I'm going to talk to myself
me va a matar me voy a hablar
of the people
de la gente
but cool
pero chinda
but
pero
I would say it's good if you are a germis
diría que es bueno si fe germis
barren
yerma
Roger
roger
Roger would say it's good
roger diría es bueno
It has to be good and regular pipe too
tiene que bueno y regular pipe también
the Catalan GDP is good
es bueno el pib catalán
Natal no I don't know him in Michaels voice
natal no no lo conozco en michaels voz
egp
egp
no idea who that is yes efe
ni idea quién es sí efe
YouTube is the one that makes criticism as well as
el youtube el que hace crítica así como
me too
yo también
Well, look, they already have another objective for
pues mira ya tienen otro objetivo para
He gets along very well with Grace Tiara Garcia
se lleva muy bien con grace tiara garcía
I don't know who it is
no sé quién es
the rich bible
la rica biblia
the rich bible I don't know who he is and suri
la rica biblia no sé quién es el y suri
the zoom and it sounds familiar but I don't know what
el zoom y me suena pero no conozco qué
content makes
contenido hace
raptor gs
raptor gs
fracture gs I think is playing with me
fracture gs creo que juega con mi que
crack could be I don't know if that's the case at that time
crack puede ser no sé si ese ese rato
Marc and the cool Marc and madness also gave
marc y lo cool marc y locura también dio
That is, they are all here
o sea están aquí todos
Marc and madness
marc y locuras
but I have not seen any expert qualities
pero no he visto cualidades perita
the idea is
la idea está
Well, I don't know if he is that good.
bueno pues no se es tan buenos el
Mycroft Cajal, or Cajal is a colleague.
mycroft cajal o sea cajal es colega
also
también
and I Juan and Juanse well I sent well
y yo juan y juanse bueno yo mandé bueno
Well
bueno
Ari gameplays
ari gameplays
I would say it would be good and it doesn't suit me.
regular diría que sería bueno y no me va
to kill of course, that is, you team up with
a matar claro o sea te haces equipo con
she and this one
ella y ésta
Javi from M&amp;R also took me with this.
javi de m&amp;r con esto también me llevo
well the mod of auro javi teams
bien el mod d auro equipos de javi
incredible I would say that it is good kind
increíble diría que es bueno amable la
sister Ariel's sister
hermana la hermana de ariel
I've never seen Michael play.
nunca le he visto jugar a michael
violet violet there is violet is the
violeta violeta allí es violeta es la
busty girlfriend
novia de pechito
I don't know
no lo sé
hello
hola
also gamer s to blow everyone away is
también gamer s para reventar a todos es
careful
cuidado
also
también
Let's go regular because this is the best
vamos regular porque este los mejores
playing one on one we are screwed
jugando uno contra uno vamos jodidos a
Loli, I also made a video and so on.
loli también le hice vídeo y demás
student
estudiante
so that you learn
para que aprendas
far away javi see for all the all go to
lejos javi vea por todos los todos van a
listen but it's not like they're after me
escuchar pero no es que vayan a por mí
is that I believe that in the first test
es que yo creo que en la primera prueba
They're going to push me on the wrist, not you.
en la muñeca me van a empujar no tú
push them then nothing will work for me
empujarlos a ellos entonces nada me van
to push even if they die
a empujar con tal de aunque mueran ellos
but they're going to push me even if it's just a little bit
pero me van a empujar aunque sea un
tree fence or some things be a
árbol cercadilla o algunas cosas sea un
fixed like the Mariana, the Mariana disc it
fijo como el mariana el mariana lo disco
play once if it is fairly regular
jugar una vez si es bastante regular
Carlos Daz
carlos díaz
Carlos de Len from Len Carlos de Len
carlos de león de león carlos de león
with a steve shot but there are people behind
con un steve tiro pero hay gente detrás
I don't know stainless steel
no sé inox
stainless steel no sealing
inox no se selling
the regular link tending to bad Phillips
el link regular tirando a mal phillips
Filis, Ama's husband, I believe.
filis el marido de ama creo
yes but
sí pero
for you, dragon at the maximum
para ti dragón a la de máxima
For you, dragon, I think he plays that one.
para ti dragón a esa creo que juega al
minecraft but i don't know how good it is
minecraft pero no sé qué tan buena es
Steve
steve
let's focus
vamos de focus
well well if it wasn't metal
bueno bueno si no era metal
metal eva is good but i didn't know that
eva de metal es buena pero no sabía que
you are first
eres primero
The XL gave us no idea about Genesis.
de génesis ni idea nos dio el xl
clippers did not give
clippers no dio
Let's finally know what Javi is going to know.
vamos al fin javi va a saber que se
feel the game over hahaha not me
siente el game over jajaja yo no
They're going to remind me of everything, Shadow.
me lo van a recordar todo shadow
Chardonnay of the best that are in
chardonnay de los mejores que están en
be careful, drought
hay cuidado sequía
they had no idea
ni idea conseguían
no idea gamer brand
ni idea marca gamer
the boat
el barca
I would rate it as being on a Liu diet.
regular lo pondría yo estar a dieta liu
qi
qi
with people who took me to another place
con gente que me llevo otra para el
team but I don't know to what extent it is
equipo pero no sé hasta qué punto es
good star yuki sees lucky luke and 13 lucky
buena star yuki ve lucky luke y 13 lucky
I don't know, don't look, he makes knicks
no se no se mire hace knicks
Maple Knicks sounds good to me but
arce knicks me suena que es bueno pero
I've never seen it Nicole oops
nunca lo he visto nicole oops
my idea of a group is not wanted
mi idea de grupo no se quiere
that there are a lot of ranges here of course
que hay un montón de rangos aquí claro
you find yourself alone that is called blond yes
te encuentras solo que se llama rubio sí
I mean, how are you going to know who it is?
o sea cómo vas a saber quién es
magnetized
imantado
and killed in a step but I don't know why
y matado en un step pero no sé por qué
I think he plays Minecraft a lot.
me suena que juega mucho minecraft
Steve's drips
goterones steve
rivers
rivers
God already lives here
ya vivir aquí dios
Well, I'm going to spend my doll
bueno yo es que me la muñeca voy a pasar
from the wrist line
de la línea de la muñeca
clear not even the line of the wrist uncle jose
claro ni la línea de la muñeca tío josé
Christ
cristo
This is why I don't know if I can Mike Mitchell
por esto no sé si pueda mike mitchell
that gold
que el oro
I don't know him
no lo conozco
as it is the same as in it
como sea igual que en él
They don't call this game the wef
no se llaman al juego este el wef
aldo geo
aldo geo
that is
ese es
I put in
pongo en
[Music]
[Música]
-Juan Guarnizo, Guarnizo bread as between
-juan guarnizo pan guarnizo como entre
regular and good paracetamol
regular y bueno paracetamol
If paracetamol is good, it took me
el paracetamol si es buena me llevó
also
también
unicorn no idea and karcher we have
unicornio ni idea y karcher hemos
finished
terminado
on the right side or the bottom
del lado derecho o la parte de abajo
believe
creo
so the hosts and youtube that too
así las hostias y youtube que también
this video
este vídeo
The Galician coach also has a problem
el dt gallego también tiene un problema
with light green if you were the stutterer
con el verde claro si fueras el tartaja
There you are saved but you are halal to open
ahí si te salvas pero eres halal abrir
Carolina is the girl from
carolina es la chica de
that I almost died because of him once
que casi me van por su culpa una vez por
It's your fault not mine for opening your
su culpa no por la mía por abrir su
Twitter or rain I think he follows me I think
twitter o lluvia creo que me sigue creo
I think I'm sure but I think I
creo que estoy seguro pero creo que me
continued with the problem
seguía por el problema
I have here at least at least
yo tengo aquí por lo menos por lo menos
at least one of them is going to die
por lo menos una una la va a morir
for months that sprint sprint of
durante meses que sprint sprint de
a very good prince is not if he is good
príncipe buenísimo no es si es bueno
be at least one imagine one
sean por lo menos una la imagínate una
This half is going for me straight away.
la de esta la mitad va por mí a saco
clear
claro
I mean, let's go, let's go, screwed, let's go, let's go
o sea vamos vamos jodidos vamos vamos a
see what he's posting on Twitter
ver que está poniendo en twitter
to be at the event
de estar en el evento
heart
corazón
what makes the tournament so sad haha
que hace sagrera del torneo jaja
Javier is in
javier está en
Javier and this one in skeet craft and mine
javier y de esta en skeet craft y mía
I also beg heaven to kill him for me
también suplico al cielo que me lo mate
babu
babu
and if not, let him die in the first game
y si no que muera en el primer juego
There is no need to beg heaven either
tampoco hay que suplicarle al cielo
a lot
mucho
leave it well and tell me in the tournament
lo deja bien y me dirá en el torneo el
cognac that paints Joel and measure the ski
coñac que pintas a joel y medir el esquí
Michael's game, a 40-year-old man who
game de michael un señor de 40 años que
lives at the expense of the sun, one heard of
vive a costa del sol se oía hablar de
the others why not better include
los demás porque no mejor incluyen a
forward or someone from the attack for sure
delantero o alguien del ataque seguro
you need the money more or
hace falta le hace más falta el dinero o
be all of the [ __ ] is
sea todas de la es
Regarding mackerel, why not better?
tocante la caballa o sea porque no mejor
They bring in the striker or someone from the attack
meten al delantero o alguien del ataque
I'm sure the money is needed more than
seguro que hace más falta el dinero de
Here they put the forward is that this
aquí que metan al delantero es que esta
People, I really mean it, my goodness, well, listen
gente digo de verdad madre mía bueno oye
We're going to train in a while, right?
vamos a entrenar dentro de un rato no sí
Of course today's training could go
claro podría el entrenamiento de hoy va
to be amazing to give me half an hour
a ser increíble para darme media hora
that reacts a couple of things and
que reacciona un par de cosas y
we start to see preparing what you
empezamos a ver preparando lo que te
left your time the best
dejó tu tiempo lo mejor
It's what there is in the family, it's what there is
es lo que hay en familia es lo que hay
Well, let's see what I wanted before starting
bueno a ver quería yo antes de comenzar
with the training I wanted
con el entrenamiento quería yo
react to a couple of a couple of
reaccionar a un par de un par de
little things then like
cosillas entonces como
How are we not going to react to a couple of
como no vamos a reaccionar a un par de
little things of the night how are we going to
cosillas de la noche cómo nos vamos a
relate to the entire range as I have
relacionar a la gama entera pues he
I don't know if there would be a video here.
corrido aquí un vídeo no sé si habría
right because I haven't seen
acertado porque no he visto
I have seen absolutely nothing here
absolutamente nada he visto aquí un
video of the best moments is worth tickets
vídeo de mejores momentos vale entradas
epic prizes and outfits okay if not
épicas premios y outfits vale si no
We have enough outfits here.
tenemos aquí suficiente con los outfits
We have here a branded article in the
tenemos aquí un artículo de marca en el
I think all the outfits are there
que creo que están todos los outfits
Okay so let's go to them family let's go
vale así que vamos a ellos familia vamos
to see the best moments and see what
a ver los mejores momentos y a ver qué
such
tal
the fact goes very well he crashes very well
el hecho va muy bien él choca muy bien
the best I think goes too far for
el mejor yo creo que va demasiado para
my taste, that is, I see more of a little thing
mi gusto o sea yo veo más una cosita
like the m of show or like for example it was
como el m de show o como por ejemplo fue
the Jordi While that will now be released here in
el jordi while que saldrá ahora aquí en
the video too but I did this
el vídeo también pero yo he hecho esto
I see him in a wedding suit
lo veo traje de boda
I see this, I don't see wedding dresses.
esto lo veo trajes de boda no lo veo
for one for the event
para una para el evento
decimario a little thing like that and you know one
decimario una cosita así y saben una
stuff
cosa
I don't see the point in this
esto no le veo sentido a esto
like the first time I'm live
como primera vez que estoy en directo
Greetings to all, a hug now many
saludos a todos un abrazos ahora muchas
thanks to people of 40 years and then to
gracias a gente de 40 años y entonces a
see that everyone can go as they want or
ver que cada uno puede ir como quieran o
It seems to me that the project is going to be disguised
bien de proyecto me parece ir disfrazado
a little not
un poco no
[Music]
[Música]
very handsome very handsome
guapísimos guapísimos
very handsome
guapísimos
the thing about the lot of fabric no
lo de los mucha tela no
Look, he has a cool vibe that I don't like.
mira que tiene un rollo guay que no me
dislikes when the photo of the PSUV as it has
disgusta cuando la foto del psuv como ha
dressed normally in your style is fine
vestido normalmente a su estilo vale no
I dislike this thing about blogs
me disgusta pero esto de los blogs
and kripper addresses for the truth and
y direcciones kripper por la verdad y
disguised thank you very much miss
disfrazado gracias señorita muchas
thank you
gracias
I think it's good
me parece bueno
horrible horrible horrible horrible
horrible horrible horrible horrible
the prettiest the prettiest
la más guapa la más guapa
the prettiest
la más guapa
what are you doing
qué haces
[Music]
[Música]
welcome
bienvenido
that about the cri but not for that either
que sobre lo del cri pero tampoco para
take it so seriously to see if it is serious
tomárselo tan en serio a ver si es serio
Of course you have to know how to be in the right places
claro hay que saber estar en los sitios
No
no
you have to know how to behave
hay que saber estar
Please what is this look I love it
por favor que es este look me encanta lo
I swear I thought it was
juro que pensé que está
mistaken
equivocado
exploded
explotó
the uncle belt
el cinturón tío
It seems that he is in disguise, it seems that he is
parece que va disfrazado parece que es
a child who has gone down to the park for the
un niño que ha bajado al parque por la
late it is me for example I did not have it
tarde sea yo por ejemplo no lo tenía
That's why I'm telling you
por eso de que te digo yo
5 or 6 years or something and I would go down to the
5 o 6 años o cosas y yo me bajaba a la
street and also had the neighborhood up to the
calle y además tenía el barrio hasta la
people from the neighborhood fed up with it
gente del barrio hasta los no
because I was going down the street halfway
porque yo me bajaba la calle medio por
Superman and he came down dressed as Superman
superman y bajaba vestido de superman
but of course not dressed as superman with a
pero claro no vestido de superman con un
powerful suit a handsome costume no no no
traje potente un disfraz guapo no no no
blue pajamas or blue pajamas and some cases
un pijama azul o pijama azul y unos caso
from the red site outside the pajamas
del sitio rojo por fuera del pijama
and now I was dedicated to hiding for
y ahora yo me dedicaba a esconderme por
all corners of the parking lot
todas las esquinas del aparcamiento
under my house and every time I passed by
debajo de mi casa y cada vez que pasaba
some gentleman or lady
algún señor o alguna señora
from here
de aquí
and Taiwan when the boy you like
y taiwán cuando el chico que te gusta
that is with all the news and you
que está con todas las novedades y te
you put them on at the same time like a t-shirt
las pones a la vez en plan una camiseta
from supermario a mickey pants
de supermario un pantalón de mickey
mouse and a donald duck belt and you
mouse y un cinturón del pato donald y te
You put it all at once because everything
lo pones todo a la vez porque todo te
I like it a lot and even if I don't but that's it
gusta mucho y aunque no pero pues eso es
what this belt has done with
lo que ha hecho o sea este cinturón con
this sweatshirt with him with this cap the
esta sudadera con él con esta gorra la
erase appears is that the cap appears from
borra aparece es que la gorra aparece de
These bad caps that they give you in the
estas gorras malas que te regalan en la
gas station
gasolinera
It is possible to thin it out for today, it was serious
es dable de raleo por hoy era en serio
red is what you have come to spend it
rojo es lo que habéis venido a pasarlo
Well as we are well we come to the
bien como estamos bien venimos a los
slam awards when right now I don't
premios slam cuando ya ahora mismo no me
I think the first thing that is here is a
creo que esté aquí lo primero que hay un
lots of people behind me I can't
montón de gente detrás mío yo no puedo
do this without greeting them hello guys
hacer esto sin saludarlos hola chavales
how are we
cómo estamos
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
I have done it very well in your style
lo he hecho capaz muy bien a su estilo
the shoes are what I don't like, honestly
los zapatos lo que no me gusta la verdad
the suit
el traje
Well, a little old-fashioned for my taste.
bueno un poco anticuado a mi gusto
Vicente, thank you very much, but nothing for him.
vicente muchas gracias pero nada para él
For good, I don't like shoes
para bien los zapatos no me gustan
To all of you watching the stream
a todos los que estáis viendo el stream
and well I hope it's a good night
y bueno espero que sea una buena noche
for everyone especially for me I have
para todos especialmente para mí yo he
come to win and compete in everything
venido a ganar y a competir en todo lo
that we can base that it is difficult when
que podamos bases que es cuando
You compete against the best, Jordi Vienes.
compites contra los mejores jordi vienes
Besides, I will do great for him.
además yo le irá estupendamente
this is the roll of like this is how
este es el rollo de me gusta así es como
I would be trending more than ever
yo iría siendo tendencia más que nunca
yes welcome
si bienvenida
Are you going to call me a party pooper or
yo me vais a llamar aguafiestas o
bitter or whatever is fine but the thing about it
amargado o lo que sea vale pero lo de lo
of the grace now of mister since it is
de la gracia ahora de míster ya que esté
the joke about Mr. already gay is in fashion and
de moda el chiste de míster ya gay y
I don't understand these things then it is
estas cosas no lo entiendo entonces es
that I am very bomber because this mind
que estoy muy bomber porque esta mente
They are my age, they must be my age or older
tienen mi edad ya tendrá mi edad o más
You know why he goes with this in his mouth?
sabes pero porque va con esto en la boca
and with that necklace and what's the joke
y con ese collar y cuál es el chiste
I think these people have the group made
creo que esta gente tiene el grupo hecho
when he decides to take someone like
cuando le da por a alguien como
meme as if it were a joke that wasn't
meme como si fuera una gracia que no
It's funny, man, how much they go further.
tiene gracia tío lo que van a más no
can
poder
you are already a misunderstood genius
ya eres un genio incomprendido
But you apply to me what is the grace of
pero me aplicáis cuál es la gracia de
that a gentleman
que un señor
I am ashamed of Ribry, he invited me to
yo a ribéry avergüenza a mí me invitó a
a gala going with a ball put in the mouth
una gala ir con una bola mete en la boca
I would be ashamed
me daría vergüenza
don't try to understand it enjoy it but
no trates de entenderlo disfruta pero
let's see the god
vamos a ver el dios
knowing how to listen half done is normal
saber escuchar medio hecho es normal
that he's crazy the farm is crazy
que está loco la granja está loco
I have doubts because I wanted to do
me nace la duda porque yo quería hacer
an interview but if you have that side
una entrevista pero si tienes ese lado
that it is not a taste of answering me
que no sea sabor a de responderme
This event
este evento
brilliant
genial
a round of applause a round of applause you know I'm the one
un aplauso un aplauso sabe yo soy el
interviewed and I would say
entrevistado y yo diría
Please take that out of your mouth.
te quita eso de la boca por favor que te
interview that I don't understand anymore Greece that
entrevista que no entiendo ya grecia que
He is already 27, this man is 27 years old
ya tiene 27 este hombre tiene 27 años
the only person who has a category
la única persona que tiene una categoría
for him alone
para él solo
how you live that moment that says no
cómo lo vivís ese momento que dice no
Check out the creation awards for
mira los premios de la creación de
content a category that is time
contenido una categoría que es tiempo
that you carry it
que la llevas
[Music]
[Música]
So
así
whatever is best for my 3 year old son
sea lo que sea lo mejor a mi hijo de 3
years thanks in fact seven thousand
años las gracias de hecho siete mil
five hundred euros behind gestures
quinientos euros detrás gestos
I wouldn't try at the highest border level
no intentaría al máximo nivel frontera
with the clock
con el reloj
really pure charade how am I going to do so
realmente puro paripé como voy a tan
few things because it's cool to at least go
poquitas cosas pues mola por lo menos ir
well dressed is good it's not that
bien ir bien vestida va bien no es que
go bad but don't me
vaya mal pero no me
you have the opportunity
tienes la oportunidad
ah
ah
Yeah
sí
There is a part that I saw
hay una parte que vi
There is a part that I saw that said in the
hay una parte que vi que ponía en el
clip of Dario's punch in the face
clip del puñetazo de darío m leche a
Oslo as a joke at the gala
oslo como un chiste en la gala
I don't know if you will put it to those who
no sé si lo pondrás a quienes te
they solve but literally it is as if it were
resuelven pero literal es como si fuera
a joke is punching someone
un chiste es pegar un puñetazo a alguien
and break a tooth
y partirlo un diente
to literally assault someone
para agredir a alguien literalmente
assault someone
agredir a alguien
I'm going to give a gift
voy a hacer un regalo
no this is a filter a filter of
no esto es un filtro un filtro de
internet or for you to do what you want
internet o para que te hagas tú lo que
you want to spectacular everyone in the
quieras espectacular a todos los de la
gala
gala
with the logo
con el logo
a filter so that they do what they want to you
un filtro para que te hagan lo que
you want
quieras
Let's see, there are dark-skinned people just for the sake of it.
a ver existen los morenos por ser
party pooper or anything I understand that the
aguafiestas ni nada yo entiendo que el
humor within humor but humor in the background
humor en el humor pero humor de fondo
I already told you it's the same, I'm a
que ya te digo es lo mismo soy yo un
a little bitter, maybe I'm a little
poco amargado lo mismo soy un poco
bitter but pot humor
amarga pero humor de porros
I smoke them, they are terrible
yo lo porro son malísimos
very bad and the worst there is
malísimos y lo peor que hay
and you tell me when you do it when
y tú me dice a mí cuando lo haces cuando
you are 15 years old, 14 or 16, which are average and
tienes 15 años 14 16 que están medios y
clean wants to do the huayno to you don't you
limpia te quiere hacer el huayno no te
wants to feel displaced because you are not there
quiere sentir desplazado porque no estás
in a group that does it and well since
en un grupo que lo hace y bueno ya que
was spending as why not smoke a
fue gastaba como porque no fumarse un
joint from time to time but it leaves you
porro de vez en cuando pero te deja
It makes you look stupid and now that's what you're doing
te deja y ahora eso te va
killing neurons
matando neuronas
The worst is the worst, so that suits you
lo peor es lo peor o sea eso te va
killing neurons until
matando neuronas hasta que
[Music]
[Música]
Okay, there I will leave it. I will put it.
vale hay dejara lo pongo
okay air something whatever the neurons that
vale aire algo como sea las neuronas que
they kill you the pores are totally
te maten los poros son totalmente
irrecoverable
irrecuperable
You understand me, fats are not funny or
me entendéis no es gracioso las grasas o
drugs are not funny it is not
las drogas no son gracioso no es
funny you don't understand
divertido no entendéis
All drugs are bad but there are
todas las drogas son malas pero hay
some that are worse live in crystal
algunas que son peores habitan cristal
no but it is not glass
no pero que no se trata de cristal se
try to recommend something good to people
trata de recomendar a la gente algo bien
that you have that smoking problem
que tú tienes ese problema que fuma
joint well okay if you have that one
porro bueno vale pues si tú tienes ese
problem, then do it yourself in your [ __ ] house and
problema pues hazlo tú en tu casa y
don't do it and don't let your
no lo hagas y no se lo hagas ver a tu
public
público
like a funny japo rosso thing
como una cosa divertida japo rosso
first when you are 40 years old
primero cuando tienes 40 años
one defines is a limit of humor
uno define es un límite del humor
but let's normalize things like some
pero que normalicemos cosas como unas
thanks then no
gracias pues no
that we normalize things like one like one
que normalicemos cosas como una como una
funny jokes about alcohol is okay
gracia bromas de alcohol está bien
Well, neither, neither, but the one who is
pues tampoco pues tampoco pero el que es
the worst are the joints
peor los porros
It's that the glass joints are worse than me
es que peor los porros a cristal que me
I have to laugh that it's at a gala
tengo que reír de que es en una gala se
I'll give you a payroll in the mouthpiece
nomina te regalo en la boquilla
parcel delivery in whatever
paquetería en lo que sea
Let's see what scandalized me that I join
a ver que me escandalicé que yo me junto
with a lot of people who smoke it
con un montón de gente que lo fuman que
energies to crystal and I was shocked not
energías a cristal y me escandalicé no
They scandalize me, I assure you that I in the
me escandalizan os aseguro que yo en la
life I traveled to analyze a joint you
vida me viaje a analizar de un porro os
I assure you
lo aseguro
Thank you very much, welcome to the King
muchas gracias bienvenido a rey
I assure you that it will be that it makes me
os aseguro que será que a mí me hace
I would miss a lot of things
mucha falta cosas muy a mí me haría
There is a very serious thing missing for
falta muchísima una cosa gravísima para
shock mommy
escandalizar mami
for youth and life and everything that
por la juventud y la vida y todo lo que
I lived, I guarantee you, but that is already
vivió yo os lo garantizo pero que ya
I'm old enough so I already see it.
tengo una edad entonces yo ya lo veo
made is a mouthpiece with the logo of the
hecho es una boquilla con el logo del
internet or a kid does it with
internet o lo hace un chaval con
3D printing
impresión 3d
This kid is cool
este chaval va guay
and that kid is doing super well but
y ese chaval va súper bien pero
you lack street look surely when
te falta calle mira seguramente cuando
you had been inacio when you had
usted había inácio cuando usted habéis
born had already lived life and knew
nacido ya había vivido la vida y sabía
everything that was everything in life that
todo lo que era todo en la vida el que
Apple, our comment is missing.
apple que nuestro comentario te falta
street that if you think you're cool because you see in
calle que si te crees guay porque ves en
tweets to people who smoke joint or who
tweets a gente que fuma porro o que
They make pot jokes and that makes you
hacen chistes de porro y eso te hace
feel older, well, congratulations to you
sentirte más mayor pues enhorabuena te
I pat you on the back twice but I
doy dos palmaditas en la espalda pero yo
I tell you that I don't think it's funny
te digo a ti que no me parece una gracia
it is a responsibility
es una responsabilidad
that is done and then they are people who
que se haga eso y luego son gente que se
They are shocked that they are promoting
escandalicen de que se hagan promo de
betting houses, do you understand me?
casas de apuestas me entendéis
I assure you that you cannot tell me that
ya te aseguro que a mí no me digáis que
You are missing a street, precisely on my street
te falta calle precisamente a mi calle
There's just more to it, there's too much for me
nomás falta más sobra demasiado para mi
I like more hours
gusto más horas
too much for my taste
demasiado para mi gusto
please
por favor
Argentina everywhere in the house
argentina en todos lados en la casa
Argentine health at home I always heard of
salud argentina en la casa siempre oí de
Nate and he told me yes yes that he was
nate y me comentó sí sí de que le estaba
giving a type of liquor I don't know if it is
dando un tipo de licor no sé si es
reliable or not but it takes a little
confiable o no pero lleva un poco
intoned can be
entonado puede ser
in tune but we were drinking rum
entonado pero estuvimos tomando ron
Well no, I mean, it can't look bad on you.
bueno no o sea no te puede quedar mal
never
nunca
crack in what we were taking very
crack en lo que veníamos tomando muy
good rum
buen ron
The one who is half bad is Marquitos
el que está medio mal es marquitos
because marquitos didn't eat so he
porque marquitos no comió así que el
Marquito is complicated, take advantage of it and
marquito está complicado aprovéchenlo y
brings hunger how handsome you are
trae el hambre qué guapo que os
lm that's [ __ ] great to be talking about
lm eso va de madre estar hablando
of a thing that is not
de una cosa que no
there is a clip of you
hay un clip tuyo
Saying hello from grandma
diciendo hola de la abuela
very good
buenísimo
thank you so much
muchas gracias
and there is no air in Paula you are not here
y no hay aire en paula no estáis
Moderating, we talked about people like this
moderando se habló de gente como este
who has put the copy seven times and
que ha puesto siete veces el copia y
It still sticks to me, it took away my kawaii, that's not it
pega igual me quitó kawaii eso es no
delete the comment and you'll be banned
borrar el comentario eso es baneado
those banned in the back and of that caliber
esos baneados en atrás y de ese calibre
is banned
es baneado
by cable or
por cable o
I take off, I don't know what your copies have
me quito no sé que vuestro copias lleva
ten minutes putting the same and that's it
diez minutos poniendo el mismo y eso es
ban look there you have it through
baneo mira ahí lo tienes a través de
cloth put so you can do it
tela puesto para que lo puedas manera
okay that's that's hiding user in the
vale ese eso es ocultar usuario en el
channel people like that are banned in this
canal sean baneado gente así en este
channel already outside understands me is located
canal ya afuera me entiende se halla
I've never gotten into you know that never
nunca me he metido a ya sabéis que nunca
ban and has never hidden a comment
baneo y que nunca ha ocultado comentario
but from now on it will be
pero ya a partir de ahora se va a
model
modelar
no no 20 minutes and that's not it
no no a 20 minutos y eso no
That's already dizziness and everything that is hater
eso es ya mareo y todo lo que sea hater
on the channel that puts me nonsense of
en el canal que me ponga gilipolleces de
for example when I talked about milk
por ejemplo cuando he hablado de leche
from the strider to people who do not comment
del strider a la gente que no comente
with respect and let them leave that hidden
con respeto y que sean deje eso oculta
on the channel and never comments again
en el canal y no comenta nunca más la
life for example today when I have put I have
vida por ejemplo hoy cuando he puesto he
made the video of dalla via's stress-
hecho el vídeo del estrés de dalla via-
people but justify this one from Nauta
gente pero justifica este el de nauta
hidden outside you can't comment on
ocultado fuera no puedes comentar en
this channel through all the videos
este canal mediante todos los vídeos
that in line that is not seen
that in line que no se ve
that done with the wall only remains
that hecho caso con la pared solo queda
during the nothingness, a dog understands me
durante la nada me entiende perro de
Dallas
dallas
hidden okay shut your mouth that is
ocultados vale cierren la boca que está
speaking my father exactly
hablando mi padre exactamente
exactly that they cry and get frustrated
exactamente que llore y que se frustren
with the wall and only I understand myself
con la pared y yo solo me entiende
and up to here everything is discussed with respect
y hasta aquí se comenta con respeto todo
the gossip of all the toilets without
el cotilleo de todos los aseos sin
disrespect the people in the chat
faltar el respeto ni a la gente del chat
neither to the people in the chat nor to the streamers
ni a la gente del chat ni a los streamer
of what we are talking about is worth it
de los que estamos hablando vale
So that's why the chapas is open
entonces por eso el chapas está abierto
now because it will be able to be open
ahora porque se va a poder estar abierto
because the least you can do is screw up
porque el mínimo que meter la gamba
hidden point
punto ocultado
hasn't stopped putting the same thing all the time
no ha parado de poner lo mismo todo el
Annika is a little bit worried, but he will be a 78 year old kid.
rato annika pero que será un crío de 78
years that I continue with the internet or the heras
años que siga yo internet o y las heras
from hahaha joints when that kid
de jajaja porros cuando ese chaval
He still doesn't even know where the seeds come from
todavía no sabe ni de dónde nacen los
children
niños
you understand me
me entendéis
They are the mentalities of young people who see
son mentalidades de chavales que ven
youtuber that makes them grow like
youtuber que los hace crecer como
Diaz for this event
díaz para este evento
very good, very well put together, I liked it
muy bien muy bien montado me ha gustado
a lot
mucho
for a topic
por un tema
let's go look for him I'll look for him and get him to you
vamos a buscarlo le voy a buscar y te lo
I bring yes
traigo sí
Well, it has a very roll
bueno lleva un rollo muy
good good
bueno bueno
the first entry honor is very bad
la primera entrada honor es muy malo
It is an honor for me to be here in the
para mí es un honor estar aquí en el
canary david first entry of
canario david primera entrada de
our prizes there was desire or that there is
nuestros premios había ganas o que haya
He looks a lot like a reggaeton singer.
mucho parece un cantante de reggaeton el
Daddy Gabino, nothing is going well, it's going well, it's going well.
papi gabino no nada va bien va bien va
Okay, handsome, I'm glad you like the idea.
bien va guapo la gana te gusta la idea
It's not normal to see "Forgive me for everything" say
no es normal ver a perdóname todo diga
but the oven thing is not normal
pero lo de horno no es normal
I respect
yo respeto
but it doesn't remind me of my moments of
pero no me recuerda mis momentos de
hater with you javi and yet always
hater contigo javi y sin embargo siempre
They were very respectful with me, I'm glad
fueron muy respetuosos conmigo me alegro
having rectified that laughing with
de haber rectificado aquel riendo con
glasses thanks region thank you very much here
gafas gracias región muchas gracias aquí
The salsa dancer is going to go one way or another
ya el salsero va a ir de una forma
different we are giving it a beating
diferente le estamos dando una caña al
awesome channel but already garbage and
canal impresionante pero ya basura y
toxicity and that [ __ ] is not going to happen here
toxicidad y esa aquí no se va a
allow here to gossip and talk about
permitir aquí sé cotillea se habla de
the 62 the controversy with all the
los al 62 la polémica con todo el
respect and the minimum of little garbage and
respeto y el mínimo de poca basura y
disrespect and those girls to everyone
falta de respeto y esas niñas a todos
these disgusting people of this type or because
estos asquerosos de este tipo o porque
those who have appeared and in the chapa no
los que han aparecido y en el chapa no
We have mentioned the internet or what
hemos mencionado de los internet o que
objectively
objetivamente
objectively totally criticizable that
objetivamente totalmente criticable que
a person in a program or equal
una persona en un programa o sea igual
which I find totally objectionable and
que me parece totalmente criticable y
It is unfortunate that in a program in a
lamentable que en un programa en un
podcast that has thousands or tens of
podcast que tiene miles o decenas de
thousands of viewers are added to a
miles de espectadores se le agrega a un
partner, that is, one of the presenters
compañero o sea uno de los presentadores
add to the other and treat it as a bm
agrega al otro y se trate como un bm
It is okay to treat it as a meme that is
vale que se trate como un meme que se
treat it as a grace
trate como una gracia
[Music]
[Música]
and on top of that there are brands making memes
y que encima haya marcas haciendo memes
With that, I am equally criticizable.
con eso pues igual de criticable me
It seems that they appear at a gala of this
parece que aparezcan en una gala de esto
and look, I'll give you a mouthpiece and they will do it
y mira te regalo una boquilla y se hagan
jokes about joints or glass or anything, me
chistes de porros ni cristal ni nada yo
I can guarantee that you have seen
puedo garantizar que yo habéis visto
photos of me when I was young I can guarantee
fotos mías de joven yo puedo garantizar
that things like that don't scare me at all
que a mí cosas de esas no me asustan al
On the contrary, already at 36 years old, I can say
contrario ya con 36 años o puedo decir
that I look back
que miro atrás
I look at myself when I was 18 and
que me miro a mí cuando tenía 18 años y
the brave [ __ ] who flaunt
los valientes que ostente
I should have given it to your father in all
tenía que haber dado a tu padre en toda
the mouth
la boca
really the things you do
de verdad las cosas que ustedes hacen
thanks to the kids I'm a fan of
gracias a los niñatos que soy fan de los
YouTube offends you and they put those things on you or
youtube ofender y os ponen esas cosas o
give and shame well I'm not going to give you
dar y vergüenza bueno no os voy a dar
embarrassed to ask I'm not public you
vergüenza preguntar no soy público usted
you are not going to see your own
no vais a ver vuestros propios
comments in 20 years but you
comentarios dentro de 20 años pero os
You will be ashamed and you will understand it and what
daréis vergüenza y lo entenderéis y qué
Xavi was right, what a shame today
razón tenía xavi qué vergüenza de hoy
What a stupid [ __ ] PSOE
que tonto psoe
I offend less, it seems regrettable to me
yo ofender menos me parece lamentable
precisely because you like both
precisamente porque tú te gustan ambos
two pieces that even Pau is already a member of
dos piezas que hasta pau ya es miembro
exactly in another pothole in the
exactamente en otro bache en por los
other members there are literally no if not
otros miembros no hay literalmente si no
They do it for you based on what you spent on
te lo hacen por lo gastado en
favorite subscriptions be it
suscripciones de favorito sea sea
that you have a problem that your escape
que tú tienes un problema que tu fuga
because you're hooked on weed or
porque estás enganchado lo porro o
because there are people who are hooked on
porque hay gente que está enganchada a
the joints and if not he won't sleep if he doesn't
los porros y si no no duerme si no se
smoke a good joint okay
fuma un porro bueno vale
I think it's all a matter of the Sami mind.
yo creo que todo es cosa de mente sami
suddenly you know it suddenly it occurs to me
de repente ya lo sabéis de repente se me
I decided to quit smoking tobacco and I did it
ocurrió dejar de fumar tabaco y lo hice
If you want to know how I have improved, how it will go
si queréis como he mejorado cómo va a
improve health I can raise lower the
mejorar la salud puedo subir bajar la
awesome staircase
escalera de madre
I take the shopping for the child's stroller to the
subo la compra del carro del niño al
child in my grandmother's arms at
niño a mi abuela en brazos por las
stairs to a fifth and new hobby and
escaleras a un quinto y nueva afición y
Literal ones don't give me heartburn anymore, you don't give me heartburn
literales ya no me dan ardores no me das
burning, nothing to eat makes me sick
ardentía no me sienta mal nada de comer
You don't know how life changes
no sabéis lo que cambia la vida
drugs all drugs are very bad
drogas todas las drogas son malísimas
there is more and less is noticeable in the voice according to
hay más y menos se nota en la voz acordé
that many times there are already more drugs
que muchas veces ya hay más hay drogas
in ban - it's not that the alcohol is going to go away
en baní - no es que el alcohol a se va a
fix in the mentality of the one who will
fijar en la mentalidad del que habrá
put that what will it have
puesto eso que tendrá
15 years or 14 years is not that alcohol
15 años o 14 años no es que el alcohol a
week is that it is not about your hand you
semana es que no se trata de tu mano tú
- it's about not inciting or treating it
- se trata de que no incite o lo trate
as a grace nothing hears that I one day
como una gracia nada oye que yo un día
Here I have a beer, well then I
aquí me tomo una cerveza bueno pues me
I have a beer
tomo una cerveza
because I am responsible for saying that is
porque yo soy responsable de decir o sea
Well, look, a beer, she commented tomorrow.
pues mira una cerveza comentó mañana la
beer I can have a beer
cerveza yo me puedo tomar una cerveza
every month or every two months
cada mes o cada dos meses de una
a little drink on special occasions
copichuela en las ocasiones especiales
Okay
vale
what makes bad good is different damage to
qué hace mal bueno es diferente daño a
something else different what happens as for
otra cosa diferente lo que pasa como por
example with the joints and that's what I
ejemplo con los porros y es a lo que yo
I meant that it is irreparable damage
me refería que es un daño irreparable
There are other drugs that harm you
hay otras drogas que te hacen un daño
more or less repairable than the body
más o menos reparable que el cuerpo se
regenerate whatever is worth it
vuelve a regenerar lo que sea vale esa
part of the body that is affected can be
parte del cuerpo que es afecta se puede
To improve, you can treat anything but
mejorar se puede tratar lo que sea pero
the damage of the joint is completely
el daño de los porro es completamente
irreparable and when you are 40 years old and
irreparable y cuando tengas 40 años y
you talk like an idiot
hables como un
and you can't relate to people who
y no te puedas relacionar con gente que
not be those in the square below
no sean los de la plazoleta de abajo de
your house then you will be ashamed
tu casa pues entonces te darás vergüenza
and you will remember what is happening to you
y te acordarás de lo que te está
saying wise man limeira
diciendo sabio limeira
You understand me and I'm not going to say if the
me entendéis y no voy a decir si el
alcohol has been gone for more or less
alcohol hace más o menos de que no soy
Doctor, I don't understand but I can guarantee
médico no entiendo pero puedo garantizar
I know people who smoke for years
que conozco gente que fuma por los desde
does
hace
20 30 30 years and you listen to them talk and
20 30 30 años y tú los escucha hablar y
I tell you
les digo
and they make me ashamed
y me dan vergüenza
because they don't connect one sentence with the other
porque no conectan una frase con la otra
well and they tell you things that are not true
bien y te dicen unas cosas que no no son
smart
inteligentes
You know what to exercise and what to do.
sabéis lo que hay que ejercitar y a lo
that you have to get hooked on reading to see
que te tienes que enganchar a leer a ver
documentaries to inform you about things
documentales a informarte de las cosas a
things that get you high, man
cosas que te suben tío
He understands me and that's it, and if there is someone
me entiende y ya está y si hay alguien
who doesn't understand it because he sees his
que no lo entiende porque ve a su
YouTube that ha ha ha ha humor well no no
youtube que ja ja ja ja humor pues no no
It's funny and I respect anyone who smokes it.
es gracioso y yo respeto al que lo fume
Okay, he doesn't respect that I don't smoke, I've met him
vale no respeta que no fume he conocido
many people who have smoked but did not
mucha gente que ha fumado pero no lo
treated my audience on the internet as if
trató en internet mi audiencia como si
It would be a grace simply that you
fuera una gracia simplemente eso que tú
you format them perfectly
te los formatos forma perfecto
but don't treat the mayor as if he is
pero no trates el intende como que es
funny and like making a
gracioso y como haciendo una
normalization of avalanches no
normalización de aludes no
in my opinion
en mi opinión
the video and appears
el vídeo y aparece
and
y
friend for me we should all
amigo para mí tendríamos que todos
Well
bueno
we do a 32 13 21 h but how would they be
hacemos un 32 13 21 h pero como serían
This is how you can interpret it, nobody is
así lo podéis interpretar nadie es
perfect perfect let's do the
perfecto perfecto vamos a hacer los
guys and sincerely that I respect and
chicos y sinceramente que yo respeto y
friends, I always mark it well, all the
amigos lo marca yo bien siempre todo el
roll but we are criticizing ourselves
rollo pero estamos criticando nos
We are here to criticize each other then
estamos aquí para criticarnos entonces
you give the same impression
ustedes da la misma impresión
you give it to the same person
ustedes dan os da la misma el mismo
bearing and gives you the same impression
porte y os da la misma impresión
gref I love how it goes I love it
gref que me encanta cómo va me encanta
how it will give the same impression made
cómo va a dar la misma impresión hecho
that this
que esto
that is, the same impression
o sea la misma impresión
asked
pregunto
or it doesn't matter, it looks just as pretty
o da lo mismo se ve igual de bonito
he is the protagonist
él es el protagonista
but it still works great
pero igual va de madre
to you at the Palau de la
a ustedes a la vista en el palau de la
music from Barcelona, uncle
música de barcelona tío
No
no
this also for your string to do
esto también para tu string para hacer
I thank you, as far as I know, for making you one.
las gracias yo que sepa para hacerte una
story something to sleep maybe
historia algo para dormir a lo mejor
These clothes are also for sleeping but for
esta ropa también para dormir pero para
the Palau de la Msica in Barcelona, uncle
el palau de la música de barcelona tío
would be like that you can interpret it nobody
serían así lo podéis interpretar nadie
It's perfect, perfect, let's go, let's do it
es perfecto perfecto vamos vamos a hacer
the boys all together this microphone by
los chicos todos juntos este micro por
here to begin, let the beginnings begin
aquí a que empiece que empiecen los
They're throwing this at Costco, this to me
están tirando un así a costco esto me
It sincerely seems like one of the most
parece sinceramente de las cosas más
surrealists of history for the
surrealistas de la historia para lo
You heard what I said, let's go.
habéis oído como he dicho vamos si
we are
estamos
worth 3 2 1 3
vale 3 2 1 3
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
[Music]
[Música]
your [ __ ] mother the best prize
tu madre el mejor premio
and the award for 'best game of the year'
y el premio al 'mejor en juego del año
is
es
attentive some 151
atento algunos 151
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
Which of the angers causes so much of it?
por cuál de los enfados salen tantas la
last a prize
última un premio
They are giving the latter a prize for
le están dando a último un premio por
get angry and throw [ __ ]
enfadarse y tirar
the tortilla side
la tortilla lado
This tyrant Saddam and Schuster
este tirano sadam y schuster
the anger that is the one that the one that the one that the
el enfado que es el que el que el que la
messed up about the tortilla
lió por lo de tortilla
for that anger
por ese enfado
he gets angry not seriously
él se enfada no en serio
[Music]
[Música]
It's really a shame that my first prize
manda güevos que el primer premio de mi
life be this
vida sea éste
sends egg spears and well for
manda lanzas de huevos y bueno por
last to say that the content that most
último decir que el contenido que más
I enjoy myself, I'm not in tortilla land
disfruto yo no estoy en tortilla land
because I can't get out of the house brand
porque no me sale de la marca casa
man in general is for all
hombre en general es por todos los
anger
enfados
It's for everything in general
es por todo en general
please of the honors
por favor de los honores
What I don't like about wearing is the
lo que no me gusta de llevar es el
hairstyle that we always go for
peinado para el que siempre vamos a
erase or do not comb much the same
borrar o no se peina mucho igual no
the prize for that I say but wind and le
el premio a eso digo yo pero wind y le
won
ganaba
wind the wind will go much better and more
wind the wind irá mucho mejor y más
funny the one with the box
gracioso el de la caja
totally wind and he won
totalmente wind y le ganaba
The wind will suit him better, yes.
el the wind irá mejor a ese sí que le
missing street
falta calle
roger of the year that agent max or
roger del año esa agente max o
ah
ah
Hello everyone
hola a todo el mundo
saliva
la saliva
because I think I'll put on
porque pienso ponerme
like the wolf
como el lobo
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
I feel super supported by
ciento me siento súper arropado por
all of you who I have contained that speak
todos los que he contenido que habláis
super good of me and I many years in
súper bien de mí y yo muchos años en
this and I always felt super good with
esto y siempre me sentía súper bien con
you already thanks to my friends to me
vosotros ya gracias a mis amigos a mi
family and everyone and for being
familia y a todo el mundo y por estar
here by
aquí por
because I have no idea right now
porque yo no tengo ni idea ahora mismo
clip of the year the new right of the crash
clip del año el derecho nuevo del choque
It's the same thing, the PNC hate as a grace
es lo mismo la pnc odio como una gracia
and thanks does not have the one of let's play
y gracias no tiene el de vamos a jugar
that funny system of repairs
ese sistema divertido el de los reparos
things on twitter
cosas en twitter
I would give the prize to the one whose
yo le daría el premio al de al de el
grandfather
abuelo
grandfather's grandfather good but grandfather
ar del abuelo abuelo bueno pero abuelo
his
suyo
the clip of the year
el clip del año
2021 goes to Sergio Kun Aguero
2021 va para sergio kun aguero va a
play
jugar
totally totally something let's go
totalmente total algo vamos
good to play
bueno jugar
the anger that ended up getting into the FM
el enfado que terminó metiéndose al fm
from a hater
de un hater
that ends up making the frivolous hater
que termina mente hacer el frívolo hater
all to me
todos a mí
[Music]
[Música]
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
ah
ah
[Music]
[Música]
Yeah
sí
percent is recording audio
ciento está grabar audio
if you had to win a prize for something
si tuvieras ganar un premio por algo
well it didn't work out
bien no se dio
[Music]
[Música]
Rajoy
rajoy
x
x
please
por favor
[Music]
[Música]
and the people are gone
y la gente hay partido
as
cómo
That's the expert, look at my dog.
ese es el perito mira mi perrita
[Music]
[Música]
I'm splitting my sides with the expertise
me parto el peritaje
after the piece of speech that you
después de el pedazo de discurso que te
You have marked I am going to ask you a favor
has marcado yo te voy a pedir un favor
you could
tú podrías
just for a second take that off
solo durante un segundo quitarte esa
ball from the mouth and give us a
pelota de la boca y regalarnos un
Do it with grandma in your mouth, please.
hazlo con la abuela en la boca por favor
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
doing many years
haciendo muchos años
do not fail others
no faltes a los demás
I love whoever edited this video
me encanta el que ha editado este vídeo
the one who uploaded this to a
el que ha subido esto que a una
compilation asking for subscription
recopilación pidiendo la suscripción
Do you think they have hired people to
tú crees que hayan contratado gente para
wait outside and I fill the theater with
esperar afuera y yo llenar el teatro del
event I have my doubts
evento yo tengo mis dudas
thoughtful of another full of youtubers are
pensativa de otra llena de youtubers son
youtuber and family members of youtube in the
youtuber y familiares de youtube en los
that are filling the family theater
que están llenando el teatro familiar
for sure yes
seguro que sí
Thank you all so much, it really is
muchísimas gracias a todos de verdad es
an award that makes me very excited
un premio que me hace muchísima ilusión
There is a lot of work behind it and my
hay muchísimo trabajo detrás y que mi
family is supporting me that the
familia está estás apoyándome que los
streams that I respect so much
streams a los que tanto respeto me
supported makes me eternally happy and
respaldó me hace eternamente feliz y
I live for my profession and I will follow it.
vivo para mi profesión y lo seguiré qué
They gave us the prize for the crash that has seen us
premio le dieron al choque nos ha visto
I don't know what prize they gave him for crashing.
no qué premio le dieron a chocar
stop putting that will tell him the shock
dejar de poner a que le dirá la choca
You see, you're almost 30 years old.
ya ver que ya tienes casi 30 años la
half of what you have, grandpa Javi, hehe
mitad de lo que tienes abuelo javi jeje
and the award to Dallas for the YouTuber with
y el premio a dallas por el youtuber con
more money donated than the 10,000 bitcoins
más dinero donado de los 10 mil bitcoin
better the crash first
mejor es primero el choque
better this email
mejor este email
the revelation
a revelación
Well, but for me it would have been me, Juan.
bien pero para mí hubiera sido yo juan
For me today it has been Juan, grace is
para mí hoy ha sido juan la gracia es
It's fair that there are people like you who know it
justo que haya gente como tú que se lo
takes everything too seriously and is
toma todo demasiado en serio y es de
Crystal, you are cannon fodder for this
cristal eres carne de cañón para esta
People, you're 40 years old, brother, stop being
gente tienes 40 años hermano deja de ser
so boring you have no grace or
tan aburrido no tienes gracia ni
own content and that's why you limit yourself to
contenido propio y por eso te limitas a
comment
comentar
But don't be so friendly.
pero a ver no te hagas tanto amigos
He has taken the name Javi das Pena
se ha puesto de nombre javi das pena
because we will have it now, the chat is valid
porque lo habremos vale ahora el chat
challenge of the whole level but we are going to
safía de todo el nivel pero te vamos a
hygiene
higiene
that is
o sea eso
A kid who is not Spanish is worth it
un chaval que no es español vale es un
kid who has Spanish and look what
chaval que tiene español y fíjate lo que
has burned down
se ha ardido
what has burned or is that you have not
lo que se ha ardido o sea no habéis
banned many people there are now no
baneado mucha gente hay de en ahora no
you know banned three more people or
sabéis baneado a tres personas más o
at least three people more or less
menos no sea tres personas más o menos
Well, one of those three is so angry and
pues uno de esos tres está tan rabioso y
can't stand that you get involved and that
no puede aguantar que te metas y que
criticize your youtube and how
critiques a su youtube y como las
ways of air chat has been spent a
maneras del chat aire se ha gastado un
euro to do it like that and not even the
euro para hacerlo así y ni siquiera la
I wanted to be like his name and handsome
quería ser como con su nombre y apuesto
Javi, you're pathetic.
javi das pena
You really just left me with everything.
de verdad que ya me acabas de dejar todo
striped uncle
rayado tío
He really just left me now
de verdad que ahora me acaba de dejar
all scratched up dude
todo rayado tío
You've already hurt me, my friend, you've left me
ya me has hecho daño amigo me has dejado
fatal the whole chat is with you
fatal todo el chat está contigo
long live the joints
vivan los porros
no no no
no no no
and on top of that he'll have screwed it up
y encima y encima la habrá
spend the euro in the worst way and doing
gastarse el euro de lo peor y haciendo
for every friend
para todo amigo
that you have won Islam the clips very
que has ganado el islam los clips muy
characteristic you could tell to shut up
característicos podrías mandar a callar
to everyone who is watching us with
a todo el mundo que nos está viendo con
a small gesture of yours because
un pequeño gesto de los tuyos porque
what is our camera in the background
cuál es nuestra cámara al fondo
from the screen
de la pantalla
talking
hablando
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
and the winner of the talk show of the year is such
y el ganador al talk show del año el tal
show
show
the talk show evidently without any
el talk-show evidentemente sin ninguna
doubt
duda
without a doubt
sin ninguna duda
without a doubt Jordi Gual
sin ninguna duda jordi gual
but let's go without any doubt there is no
pero vamos sin ninguna duda no hay
competition there is no competition no
competencia no hay competencia no
for the awards and above all for the
por los premios y sobre todo por la
song from before and such because it is that
canción de antes y tal porque es que lo
has won the wild project
ha ganado the wild project
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
[Music]
[Música]
but without a doubt that is the way the roll
pero sin duda o sea la manera el rollo
that carries the deal is the best would be
que lleva el trato sea la mejor estaría
It's good that there was internet or also
bueno que hubiera el internet o también
because one of his teeth broke already
porque se le rompió un diente a uno ya
It would already be the last straw for awards.
ya sería el colmo ya de los premios
First of all, thank you very much
primero de todo muchas gracias
I like the gala a lot, it is very good
me gusta la gala mucho de está muy bien
It is very professionally made, removing a
hecha está muy profesional quitando un
a couple of very professional little details, very
par de detallitos muy profesional muy
professional seems to have organized
profesional parece que han organizado
people who have been doing it all their lives
gente que llevan toda la vida haciendo
this kind of things and I think this
este tipo de cosas y yo creo que este
prize
premio
the case that people organize takes him
el caso que organiza la gente le lleva
still a certain thing and you want it done
todavía cierta cosa y queréis lo ha
hired clear really is the prize
contratado claro realmente es el premio
to a content although change and green
a un contenido aunque cambio y verde
the same as the site on the internet for the
igual el sitio para en internet para el
content as of the same project a
contenido como de igual proyecto un
content where people get wet where
contenido donde la gente se moja donde
we talk about complicated topics sometimes
se habla de temas complicados a veces
[Music]
[Música]
you could
podrías
I was about to be
estuve a punto de ser
murdered by Pablo Escobar we have
asesinado por pablo escobar tenemos a
go get if they are going to kick me out
pasar a conseguir si me van a echar de
your fifteen twenty million visits
tus quince veinte millones de visitas
for 260 literally
por 260 literalmente
It is a type of SEO salt
es un tipo de sal seo
It is a type of salt or people get it
es un tipo de sal se o la gente se le
He thinks he's the CEO, but he's the one
cree que es el ceo nada más que es el
salsa youtuber, I would recommend him
salsero youtuber sea yo le recomendaría
to the people who watch the fae video
a la gente que mira el vídeo de la fae
what made the good salsa singer bad and
che que hizo del salsero bueno malo y
you will understand that the clear salsa singer here
entenderá que el salsero claro aquí lo
What happens in Spain that the birth of the
que pasa en españa que el nacimiento el
Sar made nachos for himself as a YouTuber
sar se lo hizo nachos al ser youtuber
Okay, then of course you infer that I don't know
vale entonces claro infiere tú que no sé
why did he have so much hate
por qué tenía tanto hate
ease that was a little that the salsero
facilidad que era un poco que el salsero
empty to the secret of ownership that
vacías al secreto de propiedad de que
It wasn't that it wasn't harmful either, it was nacho
tampoco era que no era dañino sea nacho
get rid of your view that people threw at him
deshace de tu ver la gente le echaba
a lot of hate and all he did was
mucho hate y lo único que hacía era
clear is the month and see was the one that gave
claro es el mes y ver era el que dio
bad image of the salsa singer really is
mala imagen al salsero realmente sea
because Nacho literally comes out to tell you
porque nacho sale literalmente contarte
what happened in two minutes point ni
lo que pasaba en dos minutos punto ni
he thought
opinaba
read tweets look at this
leer tweets mira este
spot
punto
and people threw hate at him and said what?
y la gente le tiraba hate dijo pero qué
there is something wrong with what he does
tiene de malo lo que hace
does not understand that he has bad desires
no entiende que tiene malos deseos son
many things to the pse or anything
muchas cosas al pse o de cualquier cosa
that it may have become controversial
que sea polémica puede haber salido
even video games can have salt
hasta los videojuegos puede haber sal
be vital and then the slam prizes
ser vital y entonces los premios slam
These will be complete the year you
éstos estarán completos el año que le
put the salsa category because it is
metan la categoría del salsero porque es
one more category
una categoría más
award for 'best
premio al 'mejor
the best salsa channel because it is a
el mejor canal de salsa porque es una
category more
categoría más
so when I accept it is the policy it is
entonces cuando acepte es la política es
to the PSE or politics and many to being
al pse o la política y muchísimos al ser
many to the pse or in what series of this
muchísimos al pse o en qué serie de esta
people who make tortillas
gente de la que hacen de tortilla la
denied the I don't know that there is no salt or if it is
negó la no sé que no hay sal se o si es
that the salsa dancer is what moves them
que el salsero lo que los mueve
but that is not good enough for many people
pero eso no bien queda mucha mucha gente
It is not that the jump in the content of this
no es que el salto del contenido de este
new controversial video I don't know what's not worth it
nuevo vídeo polémica no sé que no vale
but that within our series you talk
pero que dentro de nuestra serie habláis
at 66 to the CEO no then Jordi while
al 66 al ceo no entonces jordi while
I say it right there
mismo yo digo ahí mismo
did a super practical thing and
hizo una cosa súper y práctica e
hypocrite from the other day that we were
hipócrita del otro día que lo estuvimos
seeing
viendo
It was when the punch to Dario happened
fue cuando lo del puñetazo a darío que
It was put on one of those channels, I don't know if
se puso en uno de esos canales no sé si
shitty
de
effectively in the 200 channels
efectivamente en los 200 canales
So you're not going to go to the shitty gentleman.
entonces al señor de no va por
finally gave wings and not 800 channels that have
fin dio alas y no 800 canales que han
uploaded they have commented on the click of the
subido le han comentado el clic del
Dario's punch, no milk, and now he
puñetazo de darío m leche no y ahora él
I had two videos talking about the punch
tenía dos vídeos hablando del puñetazo
from Dario of ph and it is that all this
de darío de ph y es que todo este
content is salsa in a way
contenido es salsero en cierto modo
He takes an uncle who almost kills him
se lleva un tío que casi lo asesina
Pablo Escobar was free to go
pablo escobar se llevaba libre para
I don't know how to talk to you about the NFC coins.
hablarles de los nfc de la moneda no se
They were left as soon as they are salted by Manuel
quedaron en cuanto son sal seo a manuel
Salcedo del corazn is not salsa de
salcedo del corazón no es salsa de
YouTube is not the server for all salsa
youtube no es el servef al salsero todo
whatever salsa salsa rica
lo que sea salsa salsa rica
Let's see the gentleman, it's not an interview, it's not
a ver al señor no es entrevista no son
interviews
entrevistas
They are talks, it is not, it is not, they are not
son charlas no es no es no son
interviews other things are talks
entrevistas otras cosas son charlas
you understand me
me entendéis
30 thousand dollars then Xavier one
30 mil dólares entonces xavier una
Madness those months in fact is not any
locura esos meses de hecho no es ninguna
song sorry to those who sing of
canción lo siento a los que cantan de
true because he made it into a
verdad porque él lo convirtió en una
song
canción
It was [ __ ] great, it was there all the time.
de madre estaba todo el rato ahí
with the topic and toxicity out and the
con el tema y toxicidad fuera y la
I really remember it with great pleasure.
verdad que lo recuerdo con con gran
Honey, thank you very much, Lucas is a genius.
cariño muchas gracias lucas es un crack
tasty
sabroso
please also the honors of the
por favor también los honores de la
community and extreme voting
votación de la comunidad y los extremos
okay let's go
okay let's go
sports player of the year
jugador de sport del año
has two networks
tiene dos redes
but a good idea was completely missing
pero faltó completamente buena idea
[Music]
[Música]
And Daddy Gabi is a very good person.
y es que papi gabi es buenísima personas
from Oslo
de oslo dio
start to the person
inicio a la persona
[Music]
[Música]
and fun to snack on with the 100
y divertido ya para picarlo con los 100
I have told people this a lot at some point
personas lo he contado alguna vez mucho
time and I have some photos with him
tiempo y tengo alguna foto con él
right now where would the photo be
ahora mismo donde estaría la foto
the interview I did with him was destroyed
a la entrevista que le hice de destrozó
in a comment and you limit yourself to
en un comentario y te limitas a
respond by saying that you earn more than me
responder diciendo que ganas más que yo
and my parents
y mis padres
It shows how much pain remains,
demuestra la pena queda así lo mucho que
you know you are not capable of entertaining
sabes que no eres capaz de entretener
by yourself and you refer to comment
por ti solo y te remites a comentar
content from others
contenido de otros
worth two thousand viewers two thousand
vale dos mil espectadores dos mil
spectators in this right in that of
espectadores en este derecho en el de
in the afternoon talking about the heart six
por la tarde hablando del corazón seis
a thousand how many you have you are before another
mil cuántos tienes tú estás ante otro
euro and you tell me or not better yet
euro y me lo dices o no mejor aún
raise the call, raise the debate
sube la llamada sube a debatir
and
e
a debater now comes in and will believe that
un debatido ahora entra va a creer que
will rise
subirá
believes that his life
cree que su vida
[ __ ] but the interview that is televised
pero la entrevista que televisa
Papilla is already older than he sings
papilla tiene ya más años que canta
forward was not even known for stinging
palante no era ni conocido para picar
well when it says before seen
bien cuando dice antes vista
truth
vera
it was not even known to catch
no era ni conocido para pillar
since you have my interview four years ago
desde tu tiene mi entrevista hace cuatro
years
años
has three thousand visits
tiene tres mil visitas
in 2017 the papyrus channel
en el 2017 el canal de papiro
has the channel because a person who
tiene el canal porque una persona que
come on we are
pasa estamos
to interview him again
de entrevistarle otra bien
chat
charla
and
y
selling a motorcycle you don't have or you have
vendiendo una moto no tengas o tienes
some of you don't know how hard they were
algún no sabéis el trabajado que eran
this interview
esta entrevista ción
you don't know the job interview
no sabéis el trabajo entrevista
you have depends on the parts tested I
tienes depende de las partes probados yo
I'm noticing 53 thousand subscribers had
estoy notando 53 mil suscriptores tenía
to snack and here
para picar y aquí
I'll come up whenever you want now please
subo cuando quieras ahora por favor
right now
ahora mismo
right now please
ahora mismo por favor
you tell me
dime tú
Tell me a link to some good street art.
dime un enlace de street art bueno
when we do it to connect because
cuando lo hacemos para conectar porque
if I was hiding you without putting your
si te estaba ocultando sin poner tu
name how do we do it
nombre como lo hacemos
like the week
como la semana
play me your record
ponme tu disco
Please play me your CD
ponme tu disco por fa
and I add you and you accept me
y te agrego y tú me acepta a mí
Let's see the photo I had with daddy.
a ver la foto que yo tenía con papi la
life of this
vida de ésta
I want you to see me with daddy I saw her
que quiero que me veáis con papi la vi
we do it
lo hacemos
Oh
ay
Haiti with Daddy the Vine
haití con papi la vid
I'm going to say that young people are [ __ ] crazy.
voy a que jóvenes suelos pues
It's been five years since this
hace cinco años de esto
what jacket is
qué chaqueta está
what jacket is a blue jacket
qué chaqueta está una chaqueta azul
I don't even know what jacket it is
no sé ni qué chaqueta es
okay okay
vale vale
that if heavy that Javier is all that
que si pesado que javier es todo lo que
you say but he is there every day
dices pero él todos los días está
in front of thousands of people and we
delante de miles de personas y nos
It entertains, I'm sure it pisses you off that I say
entretiene seguro que te jode que diga
the truth about the YouTubers you like
la verdad de los youtubers que te gustan
and you walk around crying long live the churra
y andas llorando viva el churra
No, but they have warned me about something, Paulo.
no pero me han avisado una cosilla paulo
He warns me of something, he's not right
me avisa una cosilla no tiene razón
Don't give him any more ball, 9 is more ball
no le deis más bola 9 es más bola
let him spend the money because
dejarle que se gaste el dinero porque
I'll say it tomorrow, I'll remember it tomorrow
ya lo diré mañana acordarme mañana
past
pasado
remind me tomorrow the day after to say it
recordarme mañana pasado que lo diga el
because
por qué
although well we could be careful and
aunque bueno podríamos tener cuidado y
period no I don't know I don't know if but
punto no no sé no sé si pero
It has already been explained why you can't, okay?
ya se explicó porque no puedes vale
ignore him
pasar de pasar de él
good for snacking and we like it very much
bueno para picar y nos cae muy bien a
all
todos
[Music]
[Música]
the roads
los caminos
Please whenever you want, gorgeous ua
por favor cuando quieras guapísima ua
bitter prison dance of the year is for
prisión amarga baile del año es para
who have nominated and it's going to go well
quienes han nominado y va a ir a bueno
but daddy Gabi without a doubt and DJ Mario
pero papi gabi sin duda y dj mario
yes yes if you want to go up, go up, go up
sí sí si quieres subir que suba que suba
for pillay
para pillay
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
[Music]
[Música]
and I just want to say something before
y simplemente quiero decir algo antes de
leave
irme
[Music]
[Música]
thank you
gracias
more lack of euros
más falta de euros
to
a
I'm going to give a gift from the position
de posición voy a hacer un regalo
no this is a filter a filter of
no esto es un filtro un filtro de
internet or for you to do what you want
internet o para que te hagas tú lo que
you want efe
quieras efe
worth the 15 that passes
vale al 15 que pasa
that we have him called to a play in
a que lo tenemos en llamado a un play en
Seriously, first they are here
serio pues primero aquí si están
calling a [ __ ] they called you
llamando a un te han llamado
Damn Buddhism, come on, tortilla, damn it
el budismo vamos tortilla
ah
ah
how do they change the rubber on the auro?
como auro le cambian la goma al
microphone every week
micrófono cada semana
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
Hey, now you hear me.
oye ahora me escuchas
I heard perfectly that they were like this no
escucho perfecto que eran como esto no
It will be a video that is not strange that had this
será un vídeo no es raro que tuvo este
video if you want a live pcr no
vídeo si quieres una pcr en directo no
I already did that and I don't recommend it.
eso ya lo hice yo y no te lo recomiendo
I really don't recommend it much.
la verdad no te lo recomiendo mucho
Now um as of next highlight
ahora um como de siguiente destacado
author to see your scholarship is fasting from
autor a ver tu beca se ayuna del
antigen that from the stick
antígeno que desde el palito
There is a shooting that is with the stick uncle
hay una de tiro que es con el palito tío
what a mess
vaya telita
I am not able to get into it as much as
yo no soy capaz de meterme lo tanto como
only
solamente
a great project
un gran proyecto
I feel with Kobe but very happy
me siento con kobe pero muy contento la
truth is a project that we exposed
verdad es un proyecto al que expusimos
lots of love and hey it looks like this
mucho cariño y oye que se ve así
recognized the truth is that [ __ ] what
reconocido la verdad es que qué
disgust the truth is that I feel very
asco la verdad es que me siento muy
proud
orgulloso
look man
mira tío
in trauma life today in draw my life is
en trauma la vida hoy en draw my life es
the CNDH I will be brief yesterday they were held
la cndh seré breve ayer se celebraron
The awards are organized by
los premios están organizados por
decree in order to reward and
decreto con el fin de premiar y
recognize the work of the best
reconocer el trabajo de los mejores
Spanish-speaking streamers of 2021
streamers hispanohablantes del 2021
truce by seven thirty everything was
tregua por las siete y media todo estaba
perfectly arranged in the palau de
perfectamente dispuesto en el palau de
Barcelona's music with a red carpet
la música de barcelona con alfombra roja
and all the gala had more than one
y todos la gala contó con más de un
million viewers at its peak
millón de espectadores en su punto
high its very good the very good but already
álgido su muy bien la muy bien pero ya
I'll say it when I have a category for it.
lo digo cuando tenga una categoría para
the salsa singer then and waiting since
el salsero entonces y esperando desde
then the golden globes and placing
luego los globos de oro y colocándose
as the third most viewed string
como el tercero string más visto el
first also belongs to the grave and the
primero pertenece también al grave y el
second and by with the boxing evening
segundo y by con la velada de boxeo
Let's go with the winners and the best
vamos con los ganadores y mejores
moments
momentos
thanks to you ask me what I
gracias a usted me pregunta que me
You seem to be a very good presenter.
parece ores como presentador muy bien
very good very good very good very good
muy bien muy bien muy bien muy bien
very good very good did it very well these
muy bien muy bien lo hizo muy bien estos
It all started with the award from the CNDH
de es la cndh todo comenzó con el premio
to the best clip of the year that was awarded
al mejor clip del año que fue entregado
To the kun for his good we are going to play the kun
al kun por su bueno vamos a jugar el kun
aguero while drinking a little water began
aguero mientras tomaba un agüita comenzó
to talk about the book explosion
a hablar de la explosión del libro de
2020 to then release its good let's go
2020 para después soltar su bueno vamo a
the former footballer could not attend the
jugá el exfutbolista no pudo acudir a la
gala but connected to thank him
gala pero se conectó para agradecerlo a
then came the feil of the year that did not
continuación vino el feil del año que no
It could have been for someone else than for Ibai due to
podía ser para otro que para ibai debido
at the 40th Music Awards when
al momento en los 40 music awards cuando
covered the spectators' stomachs
tapó a los espectadores el vientre
Rosala and Rabo Alejandro, not even if they wanted to
rosalía y rabo alejandro ni queriendo
could have done better the anger of the
podría haberlo hecho mejor el enfado del
The year was tough but it was a pleasure
año estaba reñido pero fue a gustito
account and one who won the trophy
cuenta y uno quien se alzó con el trofeo
thanks to his attack against and open
gracias a su ataque contra y abro
quotes the brats who see and tortilla
comillas los niñatos que ven y tortilla
land
land
It's incredible that they gave him an award
increíble que le hayan dado un premio
that's why god
por eso dios
it's incredible
es increíble
incredible
increíble
v0 rsh numeral
v0 rsh numeral
8.453
8.453
Let's see, Paulo, write it down quickly, write it down
a ver paulo apunta lo rápido apunta lo
Paula, and quickly, we'll add it.
paula y rápido que lo vamos a agregar
now
ahora
He pointed at the pau and sent it to him via waza
apuntó a la pau le manda melo por waza
then for a snack at the dance of the
después para picadita en el baile del
A year later, Agent Max won the award for
año luego agente max obtuvo el premio al
'Best RealPlayer for its fans in GTA
'mejor realplayer por sus hinchas en gta
five who deserved the award left it
cinco que merecía el galardón lo dejó
clear when giving his speech
claro al dar su discurso de
gratitude following with your
agradecimiento siguiendo con su
Maxwell's character won the award for
personaje maxwell ganó el premio al
best iu sports player christina and
mejor jugador de iu sports christina y
nor for best reporter of the year in IES
ni a mejor reportera del año en íes
forks and expire
forks y caducar
Yes Christine and this year it has not been
si christine y este año ya no ha sido
summer sport
deporte verano
Christina and this year she has been a reporter
christina y este año ha sido reportera
Christina starts as a reporter
christina inicia en el sido reportero
the best caster of the year these two were
la mejor caster del año estas dos fueron
the only women awarded come and see
las únicas mujeres premiadas venga a ver
If next year any of them sneak in
si para el año que viene se cuela alguna
most streamer
streamer más
But what does it matter if they are women or that
pero que importa que sean mujeres o que
be men within the category
sean hombres dentro de la categoría lo
what there is to what there is man for me is
que hay a lo que hay hombre para mí es
from anger he should have won neither
del enfado lo tenía que haber ganado ni
Sanchez
sánchez
the best is first and rl was kid and us
el mejor es primer y rl fue kid y nos
Wind surprised and the truth is the wind
sorprendió wind y la verdad the wind
I enjoy as you well know it was more than
disfruto como bien sabes estuvo más de
700 hours of live viewing
700 horas en directo visitando
different Spanish streamers very much in tune
diferentes streamers españoles muy a la
height of the great docurealities of
altura de los grandes docurealities de
television and speaking of content
la televisión y hablando de contenido de
Television: The Wild Project won for Best
televisión the wild project ganó a mejor
talk show for its interview format
talk show por su formato de entrevistas
and we go again with ibai who won
y vamos de nuevo con ibai que ganó a
best song of the year with the quartet of
mejor canción del año con el cuarteto de
I was going with Luca Requena with whom
ibai junto con luca requena con quien
collected the award and art for the
recogió el premio y arte para los de
Luca Requena always beats me, right?
siempre me lo gana luca requena verdad
Well, since we're here, let's get to it.
bueno y ya que estamos vamos con el
rest of the prizes that he won and vai obtained
resto de premios que ganó y vai obtuvo
the award for event of the year with the
el galardón a evento del año con la
boxing evening although it was also
velada de boxeo aunque también estaba
nominated by other of his blessed ones
nominado por otros de sus benditos
events and the best cinema award and it is
eventos y el premio mejor el cine y es
that as I say now if someone deserves
que como digo ahora si alguien se merece
that prize that is you arrives in its
ese premio ese eres tú llegue en su
own category of jager of the year won
propia categoría de jager del año ganó
With his boxing jagger I received the award
con su jagger boxeador recibí el premio
with a black ball in his mouth he competed
con una bola negra en la boca competía
with Diamond Professor travel and arrive
con diamond profesor viaje y llegar
Princess Fernanflor won the award for
princesa fernanflor ganó el premio a la
best career for his great work
mejor trayectoria por su gran trabajo a
over the years he was not in the
lo largo de los años no estuvo en la
gala but sent a video thanking the
gala pero mandó un vídeo agradeciendo el
award another who could not attend
galardón otro que no pudo acudir al
Palau de la Msica was once a haurn but it
palau de la música fue haurón pero se
connected live to collect his
conectó en directo para recoger su
tortilla award from the CNDH, El Chocas and
premio por tortilla la cndh el chocas y
His 1,500 euro suit won the
su traje de 1.500 euros ganaron el
revelation streamer award because
premio streamer revelación porque
508 katiba bears is not the best suit
508 katiba bears no es el mejor traje
I didn't like this. You could see the prizes.
esto no me gustó pudiste ver los premios
Yesterday they seemed fair to you, that's fine by us, great.
ayer te parecieron justo nos vale genial
Friends, I did like them but in situ
amigos a mí sí me gustaron pero in situ
and put pressure on you left in this
y meter presión usted dejó en esto
also uncle has been but the week
también tío se ha hecho sino la semana
among all, a good category is missing
entre todo sea falta una categoría bueno
one or two categories for the salsa singer as well
una o dos categoría para el salsero así
No, not everyone is represented.
no no está representado todo el mundo de
the string vale
los string vale
Let's see, let's get that [ __ ] in.
a ver vamos a meter a ese no
We're not going to put that [ __ ] in here.
vamos a meter ese aquí no
and now we train, no paulo
y ahora ya entrenamos no paulo
what is 3 in the morning anyway
qué son las 3 de la mañana además
we put the [ __ ] in and train
metemos al y entrenamos
I can't tell that Paulo doesn't exist.
no me sale que no existe paulo ese
user
usuario
It tells me that it doesn't exist
me sale que no existe
Paula, I get that you need and use the
paula me sale que necesites y usar el
I'm sure he sends them well
seguro las manda bien
that the debate is only on YouTube for
que el debate sólo sea en youtube para
that not the law
que no la ley
okay okay okay
vale vale vale
completely
totalmente
thanks to less
gracias a menos
short family on twitch
familia corto en twitch
but we'll leave it to you to see if it exists
pero te dejamos a ver si existe
Now if it comes out, let's see if it exists and
ahora si me sale vamos a ver si existe y
when the so-called family comes in short
cuando entre la llamada familia corto en
tweet
tweet
short in tweets coming to youtube
corto en tweets venidos a youtube
and then we go back to tweets to sell on
y luego volvemos a tweets para vender en
trees
árboles
because my hand
porque mi mano
hello
hola
until I have
hasta que no tengo
second
segundo
the smell
el olor
I speak but I don't see you yet
yo hablo pero que no te veo todavía
but
sí no
This is a debate, man, I don't have to
esto es un debate tío yo no tengo por
why put on the camera by myself
qué ponerme la cámara yo solamente
I want to comment on some things here and why
quiero aquí comentar cositas y porque
you save tweets anyway or
guardas tweets de todas formas ni
it is not even necessary
siquiera hace falta
put the camera
poner la cámara
because
porque
with all due respect some need but
con todo respeto alguno necesidad pero
why don't you point the camera at what
por qué no pones la cámara hacia lo que
you can't show your face of fear
no puedes dar la cara de miedo
I don't feel like showing my face
no apetece poner mi cara
but sometimes we have to see the faces
pero a veces tenemos que ver las caras
that they put we have to see who you are no
que ponen tenemos que ver quién eres no
No
no
there is no need, there is no desire
no hay necesidad no apetece
almost any random emeterio any
casi cualquier random emeterio cualquier
anonymous string if either that or that
string anónimo si es que o bien que
comes and if it is
viene y si es
so anyone can take a chance on anyone
así cualquiera se la juega en cualquiera
brave because the problem is that I am
valiente pues el problema es que estoy
arguing as if arguing about
discutiendo como si esté discutiendo por
an anonymous person who does not show his face and
una persona anónima que no da la cara y
doesn't know who has that need
no sabe quién tiene esa necesidad
It is not necessary that
no hace falta que
Okay, now I'll change it.
vale ahora cambio lo
What do you say about boxing?
que dices de boxear
who doesn't understand that you don't need to
que no entiende que no hace falta que tú
to be debating a person knows
para estar debatiendo una persona sepa
his name and his surname nor his [ __ ] face
su nombre y su apellido ni su cara
arguing go argue then you
discutiendo ir a discutir entonces tú
You go up very cocky but they don't put the
subes muy gallito pero no ponen la
camera
cámara
who is the person and [ __ ] to another one
cuál es la persona y pollas a otro de
first is to say her first faults
primero es decir ella de primeras faltas
respect you say they earn more money
el respeto dices que ganan más dinero
that a person is a donation
que una persona es una donación
the twitter camera
la cámara twitter
I repeat, why do you need my Twitter?
te repito para qué necesitas mi twitter
so you are a rank that comes here
entonces eres un rango que viene aquí
says go crazy xxi you screw up nothing happens
dice enloquece xxi la cagas no pasa nada
because nobody knows who you are but but
porque nadie sabe quién eres pero pero
that you need there to be consequences
que necesitas que haya consecuencias
also what scares you of
también también que te da miedo a ti de
8 here giving face in my name all
8 aquí dando la cara en mi nombre todos
ways there are those who kingsley but you
modos hay quienes kingsley pero te
repeat repeat you are the stream I am not
repite repito tú eres el stream yo no
I am smart you are a person who accesses and
soy listo eres una persona que accede y
that she has a lot of nerve to come here
que la echa mucho huevo a venir aquí
enjoy even if you spend money
disfrutar incluso está gastado dinero
because it is work he saw as insulted
porque es trabajar vio como insultado
resulting in them not even being of
resultando que ni siquiera esteban a de
your chat that has plunged you to you to see
tu chat eso los ha sumido tú a tú a ver
also a man and tell me who is something
también un hombre y dime quién es algo
I probably played with the need for that
probable jugué con la necesidad de que
give you my name because you are so afraid
te dé mi nombre porque tiene tanto miedo
that I am not bonet because I am not
que yo no estoy bonet porque no me
I feel like boxing with two thousand people
apetece boxear mediante dos mil personas
we have had today
hemos tenido hoxe ar
They know what I
saben lo que yo
I listen, they listen to me but that I am
escucho me escuchan pero que yo soy
silly
tonto
and
y qué
It's easy to call people stupid no no
fácil es llamar a la gente tonto no no
nothing happens, let's see for real
pasa nada vamos a ver de verdad
you need me to say my name and I ask
necesitas que diga mi nombre y me pido
to be able to start talking to me
para poder empezar hablar conmigo
inside they obviously have to give me
adentro evidentemente me tienen que dar
the face
la cara
because you are simply a voice
porque eres simplemente una voz
who makes a fool of himself doesn't know who you are
que hace el ridículo no sabe quién eres
the invasion if it wants to come, it comes
la invasión si quiere si quiere venir da
the face if you don't go away
la cara si no vete
Let's see, I know who you are because you are
a ver yo sé quién eres porque estás
spend money on paypal you how much
gastar dinero por paypal tú cuánto se
knows who I am you how old is 23
sabe quién soy tú cuántos años tiene 23
years old and at 23 you dedicate yourself to
años y con 23 añitos te dedicas a
get so angry
enfadarte tanto
Don't interrupt, I'm talking to you.
no interrumpas que te estoy hablando
Listen, otherwise you won't know later.
escucha que si no después no sabes
answer at 23 years old he dedicates himself to
contestar con 23 añitos se dedica a
spend money to get a name
gastarte dinero para ponerte de nombre
in the donation
en la donación
Javi, you are [ __ ], you are 40 years old and you
javi tienes 40 años y te
you call the school
llamas al colegio
You think that by reading the name that
tú te crees que por leer el nombre que
I have put on the credit card
tengo puesto en la tarjeta crédito de
paypal payment is that my real name
pago de paypal es ese es mi nombre real
Listen to me carefully but this is
escúchame atentamente pero esto es
percent of the paypal account is not
ciento de la cuenta de paypal no la
you have with your real name is not a
tienes con tu nombre real no es una
PayPal account PayPal is a platform
cuenta paypal paypal es una plataforma
payment had a credit card for
de pago tuvo una tarjeta crédito para
pay obviously numbers my part there is
pagar obviamente números mi parte hay
that you have your original name registered
que tener tu nombre original registrar
your ID, we have also tasted said
tu dni demás hemos degustado dicho
sport as a payment platform with
deporte como plataforma de pagos con
credit card or author's name
tarjeta de crédito o un nombre del autor
and it turns out that I'm not stupid
y fuera que no soy tonto
you can't start the debate no
no puedes empezar el debate no
not with real structures in PayPal
no con estructuras reales en paypal
No
no
ask
pregunta
legal not what you do not
legal no lo que tú haces no
chiles without understanding that they don't realize you
chiles sin entender que no te dan cuenta
paypal but then now for a
paypal pero entonces ahora por una
card that doesn't have your name on it
tarjeta que no pones tu nombre
[ __ ] man
macho
through this
a través de esto
because money transactions
porque el dinero las transacciones de
money must be registered very
dinero tienen que estar registradas muy
good
bien
These cards are also my name
estas tarjetas también es mi nombre
wait the card has your name but
espera la tarjeta está tu nombre pero a
I can think of another name, the great studio.
mí me sale otro nombre el gran estudio
It's exactly the one that is most for me now
es exactamente el que más es para mí ya
We are calm and have our heads down.
está estamos tranquilos y bajada la cara
or you just walk away or you stay on
o simplemente vas alejados o sigues en
loop no
bucle no
You continue, I hope the camera doesn't go to me
sigues espero que la cámara no me voy a
put you're going to have enough with me
poner vas a tener el suficiente conmigo
This is an easy 6, let alone three.
este es un fácil 6 quite que decir tres
things
cosas
don't mediate and make a video
no mediatizar y hacer vídeo
If you don't go and don't show your face, you're a
si no vas y no va a dar la cara eres un
[ __ ] coward and he's going to
cobarde de y te va a
give
dar
It is not necessary to watch the race but
no hace falta ver la carrera pero
the things you put into what you do
las cosas que pones lo que haces
but this is funny that you need
pero este es gracioso que tú necesitas
you need more people
más necesitas personas
listen to me listen to me a world has no
escuchar me escucha un mundo no tiene
validity in the arguments of the
validez en los argumentos de las
people with whom you need to debate
personas con las que debates necesitas
know more about them than more than 15
saber más cosas de ellos que más de 15
have more friends imagine that I took
tienen más amigos imagínate que tomé
kinetic to me for something that you yourself have
kinética a mí por algo que tú mismo has
done on your twitter account but by
hecho en tu cuenta de twitter pero por
that is to look for where it is
eso es para buscar en donde se
turning points for something point of
puntos de inflexión para algo punto de
reference to throw here is not what
referencia para tirar por aquí no es lo
what do you need
que necesitas
But I repeat that I believe that this
pero te repito que yo estimo que este
text the cowardly state is on youtube
texto el estado cobarde está en youtube
with two thousand people, it seems bitter
con dos mil personas como que amargado
of money to put a message that is not
de dinero para poner un mensaje que no
you
le
It matters and I'm already thank you very much
importa y ya estoy muchísimas gracias de
The truth is that what touches me the most
verdad es que lo que más me toques los
balls is that you have an opinion and
es que a ti te con una opinión y
a reflection and your first answer is
una reflexión y tu primera respuesta sea
resort to what you earn more money than me
recurrir a qué ganas más dinero que mis
parents and that I think it is false, besides
padres y que yo que es falso además se
they are a real pain
tocan los
that will appeal yes
que recurrirá sí
the problem
el problema
from the image of the imagined
de la imagen de lo imaginado
evidently has no institutions
evidentemente no tiene instituciones
because maybe he's going to say things here
porque a lo mejor va a decir cosas aquí
He's going to throw something expensive at me that you are from
me va a echar cosa cara que tú eres de
leave me a lion even though you are not the lord
dejarme un león aunque tú no es el señor
Imagine what kind of mess they throw at me
imagínate qué minsur que me echan en
face that I mess with people
cara que yo me meto con las personas
blondes and now
rubias y ahora
but the stress that I am not a brother
pero que el estrés que no soy hermano
director, I'm the one explaining
director estoy el que está explicando
content is you I am a spectator
contenido eres tú yo soy un espectador
which is not the same at the same level of
que no es lo mismo en el mismo nivel de
my
mí
in the same voice as serious then good
en la misma voz que grave entonces bueno
It's that I'm serious so I'm very easy
es que soy grave entonces soy muy fácil
the real thing and then that
la cosa de verdad y luego eso
You have nothing to say, we have nothing to say
no tienes nada que decir no tenemos si
You don't have an answer to what I have
no tienes una respuesta a lo que tengo
that is, a person who donates saying
es decir una persona que dona diciendo
that you appeal is that it is true
que que tú recurre es que es verdad es
say you are in some way a
decir tú eres de alguna manera un
media parasite you don't need that
parásito mediático no necesitas que
other contents to exist and
contenidos demás para existir y
subsist because without the content else
subsistir porque sin el contenido demás
you do not exist that the content and that the
tú no existes que el contenido y que el
content would not be for him quoted for you
contenido no sería para él citó para ti
cons and original as for example is
contras y original como por ejemplo es
say I don't know how to put you live on tweets
decir no sé ponerte en directo en tweets
to play a video game and the ins and outs
a jugar a un videojuego y entretelas
people to create content to stay
personas hasta crear contenido quedar
play a video game play a
jugar a un videojuego jugar a un
video game own content
videojuego el contenido propio
because the video game is because it is
porque el videojuego es porque es
video game of the person who is
videojuego de la persona que está
training the clear
entrenando lo claro
that conclusion is quite stupid
esa conclusión bastante estúpido la
I'm telling you the truth, you depend on
verdad te estoy diciendo tú dependes de
continue others and comment on the content
continuos demás y comentas el contenido
and the one who plays video games depends on the
y el que juega a videojuegos depende del
video game
videojuego
and now well correct
y ahora bueno correcto
So what is the proper content?
entonces cuál es el contenido propio
but it is not even a little true
pero que sea verdad ni una mínima
response to what I told you
respuesta a lo que te he dicho
but for
pero para
that you ask yourself, I told you that
que te preguntes a ti te dicho que
It seems normal to respond to someone who
parece normal responder a alguien que te
donate and if he tells you he needs you
dona y de si te dice necesitas contigo
besides
además
failed or something like that I have not said
fracasado o algo parecido yo no he dicho
with literal words but it will even
con palabras literales pero hasta va a
understand that in fact you what are you
entender eso de hecho tú qué estás
talking about respect but if in that
hablando de respeto pero si en esa
donation in that first donation so
donación en esa primera donación tan
Nick Davis's post is delayed
puesto de nick davis
the next moment you have me
al siguiente instante tú me has
insulted, that is to say, well, no response
insultado es decir bueno de respuesta no
in response nothing happens
en respuesta no pasa nada
for you own content
para ti contenido propio
own content take a camera
contenido propio una cámara de
create a video and surpass a video of a
crearte un vídeo y supera un vídeo de un
example
ejemplo
favorite
favorito
I don't see much stress and you see me
no veo mucho estrés y me ve a mí que me
hates
odia
Success loves to see you if it is burned and
el éxito te ama ver si está ardido y
after up to 25 payments
tras hasta 25 pagos
40 year old [ __ ], really true
retrasados de 40 años verdad de verdad
that I really have no problem with them
que no tengo problema de verdad que los
Five payments don't matter to me, uncle.
cinco pagos me la traen al pairo tío que
I don't give a damn
me la sopla
you swallow a street was here well
te traga un street estaba aquí bien
where trick and work did so much that you
donde trick y trabajar dido tanto que te
you have spent money on being late
has gastado dinero en ponerte
and so offended because I told you that
y tan ofendido porque te he dicho que
You are silly and cowardly but I have had the
eres tontito y cobarde pero he tenido la
need to donate to comment
necesidad de donar te para comentarte
which I found quite funny
que me hacía bastante gracia
the whole theme of the crystal being and
todo el tema del ser de cristal y de
having to depend on other people
tener que depender de otras personas
to create your own content, that is,
para crear tu propio contenido o sea es
very easy but let's see, let's see, let's see it has
muy fácil pero a ver a ver a ver tiene
A daughter with three current ones does not define you
una hija con tres actuales no te define
answer that it is your own content
contesta que es para ti contenido propio
but tell me in streamer write the disc
pero dime en streamer escriba el disco
own mister view for example you know
propio míster vista por ejemplo sabes
Who is Mister Seen? I served that one
quién es mister visto me serví ese
Correct own content is not based on
contenido propio correcto no se basa en
the contests that he holds
los concursos que lleva
It is not the content, it is the one that organizes it
no es su contenido él es el que organiza
the entire event
todo el evento
and will organize, form, and search for newspaper archives
y organizarán formó y buscó hemeroteca
You are comparing me, that is, you think
tú me estás comparando o sea tú crees
you are at the same content level
estás al mismo nivel de contenido
original that mister seen I did not throw
original que míster visto yo no me eché
as if stopping with no one who you are
como parando con nadie el que estás
comparing in true each one has its
comparando en true cada uno tiene su
style and there will be people who like my
estilo y habrá gente a quien le guste mi
be good and now people who like you
ser bien y ahora gente que le guste
free and wise but that is not my
sabio libre y da no pero si eso no es mi
ask me I'm seeing you do you think that
pregunta te estoy viendo tú crees que
you are at the same level of originality and
estás al mismo nivel de originalidad y
of own content that mister seen
de contenido propio que mister visto
there will be people who think so and
es más habrá gente que piense que sí y
people who think that they don't
gente que piense que no
is
es
What I'm asking you is that I
que yo estoy preguntando a ti es que yo
I don't know, asking people automatically
no sé preguntando a la gente automático
but I'm answering you, that is to say,
pero yo te estoy respondiendo o sea me
serve yourself more and also replied that I am
servirse más además respondió que estoy
answering friend you don't listen apart from
respondiendo amigo no escuchas aparte de
Its author is deaf, they eat us, it's worth Viterbi.
su autor es sordo nos comen vale viterbi
It is based on the reactions that the
se basa en las reacciones que tiene la
people when he gives them money he is not
gente cuando él le regala dinero no está
2000 those questions ask me if you
2000 esas preguntas me pregunta si tú
You think it's the same level of
crees que es el mismo nivel de
originality and its own content that
originalidad y de contenido propio que
Mr. did you see that? That's a question there.
mister viste esa es una pregunta hay
who seems to be all about creating
quien parece que todo para crear
Contents are based on third-party things
contenidos se basan en cosas de terceros
200 put it everyone is based on
200 ponerlo todo el mundo se basa en
third-party content but they want Javi
contenido de terceros pero quieren javi
but if
pero si
I will answer you whatever comes to mind
yo te contestaré lo que me salga de la
dick if I don't you can't answer
si yo no no se puede responder
I mean the question is that you are at
o sea la pregunta es que es que estás al
same level
mismo nivel
level of content originality
de nivel de originalidad de contenido
own and your answer is
propio y tu respuesta es
There will be videos in which the
habrá vídeos en los que se dividirán los
no
que no
the squid game of my service to you
el juego del calamar de mi servirte
looks like original own content
parece contenido propio original
The Squid Game seems to me to be
el juego del calamar me parece que es
a
una
taken to Miami too but he himself
sacada a miami también pero el propio el
cep is inventing the idea of the game of
cep está inventa la idea del juego del
squid originally that he has
calamar originalmente ese él se ha
based on squid juice and I
basado en el jugo del calamar y yo me
I base it on the slopes and the fight that
baso en los faldeos y en la pelea que
have others, you don't see them and
tienen los demás no tú los ves y los
you put in your video is different and the
pones en tu vídeo es diferente y los
other days and provided information if I
otros días y aportó información si me
problems and I don't think it's bad that
problemas y no me parece mal que
I will dedicate commentary
dedicaré comentar
let me continue
me deja seguir
the
la
branch
rama
further
más
easy
fácil
[Music]
[Música]
you have millions of people on YouTube
tienes millones de youtube es de gente
that makes its own content I say that I know
que hace contenido propio digo yo que se
say the same on Saturday be the same me
diga el mismo el sábado ser el mismo yo
that I know original content of my own
que sé contenido original propio el
same serious making them the awards and
mismo grave haciéndolos los premios y
go to your live shows with but literally
vayan sus directos con pero literalmente
They are based on the cinnamon content
están basado en el contenido canela
we the people the people the people see
nosotros la gente la gente la gente ve a
I was there because he is funny because of his personality
ibai porque es gracioso por su persona
and goes and dedicates himself to reacting
y va y se dedica a reaccionar el
literally everything other people's content
contenido de los demás literalmente todo
the content of ibai is commenting
el contenido de ibai es comentando
games of the other games of the
juegos de los demás partidas de los
others or reacting to videos of the
demás o reaccionando a vídeos de los
besides those you are, you have the
demás de los que tú estás tú tienes al
Mr. Javier, the same but I was going
señor javier lo mismo pero iba
literally too
literalmente también
is dedicated to doing
se dedica a hacer
literally the same thing but with a different type
literalmente lo mismo pero con otro tipo
of content
de contenido
what is the difference between reactions or
cuál es la diferencia entre reacciones o
now the problem is not that it is
sea ahora el problema no es que sea
own now the problem is that if the
propio ahora el problema es que si el
whether or not
pse o no
the main difference
la diferencia principal
It's for nothing
es por nada
talking again but why have
otra vez hablando pero porque tener
because he relies so much on pasta that you
porque recurre tanto a la pasta que te
I was passing the money, uncle just told me
pasaba el dinero tío me acaba de decir
the difference between you and me I tell you
la diferencia entre tú y yo te digo me
because the main difference is that I
por la principal diferencia es que yo
because the pasta
porque la pasta
the
la
main difference because
diferencia principal porque
supports
apoya
but what would be the problem if it were
pero cuál sería el problema en que sea
main but why are you laughing like that
principal pero por qué te ríes como el
dog to discover the
perro de descubrir el
why he's nervous nothing happens but
por qué está nervioso no pasa nada pero
I can't mess with your physique
que con tu físico no me puedo meter
because he doesn't show his face but because he has
porque no da la cara pero porque tiene
that need
esa necesidad
Yeah
si
you do not depend on others, you look at them
no dependes de los demás las miras la
The miniature canteen you have doesn't come out
cantina miniaturas que tienes no sale
your face dude doesn't come out a match is
una tu cara tío no sale una match es
terrifying
acojonante
original is regrettable
original es lamentable
in humans
en el ser humano
You don't have a [ __ ] picture of yourself, man.
no tienes una foto tuya tío
literally in Sahara failing to achieve
literalmente en sáhara no logrando
you are literally entering it
literalmente estás entrando a la misma
non-right whose thumbnail is my face
non derecho cuya miniatura es mi cara
Congratulations, man, the only video, the only one
enhorabuena tío el único vídeo el único
video the only uncle
vídeo el único tío
literally from other people has 66
literalmente de otras personas tiene 66
and that's it, you don't realize it but
y punto no te das cuenta pero lo
we try people think alike time
intentamos personas piensan igual tiempo
But let's see the content then.
pero vamos a ver entonces el contenido
Ibai's own content and I love it
de ibai el contenido propio y me encanta
yes saliva and in the thumbnail but the
si saliva y en la miniatura pero el
content and vice versa own content
contenido y vice el contenido propio
because it appears in the thumbnail as
porque sale en la miniatura como
and for more factors but one of them yes
y por más factores pero uno de ellos si
you come out the miniature look I am how
tú sales la miniatura mira yo soy cómo
this works
funciona esto
the subject is main on youtube
la asignatura se principal en youtube
the title seems natural obviously
parece la natural el título obviamente
It is the most important thing on your channel
es el más importante mismo en tu canal
in which what is very easy to understand
en lo que lo que es muy fácil entender
that what you sell, even if you sell, is not
que tú lo que vendes aunque vendes no
you understand yourself you sell yourself
entiendes a ti mismo te vendes las
news
noticias
but but but never deduction and that
pero pero pero nunca deducción y eso le
It invalidates your personality a little.
quita validez de un poco tu persona
because people get in person with
porque la gente se mete en persona con
what I do on YouTube about myself
lo que haga en youtube de mi persona yo
I had people come to your channel for
tuve que la gente entra en tu canal por
the million
el millón
Okay
vale
That's all the double hatred when
eso es con todo el doble odio cuando
they talk about politicians
hablan de políticos
and you know which channel is the most
y sabes cuál es un canal el canal más
famous American salt seal
famoso de sal sello norteamericano
Philip de Franco
philip de franco
since you know what it is
desde que sabes cuál es
and you know which one is from the suitcase
y sabes cuál es de la maleta
quite quite pitiful the others
bastante bastante lamentable los demás
to keep the opinion away from everyone
para alejar la opinión para sí todos sí
but I usually support everyone but talk to them
pero todo me suelo apoyar pero habla con
respect uncle
respeto tío
scar I understand perfectly with him
scar entiendo perfectamente con el
ridiculous what are you doing because I don't
ridículo que estás haciendo porque no me
says to your face that the ridiculous thing is
dice en la cara que el ridículo si lo
Okay
vale
literally those channels are from
literalmente esos canales son de
salsa dancers and in all the miniatures
salseros y en todas las miniaturas se
they put themselves
ponen a ellos mismos
then that would be your own content plus
entonces eso sería contenido propio más
than yours
que el tuyo
from now on in my thumbnails
a partir de ahora en mis miniaturas
I decide to put my face on one side now
decido ponerme mi cara en un lado ya
It would be a player, it wouldn't be more content
sería player no sería más contenido
own in effect corona ok ok ok
propio en efecto corona vale vale vale
and it wouldn't be long now
y ya no tardaría
do not continue this extended pressure and
no prosiguen este presión extendido y
I extend I wonder
extiendo me pregunto
why do you have that need when the
por qué tiene esa necesidad cuando la
person who is not there because they are
persona que está no tiene porque están
testing my opinion
testeando mi opinión
But listen to me if it doesn't seem to you to have
pero escúchame si no te parece haberse
spent five times money to put a
gastado cinco veces dinero para poner un
little message to appear on screen for
mensajito para aparecer en pantalla para
insult
insultar
It really doesn't matter that there are 50 and
de verdad que no pasa nada que son 50 y
apart from no co-payments for people it is
aparte sin copagos para la gente es
much to prevent only supports for me
mucho a para prevenir sólo apoya para mí
This is rich and it is very cool the only thing that
esto es rico y es muy guay lo único que
It happens to you that you are a coward who does not put
te pasa que eres un cobarde que no poner
the camera but if it is served with these
la cámara pero si está servido con estas
spend money on a string to appear
gasta dinero en un string para aparecer
on screen I don't spend any money between
en pantalla no me gasta dinero entre
wind sting to enter into debate
viento sting para entrar a debatir
with you time
contigo tiempo
but not to face the hour of the
pero para no dar a cara a la hora de la
truth is it has no balls because it is normal
verdad no tiene huevo porque es normal
He's making a fool of himself but from the
está haciendo el ridículo pero desde el
ridiculous you are good not at all
ridículo tú eres bueno no del todo
Because you don't show your face, you're very cowardly.
porque no dan la cara eres muy cobarde
just because
porque si
not entirely, I repeat it to you again
no del todo te lo vuelvo a repetir el
little pig if he will return or not at all because
cerdito si volverá o no del todo porque
They don't show their faces because you are very cowardly
no dan la cara porque eres muy cobarde
not even so we can see what kind of
ni siquiera para que veamos qué tipo de
things write
cosas escriben
Twitter
twitter
and Facebook, Instagram and nothing
y facebook instagram y nada
What do you want me to give you on Instagram, God?
qué quieres que te dé mi instagram dios
so that we can see who you are, what things you put
al que veamos quién eres qué cosas pones
I have it and I don't feel like it
lo tengo y no me apetece
It's very easy, it's simply that you
es muy fácil es simplemente que a ti te
where with an opinion with a reflection
donde con una opinión con una reflexión
and you answer first with what
y que tú respondas de primeras con qué
you earn more money than my parents is very
ganas más dinero que mis padres es muy
sad uncle those things not the new ones
triste tío esas cosas no las nuevas
fairies because they were really sorry to tell you
hadas porque eran pena de verdad te lo
I say active and you should know that
digo activa y lo deberías saber tú que
You've been in this for a long time, you know the
llevas en esto mucho tiempo ya sabes el
to answer the to answer is that
responder a los a responder es es que
knowing that if you call me it has failed and
saber que si tú me llama ha fracasado y
I say to you no more parents
yo te digo a ti a no más padres
that
eso
It's very cool but I can't imagine that he is
es muy padre pero no me imagino que esté
very proud of you but listens less
muy orgulloso de ti pero escucha menos
If you call me, I had failed once
si tú me llamas había fracasado a mí una
person who earns what anyone else earns
persona que gana lo que gana cualquier
family in a year in a year and a half in
familia en un año en un año y medio en
A month doesn't seem like a failure to me.
un mes no me parece un fracaso
Does that seem like a failure to you?
a ti te parece un fracaso eso
is
es
what I'm saying but you don't have to
lo que estoy diciendo pero no tienes que
answer saying you have entered here
contestar diciendo tú has entrado aquí
implying that I have not failed
dando a entender que yo no fracasado
insulting and such
insultando y tal y que
don't speak loudly because you won't
no hables por lo alto porque no te
people listen if you speak loudly
escucha la gente si hablas por lo alto
I throw more haste than I have and for more
tiro más prisa que tenga y por más
nervous that there is the fact that you
nervioso que esté el hecho de que tú
you speak at the same time as me again continues
hables a la vez que yo otra vez sigue
when they talk no no no I don't hear you
cuando hablan no no no no te escucho a
people have to wait for them
la gente tienes que esperar que ellos
I ended up like this, that's what education is about
termine así es de eso trata la educación
so if you get into stress
entonces si tú entras en el estrés
tripling the problem that is
triplicando el problema que está
frustrated so much that he has done so much to you
frustrado tanto que te ha hecho tanto
damage that I tell you about money if you
daño que yo te digo del dinero si tú
You call someone a failure for doing what
llamas a alguien fracasado por hacer lo
what do you do at work? Well, I'll tell you.
que hace en su trabajo pues yo te
I answer that man is a failed person
contesto hombre es una persona fracasada
no win this no that is not a failure no
no gana esto no eso no es un fracaso no
show me where he gave me an option he
muéstrame donde me dio una opción he
saying that you are a failure you are giving
dicho que eres un fracasado estás dando
to understand that I am a sad person who
a entender que soy un triste que me
I dedicate myself to being 40 years old. I dedicate myself to
dedico a que tengo 40 años me dedico a
be salt I know or that it is not its own content
ser sal sé o que no es contenido propio
That's implying that I'm a failure, isn't it?
eso es insinuar que soy un fracaso no
and from my donation you get that you are a
y de mi donación sacas tú que eres un
failed is your problem to have l&amp;m all
fracasado es tu problema haber l&amp;m toda
prayer first memory agreement
oración primer acuerdo de memoria
lm your first donation
lm tu donación primera
behind
detrás
to understand more or less of the failure of
para entender más o menos del fracaso de
What a shame what I do no then I don't
qué pena lo que hago no entonces yo no
I'm doing quite well, I don't consider it to be a
me va nada mal no considero que sea un
failure but I'm not telling you
fracaso pero que yo no te está diciendo
that he is a failure if Mars is here
que es un fracasado si a marte hay aquí
three same people entertained or
tres mismas personas entretenía o sea
They won't kick you out that bad or if I'm not here
tan mal no echaran o si yo no te está
going that we are good because it is good for you
yendo que estemos bueno pues es bueno te
I'm being that it's wrong and that it's already a
estoy siendo que esté mal y que ya es un
Jason failure is my message is that
fracaso jason es mi mensaje es que
our message which one hundred in minutes
nuestro mensaje cuáles ciento en minutos
the only one
el único
the only thing that has been increasing
la única cosa que ha estado aumentando
is that you depend on that dependency and
es que tú dependes de esa dependencia y
That's what I have, the difficult thing is
eso es lo que tengo que lo difícil es
that you know and are able to give it a
que tú sepas y seas capaz de darle un
personal touch and give it some
toque personal y darle algo de
staff
personal
personal to a specific content
personal a un determinado a un contenido
that in the end you can make it into a magazine is
que al final lo puedas una revista es
say a magazine can take and you can
decir una revista puede y podéis
comment on the slam awards or whatever
comentar en los premios slam o lo que
sea no and sharon moment without any
sea no y sharon momento sin ningún
The problem is already out there, plan roll
problema ya está ahí fuera plan rollo
goal for more than the difficult thing is that you
gol a por más que lo difícil es que tú
give it a little touch and a spirit that
le des un toquecito y un espíritu que
mark your personality and your opinion
marque tu personalidad y que tu opinión
and that people take things for granted
y que la gente se te tomes las cosas por
do what you have to go to
hacer lo que tú tienes que ir al
respect and that's why you think that you believe
respecto y por eso crees que tú crees
that I don't give him a top house that I
que yo no le doy un top casa que me
string and my videos don't have a touch
string y mis vídeos no tienen un toque
staff yes but what I tell you
personal que sí pero que lo que te digo
I know which letter applies to us
yo sé cuál es la letra que se aplica nos
touch to why we are here that
toque a porque es que estamos aquí que
none of us understand turquoise which is the
ninguno entendemos turquesa cuales al
end
final
and on your channel what I believe is
y en tu canal lo que yo creo es
that loses a bit of personality and that
que pierde un poco de personalidad y que
then the personal issue
entonces el tema personal
What you told me is that your person loses value.
que me has dicho pierde valor tu persona
does not remain of value and people is not
no se queda de valor y personas no es
here internet my person computer and it
aquí internet mi persona ordenador y lo
that people on the internet don't know
que no conoce la gente de internet
that these businesses do not
que estos negocios no
Okay, I know that firsthand.
vale eso lo sé de primera mano los
channels then what is it that is not
canales entonces qué es lo que no
you understand
entiendes
what is your house
cuál es tu casa
tell me what he put in the
dime qué es lo que ha puesto en la
donations in reflection is very
donaciones en la reflexión es muy
simple and it is that it is fixed so much
sencilla y es que tiene se fija tanto
with Betis together with the 600 he wins the
con el betis junto con el 600 gana lo
you can see what you have
puedes ver que es que tienes
literally in all your videos is to go to
literalmente en todos tus vídeos es ir a
those that do
las que sí
clear
claro
what we
lo que nos
involve
involucre
It is what you have worried about and for what
es lo que tú te has preocupado y por lo
that you are burning because I don't come out
que tú estás ardiendo porque yo no salgo
the one you want me to put in the
la que tú quieres que me pongan en las
miniatures
miniaturas
Uncle, I'm not worried either.
tío que yo que yo estoy preocupado ni
burned or rather savica getting involved because
ardido o sea savica metiéndose porque
They come in insulting, inside insulting
entran insultando dentro insultando
I literally need your donations to
necesito literalmente tus donaciones a
enter enjoying
entrar disfrutando
more insult more times than I insult you
más insulto más veces que yo a ti
has literally started donating
es literalmente ha empezado donando
insulting has given a name
insultante ha puesto un nombre
enjoying
disfrutando
Well yes, the truth is that yes, the truth is
bueno sí la verdad que sí la verdad el
good name a little
nombre bueno un poco
because it is burned at the level of entering
porque está ardido a nivel de entrar a
a place where no one bothers counting
un sitio donde nadie se mete contando
because you are in a place where no one will
porque estás en un sitio donde nadie te
has done nothing enjoying
ha hecho nada disfrutando
Well, because it's very simple.
bueno pues porque es muy sencillo tú
you are commenting on something in which well
estás comentando algo en lo cual bueno
Well, a little bit of ulcers are produced
pues se produce un poquito de úlceras
So I go into a little bit about what
entonces yo entro pues un poquito en que
what is bracelet at level since it is what
lo que está pulsera a nivel ya que es lo
that affects you so that you spend it
que te afecta para que tú te gastes el
money enjoy
dinero disfrutar
it doesn't affect me much
no me afecta mucho
if I am not affected
si yo no estoy afectado
because no one insults you to enjoy that
porque nadie te insulta a disfrutar que
education has because you have plenty of it
educación tiene porque te sobra el
money but education no good that's it
dinero pero la educación no bueno eso es
a person who cleverly messes with
una persona que se mete con tino que
parents generate
generan los padres
enjoy with money
con el dinero disfrutar
It is not any lack of respect what I
no es ninguna falta de respeto lo que yo
I told you what you said
te he dicho a lo que has dicho tú
but out but kid if you dedicate yourself to
pero fuera pero chaval si te dedicas a
send a donation full of arrogance
enviar una donación llena de prepotencia
and negativity I don't know what kind of
y negatividad no sé qué tipo de
response to waiting to receive a hug no
respuesta a esperar recibir un abrazo no
Be a man, at least tell me what it is.
sé hombre a ver por lo menos dime qué es
what is bad state of the stream for
lo que está mal estado del stream para
that you start donating and enjoying
que te pongas a donar y disfrutando
So if nothing has happened to me, I'm nervous
así si nada me ha pasado estante nervios
I hate that you comment
odio que comentes
So you criticize in that way
o sea que critiques de esa manera el
humor such as jager or hate
humor de por ejemplo de jager o de odios
what you do you realize that
lo que tú hagas tú te das cuenta que
These people are dedicated to
estas personas se dedican a se dedican a
do the monger and he already knows
hacer el el monger y él ya que se
presents on this site with that ball in
presenta en este sitio con esa pelota en
the mouth and just and exactly for
la boca y justo y exactamente para
provoking reactions like yours doesn't bother you
provocar reacciones como la tuya no te
realize that then anyone
des cuenta de eso entonces cualquiera
delegate
delegado
what do you need you have you can't go to a
que necesita tienes tú no puedes ir a un
event like this dressed today or that is one no
evento así vestido hoy o que sea uno no
it makes humor funny with humor
hace gracia al humor de gracias de humor
44 years old
de 44 años
Maybe they really do that to him.
de verdad tal vez eso le hagan eso el
purpose the purpose of doing that is
propósito el propósito de hacer eso es
exactly what you what you criticized him
exactamente qué tú lo que tú lo critiqué
yes you go out then what is the
sí que tú sal entonces cuál es el
problem with seems very vast of yours
problema con parece muy vasto de tus
arts and then well then too
artes y luego bueno también entonces
what is the problem and start giving it to him
cuál es el problema y ponerse a darle la
the joint talk also gave is
charla de los porros también dio es
say let's see
decir vamos a ver
They are against what I have said about
están en contra de lo que he dicho del
gold
oro
that they are bad
de que son malos
dogs are bad
los perros son malos
but from there to us but from there to
pero de ahí a nosotros pero de ahí a
go on to say that you cannot give a
pasar a decir que no se puede dar un
program filter is already a joke
filtro del programa ya cn es de coña
You can't take joints as a
no se puede tomar los porros como un
humor is not because you say so
humor no es porque no porque tú lo digas
yes yes
sí sí
no no
no no
If you can have the opinion of three to
si tú puedes tener la opinión de tres a
two balls the thing is that it is a
dos la cosa es que es una
meeting what you are saying is that
reunión lo que tú estás diciendo es que
You can't make jokes with X and X
no se puede hacer bromas con equis y se
may
podrá
Normalizing the fight is worth that, really.
normalizar la lucha vale eso la verdad
no no no but what is humor has no
no no no pero que es el humor no tiene
that having limits uncle your corners the
que tener límites tío tus esquinas las
visuals then what happens with your
visuales entonces lo que pasa con su
Simplicity, said the colleague, I get along well
sencillez dijo el colega me llevo bien
with the
con él
I don't think it's a nonsense either, well yes
tampoco me parece una burrada bueno sí
They are quite stupid, that is correct, but
son bastante burros eso es correcto pero
What happens is that it has to be able to be done
qué pasa es que se tiene que poder hacer
and his death or it has to be able to be done
y su muerte o se tiene que poder hacer
whatever I do to you I hope that I do
lo que te haga lo con espero que yo
I can tell you that no, it doesn't seem to me that
puedo decirte que no no me parece que
be good then don't say no
sea bueno entonces no digas que no se
can do that and what do you think more
puede hacer eso y qué te parece más
simply because here what is not known
simplemente porque aquí lo que no se
maybe something you do is humorous
puede que una cosa que tú haga un humor
but I'm going to donate to you by insulting a
pero te voy a donar insultando a un
streamer who is unbearable to me and who
streamer que me es insoportable y que me
annoying and when I blocked myself to get to
molesta y cuando me bloqueé ponerme a
insult him but I'm not angry
insultarle pero no estoy ardido
It's one thing for you to make humor and another
una cosa es que tú hagas humor y otra
The thing is that you normally acted as if
cosa es que tú lo normal hice como si
It was a normal thing in life and cool
fuera una cosa normal en la vida y guay
and Samael Tudor paid one euro to say that.
y samael tudor a un euro para decir eso
the channel follower who is commenting
el seguidor del canal que está opinando
and you can donate to comment on
y puede donar para opinar en
no moment is a given
ningún momento es un puesto por supuesto
the lack of respect to say something ruse
la falta de respeto decir algo de ardid
or if it is far behind we will focus on
o si está muy atrás vamos a centrar en
the issue of whether you are capable is one thing
el tema a ver si eres capaz es una cosa
is to make humor you can make humor
es hacer humor tú puedes hacer un humor
Okay, it's a joke about a porn about
vale es un chiste sobre un porno sobre
a drink whatever you want but one thing
una bebida lo que quiera pero una cosa
It's humor and another thing is normalizing it
es el humor y otra cosa es normalizar lo
as if smoking was for cool people
como si fumar por lo fuera de gente guay
There is a difference, but at what point
tiene la diferencia pero en qué momento
the people
la gente
literal but it is normalized with the type of
literal pero se normaliza con el tipo de
comments they make and get a girl out of you
comentarios que hacen y sacarte un chic
and take out the plastic of what it is called
y sacarte el plástico de según se llama
of the snitches the chayote expert
de los chivatos el práctico de chayote
where you go where you go from goat to play a
dónde vas a dónde va de chivo a tocar un
filter has balls software to take out the
filtro tiene software a sacar la
bag the year carries tone here it is called
bolsa el año lleva tono aquí se llama
snitch the bag is plastic
chivato la bolsa está de plástico
transparent with the nozzle and the
transparente con la boquilla y las
little things, not just Mr. Filters, I mean
cositas no sólo el señor filtros digo
Okay, and you haven't seen that.
vale y eso tú no lo ha visto que sea
as if they don't mention it on the internet
como si no mencionan en el internet
treated for having a topic to revive
tratado por tener tema de por revivir
things
cosas
of the world having to smoke a joint to
del mundo tener que fumar un porro para
sleep but who says it's normal
dormir pero quien dice que es lo normal
the distraction of that when you deal with it
la distracción de eso cuando tú lo trata
normally is normalizing what
con normalidad está normalizando lo
Javi's because he doesn't show his face in the
de javi porque no muestra la cara en las
miniatures
miniaturas
but the joke
pero el chiste
is
es
no smoking in your bed and now from 14 to
no fumar en tu cama y ahora de 14 para
support large avite seen since 2016 and
apoyar grandes avite visto desde 2016 y
I liked how you've improved and
me ha gustado cómo has mejorado y
learned to have ways to deal
aprendido a tener maneras para tratar
The topics continue like this, thanks friend Samuel
los temas sigue así gracias amigo samuel
What's your problem with the path I like?
cuál es su problema con camino me gusta
that drugs be normalized
que se normalicen la droga
and you have said that it cannot be done
y es que tú has dicho que no se puede
do that kind of thing and it's very easy
hacer de ese tipo y es que es muy fácil
the difference
la diferencia
that you can't make humor you're going to
que no se puede hacer humor tú te vas a
a program like chronicle you know what
un programa como crónica sabes lo que
It was to write that to Marchena for example
era escribir que a marchena por ejemplo
No
no
they don't know what it is
no saben lo que es
evening program at one o'clock
programa de por la noche a la una de la
tomorrow
mañana
and it does it best but a program of
y lo hace a lo mejor pero un programa de
internet with the audience they have
internet con la audiencia que tienen
Well, it doesn't seem right to me, and besides, it's not what
pues no me parece no y aparte no lo que
do they let us treat him like
hacen ellos nos dejaste tratarlo como
which is something cool like everyone else's
que es algo de guays como de los de todo
It's not a you don't think they do that
no es un tú no crees que hacen eso
That is to say, it is a comedy show, it is like
es decir es un programa de humor es como
visuals that lead him to trial for
visuales que le llevan a juicio por
make a joke about
hacer un chiste de
a joke
un chiste
They do what they do from my point of view
ellos lo que hacen desde mi punto de
view
vista
taking out I think
sacando creo
his power
su poder
the hater has not given any arguments
el hater no ha dado ningún argumento
solid to support your comments
sólido para sustentar sus comentarios
poisoned we are not yet golden age
envenenados no somos aún edad de oro
to be liked by everyone, Javi is fine.
para caerle bien a todos bien javi vale
Sevilla against Sevilla
sevilla ante sevilla
It would seem to be worth the punch
sería parece haber vale lo del puñetazo
We were talking about the punch in the
estábamos con lo del puñetazo en la
aggression let's call it not one
agresión vamos a llamarlo que no una
full-face aggression
agresión por toda la cara
friend plays a trick on you on the shoulder
amigo te gasta una broma en el hombro un
friend totally defenseless with the body
amigo totalmente indefenso con el cuerpo
that has ovens and the body stops
que tiene hornos y el cuerpo detiene
turn and the way of speaking and of
turno y la forma de hablar y de
addressing people with organs and
dirigirse a las personas de órganos y
This man the other presenter because
este hombre el otro presentador porque
Let us remember that he is the presenter of a
recordemos que es el presentador de un
one of the most watched programs not to feel
programa de los más vistos no sentirnos
makes him react automatically
le mete reaccione automáticamente
disconnect because in addition to seeing the face
desconecta porque además de ver la cara
how it disconnects from reality and its
como desconecta con la realidad y su
automatic reaction is to start from a
reacción automática es partir de una
pallette
paleta
Does that seem normal to you?
a ti te parece eso normal
It is obviously not correct to say that
evidentemente no es correcto es decir lo
which is completely disproportionate
que es es desproporcionado completamente
not in any sense but from there but from
no de ningún sentido pero de ahí pero de
There, but let's see, do you think Dario
ahí pero vamos a ver tú crees que darío
he made him bet, that is to say, you believe
lo hizo apostar es decir tú crees
[Laughs]
[Risas]
no no but I mean do you think that in
no no pero me refiero tú crees que en
that moment the media correctly
ese momento el media correctamente lo
that was doing because a person
que estaba haciendo porque una persona
that has internalized study is
que tiene interiorizado estudio está
accustomed to that kind of attitude no
acostumbrado a ese tipo de actitudes no
It was for whatever Perez gave because it is
era para lo que pérez sea dio porque es
fanboy of the five the mind
fan boy de los cinco la mente
is
es
I haven't seen everything
todo no lo he visto
and in the end I don't consume, that is to say, I
y al final no consumos es decir yo
tweets between little and nothing when I eat
tweets entre poco y nada cuando como
YouTube only sees us
youtube sólo nos ve a nosotros para
enjoy it yes good to insult of no
disfrutarlo sí bueno para insultar de no
to be able to have an opinion to reflect on
poder tener opinión para reflexionar
to put Javier is [ __ ] and everything
para poner javier es y todo
I fix everything you put in the
arreglo todo lo que ha puesto en las
prayers to give an opinion are in vain
oraciones para opinar es vana
that's how it is
así es
to give an opinion is an opinion
opinar es una opinión
but is aware that
pero es consciente que
people three seconds is to say I you
la gente tres segundos es decir yo te
called
llamo
in calls of
en llamadas de
opinion
opinión
and be careful with ordinary people, well to say
y ojo por gente corriente bueno decir
This person is an [ __ ] and it's an opinion
esta persona y es una opinión
It's my opinion, [ __ ], you have a lot
es mi opinión tú tienes mucho
money for what he says but education
dinero por lo que dice pero educación
not much if you say so, but I
poca no si lo dices tú que me
they have called
han llamado
for looking for the goal is why he wrote
por buscar el gol es porque él escribió
to show the invalid face of many of yours
para dar la cara inválida muchos de tus
arguments is the same as throwing a stone
argumentos es igual a lanzar una piedra
and hide your hand
y esconder la mano
friend
amigo
It is normal then that someone breaks it
es normal entonces que alguien le rompa
the mouth to another for one because it touches him
la boca a otro por una porque le toque
the shoulder
el hombro
in this type of attitudes that you have are
en este tipo de actitudes que tiene son
from the square are not from the square
de plazoleta no son de plazoleta
but it seems to me that he is [ __ ]
pero me parece que es subnormal de
fourth to punch someone for
cuarta meterle un puñetazo a alguien por
that
eso
it's a problem with joints
es un problema con los porros
Vox
vox
speaking two
hablando dos
days
días
Okay, so they have attitudes of
vale entonces tienen actitudes de
small square
plazoleta
but that is not normal
pero eso no es normal
[Music]
[Música]
then we're going to stay, I don't have a
entonces vamos a quedar yo no tengo un
A hard punch to the readers that is the
puñetazo a los lectores duro que es la
Dario's reaction is a reaction of a
reacción de darío es una reacción de una
person who has internalized it and who
persona que lo tiene interiorizado y que
that's normal
eso es normal
That is, you are drawing conclusions from
o sea tú estás sacando conclusiones de
those men for whom that is normal
esos hombres que eso para él es normal
starting from someone
partiendo de alguien
I hope not
espero que no
sea
sea
so but don't be scared as soon as
así pero es que no te asuste en cuanto
you insult well then you you you don't
tú insultas bueno entonces tú tú tú no
you see that reaction from the
ves que esa reacción de partir de los
tooth to the other is a reaction of a
diente al otro es una reacción de una
person who has fought a lot
persona que se ha peleado mucho que ha
stuck a lot or that has it
pegado mucho o que lo tiene
internalized this custom of moving
interiorizado esta costumbre de movida
because I think you're already there
porque yo creo que eso ya estás ahí
you theorizing and assuming a little bit or
teorizando tú y asumiendo un poquito o
it is to suffer almost a punctual bird
sea sufrir casi un ave puntual
of having been perfectly once
de haber sido perfectamente una vez
punctual that it has been heated
puntual que se le que se haya calentado
that he left her indirectly wrong and that
que la haya dejó mal indirecto y que
others
otros
In short, the key is live
en fin que la llave en directo
If you ridicule her for a while
si la ridícula la ridiculiza durante una
audience
audiencia
So, for touching his shoulder
o sea que por tocarle el hombro
on the shoulder
en el hombro
but what
pero que
justified
justificada
I was literally justifying it
literalmente lo estaba justificando
I'm not justifying you, that's unfair.
no te estoy justificando eso es injusto
be also part of what is a savagery and
ser también parte que es una salvajada y
that you have to put a little into someone
que hay que meterle un poco a alguien
that's why it's an ace, it's a savagery and
por eso es un as es una salvajada y
when it is directed by those [ __ ] people
cuando lo dirige esas personas la
good is distracted the clamp
buena esté distraído la pinza
completely and it doesn't make sense but
completamente y no tiene sentido pero
saying that assuming there is being
diciendo que lo de ai asumir es estar
direct family look at me follow is this
directo familia mirarme seguir es este
right Diego Gracia
derecho diego gracia
Well listen to me then explain it to me
bueno escúchame entonces explícame tú
how long we have been here and I don't know how much
qué tiempo estamos aquí y no sé cuánto
We've been here for a while but in the end your complaint
tiempo llevamos pero al final tu queja
did not contend in your complaint first was that
no contendió en tu queja primero era que
I didn't make my own content, I told you.
yo no hacía contenido propio te he dicho
that no sting to that own content
que ninguna sting a ese contenido propio
That is, all YouTubers are based on
o sea todos los youtubers se basan en
other people's things
cosas de otros
wait a moment okay is that I want your
espera momento vale es que quiero tu
response to the fact that it seems that no one
respuesta a que parece que ningún
streamer towards own content said
streamer hacia contenidos propios dicho
No one invents oneself
el propio propio nadie se inventa
some and the one who talks about his [ __ ] life
algunos y el que habla de su vida
brother
hermano
do it with your life brother no but not anymore
hacerlo de su vida hermano no pero ya no
These are all the sayings that are confirmed to know more
son todos los decires conformó saber más
beyond everything but the majority
allá de todo pero la mayoría
but
pero
They are more loyal than the fans and this
son más fieles que los fans y este
kid is the clear example face
chaval es el claro ejemplo cara
they revolted from the opportunity that
revolvieron de la oportunidad de que
put even if it's tape on your face and you'll see
suba aunque sea cinta a la cara que verá
You don't have a problem, but explain it to us.
tú no tengo problema pero explícanos
is to explain to us what your problem is, my friend
es explicarnos cuál es tu problema amigo
that we still haven't understood why
que todavía no hemos entendido porque
you enter a string enjoying what it is
entras en un string disfrutando qué es
what offended you so much
lo que te ofendió tanto
Yes, what I understand is to get involved
si lo que tengo entendido que es meterme
in tweets see what the hell I hired you for and
en tweets ver qué te contraté y
This has put this in me, you are commenting on it
me ha metido esto estás comentando la
[ __ ] until I saw her I said you're going to
hasta que no la vi dije tú voy a
see it and suddenly I saw that
verlo y de repente pues eso lo he visto
That first thing you mentioned about the
que primero que has comentado lo de los
joints man you said you can't
porros tío que has dicho que no se puede
That is to say, you say to me that it cannot be done
o sea tú frases yo que no se puede hacer
humor of X and that's enough for me
humor de equis y eso a mí ya de vale
error can be made in a room model
error se puede hacer un modelo de sala
of the balls something else that is good or
de las pelotas otra cosa que esté bien o
bad or that seems better or worse to you
mal o que te parezca mejor o peor al
world or the sea theme and you can't and
mundo o el tema de mar y tú no puedes y
you can't send a super cha
tú no puedes mandar un súper cha
saying can be the humor of what
diciendo se puede ser el humor de lo que
It is something else that is bad
sea otra cosa es que sea malo
normalize this, that's not what it's called
normalizarlo esto eso no se llama
education
educación
I'll explain this to you
esto te lo explico
That is to say, I make the donation to you
es decir yo la donación te la hago
You say go up, go up a down
tú dices que suba que suba un down
after that if you do not agree
después de eso si tú no estás de acuerdo
with some opinion of the string can
con alguna opinión del string puede
to give my opinion, that's why I have the chat open and
opinar para eso tengo el chat abierto y
He didn't censor it, people censored it for lack
no lo censuró censuró la gente de falta
of respect then if you are not of
de respeto entonces si tú no estás de
I agree with that opinion you could not put
acuerdo con esa opinión no podías poner
a super cha because you can make humor
un super cha pues se puede hacer humor
Whatever it is, don't pay attention to Javi.
de lo que sea no javi no hagas caso de
This fool in my opinion is an opinion
este tonto en mi opinión es una opinión
He doesn't watch much of that content but he knows
no ve mucho de esos contenidos pero sabe
since moves are seeing those
desde movidas está viendo esos
contents or go to the pse or to find out
contenidos o ves al pse o para enterarse
David
david
[Music]
[Música]
Why don't you come in with a super chat?
porque no entras con un super chat
saying hey look, well it can be done
diciendo oye mira pues se puede hacer
humor of whatever else is that
humor de lo que sea otra cosa es que
It is wrong to normalize what the kids
esté mal normalizar lo que los chavales
misunderstand is because you have to
entiendan mal es porque tienes que
do it enjoying the barbecue
hacerlo disfrutando del asado
so if so you are right if the
así que si es así tiene razón si la
the shape is not correct, don't tell me
forma no son las correctas no te lo
I recognize but completely that is to say me
reconozco pero completamente es decir yo
I understand that this is no longer correct.
entiendo que eso ya no es lo correcto
Okay, but from there to that I do give that
vale pero de ahí a que yo sí doy esa
such a simple opinion, so cordial, so
opinión tan sencilla tan cordial tan
courteous obviously because we did not get to
cortés evidentemente pues no llegamos a
This point I'm explaining to you
este punto en el que te estoy explicando
everything is explaining to you that here you can
todo te está explicando que aquí puedes
whoever can go up and give their opinion on anything
subir quien sea a opinar lo que sea no
no no no because there is a letter to a
no no no porque hay una letra a una
person and today I can here you can go up
persona y hoy yo puedo aquí puedes subir
when you want to give your opinion or discuss
cuando quiera opinar o a discutir
you asked here you can go up to
preguntó ustedes aquí se puede subir a
give our opinion and debate or we can give it to you
opinar y debatir o le podemos elsur a
Someone or I got scared of someone or someone
alguien o yo me achantó de alguien o le
joined someone asked that is my
unió a alguien preguntó que ese es mi
point what point is that you can't enter
punto que punto es que no puede entrar
Here is a person I don't want
aquí una persona que no quiero de
battle of arguments that insult you
batalla de argumentos que te insulte
like a monkey is what cannot enter
como un mono es lo que no puede entrar
anyone in the sense before by power
cualquiera en sentido ante por poder
anyone can enter the bridge
puente puede entrar cualquiera
but that's the point if then the topic of
pero eso el punto si luego el tema de
that the one who criticizes me is also
eso de que me también el que critique es
the humor of whether I am serious
el humor de si soy grave
the humor of that is the subject that
el humor de o sea el tema que de que
tell people what you see from afar
digas a la gente lo que se ve de lejos
that you don't like Oslo
que oslo no te cae bien
favorite
favorito
that doesn't seem normal to me
que no me parece normal
because if not you can't count like that
porque si no no se puede contar así el
legacy
legado
How he did it doesn't seem normal to me.
como lo ha hecho no me parezca normal es
another thing because
otra cosa porque
your complaint is the same, uncle, because it comes in
tu queja iguale tío porque entra
enjoying and what is your problem with
disfrutando y cuál es tu problema con
this channel and what you have seen in
este canal y con lo que hayas visto en
the cinema that I have to train uncle that
el cine que tengo que entrenar tío que
train the 34 plus
entrenar a los 34 más
for the tournament
para el torneo
that
que
the thing about humor that can become morbid
lo del humor que se puede hacer morbo
the balls is that it is a little that if that
los es que es un poco eso si esa
person from Oslo also the one that he
persona de oslo también el que el que él
It is raised and with those clothes for what
se plantea y con esa ropa para para que
There are people who say this is an idiot
haya gente que diga este es
what the hell does such access do?
qué hace tal es el acceso para
that you do this you understand is
que tú hagas esto entiendes es
exactly for what the guy
exactamente para que por lo que el tío
he puts himself on and can act later too
se pone y puede actuando luego también
criticizing him is bad, he is going to a
criticar a él reviste mal se va a una
pajama gala so that the practice what
gala en pijama para que la práctica qué
he provokes you understand he provokes he likes
él provoca entiendes el provoca le gusta
provoke now does it so that people
provocar ahora lo hace para que la gente
tell him that that tap already hits and doesn't stop
le diga que ese grifo ya hits no para
balance that I have because if I don't do it
equilibrio que he pues si no lo hace
because it is pushing the limits that is
porque es el empujar los límites es
say I'm standing here like a jerk
decir me planto aquí como
for people to say
para que la gente diga
is this there as a reaction in this
está esto allí como de reacción en este
its normal what he does going to a gala no
su normal que hace yéndose a una gala no
it could be a gala
podría ser una gala
I don't know what
no sé qué
It's for all the balls and for that
es para todos los y para que
then you're there saying that you don't know
luego tú estés ahí diciendo que no se
can do that and then also in the
puede hacer eso y luego también en el
Jager's humor catalog as a child
catálogo al humor de jager de niño
Four years literally makes you a lot
cuatro años literal a ti te hace mucha
funny
gracia
me
a mí
I don't listen explaining that I understand
no escucho explicando que yo entiendo
that is very very hard
que es muy muy duro
if you don't do
si no haces
the right thing but it is not then either
lo correcto pero tampoco es entonces
What is your problem with what I said?
cuál es tu problema con lo que he dicho
and why do you tell me you are 40 years old and
y por qué me dices tienes 40 años y
I am 36 and if I were 40 what would be the
tengo 36 y si tuviera 40 cuál sería el
problem
problema
236 you are there nearby
236 estás allí cerca
four and a half years left
faltan cuatro años y medio
but what is your complaint, food?
pero cuál es tu queja comida
It is very old like this year because yes
es muy viejo cual este año porque si
He brings his charisma to it
le pone de lo suyo su carisma la
search for information to find
búsqueda de información para encontrar
truthfulness is the closest thing to a
veracidad es lo más cercano a un
Popular journalism is worth grace Patricio
periodismo popular vale gracia patricio
Friend, tell me what is your problem with the
amigo dime cuál es tu problema con la
age is 40 years old, do you think he is a person?
edad sea 40 años te parece una persona
very old or like
muy vieja o como
and I like it a lot because Tucumn is
y me gusta mucho porque tucumán a
To debate is to try to poke the other
debatir es intentar pinchar a la otra
person
persona
questions based on what in my own way
preguntas en base a lo que a mi manera
your way of thinking is to go to the
de tu manera de opinar es ir a los
street where no one is enjoying you and
street donde nadie te está disfrutando y
get to places insulting then
llegar a los sitios insultando entonces
I'm asking you what it is
yo te estoy preguntando cuál es el
problem in case I have to run and it gives me
problema por si tengo que correr y me da
or something I have I am 36 years old who is 40
o algo tengo tengo 36 años que tiene 40
years and I don't know what
años y no sé qué
happens
pasa
of the life of the meeting, that is to say, it is not
de la vida de la reunión es decir no es
My life is 40 years, it is no longer possible
mi vida son 40 años ya no se puede
report on Dallas life
informar sobre la vida de dallas
It's a little sad in my opinion because
es un poco triste es mi opinión porque
if you are there and sat in your chair
si estás ahí y sentó en su silla
looking for the past
buscando que la pasada
You do it to me again, you take it out on me again
me vuelve a hacer me vuelves a sacar el
The subject of that letter is the subject of money
tema de esa carta el tema el dinero del
money that is going to tell you that I have to
dinero que va a decirte que me tenga que
being sad not completely with everything
haber triste no totalmente con todo
I respect everyone and I respect the best
respeto a todo el mundo y yo a lo mejor
someday I have to do it again no
algún día tengo que volver a hacerlo no
but who leads a better life and more
pero quién lleva mejor vida y más
quality of life of a person who is
calidad de vida una persona que se
gets up at 4 in the morning and has
levanta a las 4 a la mañana y se tiene
that the afternoon could not be endured or a
que partir la tarde no se aguantó o una
person who earns 10 times more
persona que gana 10 10 veces más
reporting the sun was removed from age
informando del sol se quitó de edad a la
of Wii Micro that is
de wii micro que sea
but if the sad thing would be to ask us
pero si la triste sería de pedirnos
all the
todo el
money
dinero
everyone needs money
todo todo el mundo necesitamos dinero
because we have to live then prince
porque tenemos que vivir entonces prince
explode at work no but because it goes
explote en el trabajo no pero porque va
to be sad to have an easy job
a ser triste tener un trabajo fácil
number because something mental or I'm you
número porque algo mental o te lo estoy
saying because I can't handle 40 years
diciendo porque yo no puedo con 40 años
sitting as an artist since you can or not
sentado como artista ya que puedes o no
You can think of it as false and leave me alone.
puede opinar de falso y deja usted me
let him finish that I am not saying
dejó terminar que yo no estoy diciendo
that I invent for my life ours
que yo se invente para mi vida nuestro
and tell me why 40 from what point onwards
y dime por qué 40 a partir hasta qué
age is allowed to talk about the salsa singer
edad está permitido hablar del salsero
until you get the hell out of time
hasta que te salga de los tiempo
as a site 60 years you are in the range of
como sitio 60 años estás en la gama de
the voice and goddess a new law has been
la voz y diosa una nueva ley ha sido
chosen for nothing life is worth but
elegido de para nada la vida vale pero
that destined them is that
que los destinó es que
It just may be although it seems to me
simplemente puede ser aunque me parece
a little sad
un poco triste
looking at Dallas, what does Dallas think?
mirando si a dallas que opina dallas
on the para miles island as a sheep
sobre los para miles island como borrero
Sad the elite has no job and no
triste la élite no tiene trabajo y no
You can feed your family but
puedes le da de comer a tu familia pero
because you get caught up in informing the kids
porque te coge informarle a los chavales
of the Tsar followed and
del zar seguido y
and make money from what you have to do
y ganar dinero de eso que tiene que
continue investigating assets without you
seguir investigando activos a ti sin ti
Don't get tired of being so aware of what
no te canse estar tan pendiente de qué
what happens to those who have what happens to them
le pasaba a las que le pasa lo que pasa
I don't know who it is, how this has been the day
no sé quién es como este ha sido el día
what tired me the most was loading trucks
que más me cansaba carga camiones
Well, honestly, I did have another one.
bueno yo sinceramente si tuvo otra
option is that the truck is true
opción es que el camión es cierto la
reason is to say I
razón es decir yo
I'll explain it to you from my point of view
te lo explico punto de vista
I don't have my option is not to say yes
yo no tengo mi opción no es decir yo sí
I am being possible my option is that to
estoy siendo posible mi opción es que a
trucks my option is to end up in
camiones a mi opción igual es acabar en
a higher position in that I mean me
un puesto más alto en tanto es decir yo
In my opinion, being sad at 40
para mi opinión estar triste con 40
tacos looking dallas has debated with
tacos mirando dallas ha debatido con
energy and it will be a little such
energía y será un poco tal
but that is the definition of sad or is it
pero esa es la definición de triste o es
one thing your streamer has normalized
una cosa que ha normalizado tu streamer
but he has met you in my opinion yes
pero te ha conocido en mi opinión si
be sad who feels sadness that is
haber triste que siente tristeza que es
of a melancholic and pessimistic character or
de carácter melancólico y pesimista o
I am not prone to feeling sadness
propensa a sentir tristeza yo no soy
pessimistic nor melancholic nor anything
pesimista ni melancólico ni nada
Yeah
sí
but not having money
pero no tener dinero
But Javi, how old do you want to be?
pero javi tú hasta qué edad quiere estar
his past life the seven times with
su vida pasada las siete veces con
Santander dies and lasts a hundred years.
santander muere yo dura cien años por lo
less
menos
in 10 years going up Dallas
dentro de 10 años subiendo dallas
received 35 million in bitcoin
recibió 35 millones en bitcoin
I was going to go in 10 years when I was 40.
ibai dentro de 10 años cuando tenga 40
surely chef reacting to the video
seguramente chef reaccionando al vídeo
Commenting on a video game, this would seem to you
comentando videojuego esto te parecería
sad or would you be fine
triste o te parecería bien
I'm not 40, that's the end of it.
no tengo 40 es dicho fin
and for example will be playing
y por ejemplo estará jugando a
video games obviously clear what
videojuegos evidentemente claro lo que
you do
haces
You would think the tiger is playing sad
te parecería triste tigre juega
video games that are 40 or 50 years old
videojuegos con 40 o 50 años
The goal is to be playing 10 points 50
objetivo es estar jugando 10 puntos 50
years than some examples there are more things in
años que unos ejemplos hay más cosas en
life is about
la vida se trata de
a job and contribute to maintaining your home
un trabajo y cotizar mantener tu casa
support your family then
mantener tu familia entonces
50 years don't talk to people don't you
50 años no hables a la gente no te
listen is very rude
escuchan es muy maleducado
really clear I understand that there is no
realmente claro entiendo que no haya
put the face because apart from that he has
puesto la cara porque aparte de que ha
made a complete fool of yourself that you don't know
hecho un completo ridículo que no sabes
argue nothing that has finally given
argumentar nada que finalmente ha dado
the reason is everyone's no no no they have
la razón es de todos no no tienen
education no active you enter the
educación ningún activa entras en los
insulting sites
sitios insultando
no damage
nada de daño
after the [ __ ] before after
después los antes de tras
direct we are going to bring tail called the
directo vamos a traer cola llamado el
this [ __ ] after he
este después de que se
will delay I don't know how many things
retrasara no sé cuántas cosas
justified
justificó
I'm calling you an [ __ ] again
te lo vuelvo a llamar
in response to your insults
en respuesta a tus insultos
conspiratorial
conspirativas
will have much faith in your father
tendrá de su fe a tu padre tendrá mucho
money or whatever is rude
dinero o lo que sea mal educado
writing allows and you don't show your face
escribiendo permite y que no des la cara
and of course this is what happens when
y que claro esto es lo que pasa cuando
people hide behind anonymity
la gente se esconde tras el anonimato
showing my face because I don't feel like it
dando la cara porque no me sale de los
balls and because more than one knows me
y porque más de uno me conoce
because more than one knows you
porque más de uno te conoce
and you are ashamed of being recognized like this
y te da vergüenza que te reconozcan así
It's ridiculous and being rude
es el ridículo y siendo maleducado
the desire of an uncle who is 50 years older
el deseo un tío que con 50 años más está
talking about the salsa of the law is
hablando del salsero de la ley está
just gave a review of the ops already in
acaba de pegar un repaso de la ops ya en
everything but what happened
todo pero qué pasó
in knowing how to be in they get the argument a
en saber estar en sacan el argumento un
a lot like an education
montón como que una educación
I have it like in education if you read and you
tengo como que en educación si lees y tu
first answer has been that it has more
primera respuesta ha sido que tiene más
from one of my parents uncles and that is a
de uno de mis padres tíos y eso es una
letter of education other education of two
carta de educación otra educación de dos
balls champion so you came into me
pelotas campeón o sea que tú entré a mi
directly where no one is doing it to you
directo donde nadie te está haciendo
nothing and I entered my live calling myself
nada y entré en mi directo llamándome
delayed I don't know how many consulars of
no sé cuántas consulares de
arriving is a lack of respect
llegar es una falta de respeto correcto
but you answer me with that
pero que tú me respondas con esa
category that lowers you to myself
categoría que a ti te baja a mi mismo
level
nivel
If you are teaching me in any way
si tú me estás enseñando a mí de alguna
way I'm failing at it
manera que yo estoy fracasando en la
life because I have been commenting for 40 years
vida porque tengo 40 años comentando
Don't talk to me when talking about 40 years
no me hables al hablar de los 40 años
and I repeat it to you if they brought you
y te lo vuelvo a repetir si te trajeron
direct and enjoying a person and
directo y disfrutando una persona y
saying a little more than a failure
diciendo un poco más que un fracaso su
life because he is 40 years old, so it is normal
vida porque tiene 40 años pues es normal
Let me answer you if you win again, man.
que te responda si ganas otra vez tío
normal it will not have been at school
normal no habrá sido en el colegio de la
university
universidad
private
privada
the university will be based on money
la universidad será en base a dinero
because nothing else fits me, you are a
porque otra cosa no me cuadra eres un
rude and you don't know how to behave in the
maleducado y no sabes estar en los
sites
sitios
what do you say where are you going
qué dices dónde vas
of text the two levels quiet
de texto los dos niveles tranquilo
listen
escucha
and then it is normal that you recent
y luego que es normal que tú reciente
so you don't or that is to say that you can't
así que tú no o sea que tú no puede
react if you understand being a
reaccionar si entiendes siendo un
streaming content creator
creador de contenidos en streaming
of what can be done one can
de lo que se puede hacer uno puede
wish I can relate because if it is
desear yo puedo relacionar pues si es
that I think I'm relating
que me parece que estoy relacionando
better than you deserve but that you
mejor de lo que te mereces pero que tú
What you can't do is tell
lo que no puedes hacer es decirle a
someone you are very good at because you win
alguien que eres muy bueno porque ganas
more money than their parents
más dinero que sus padres
Of course it's not going to be about making a living
claro que no va a ser ganarme la vida
doing what I like and
haciendo lo que me gusta y
wonderfully
estupendamente
Uruguay what I told you that a
uruguay lo que te he dicho que un
failure
fracaso
the things that
las cosas que
you are youtube
eres es youtube
trying the pressure that has a
intentando la presión que tiene un
comment like mine simply
comentario como el mío simplemente
try not to answer and if not what do I have?
intenta no responder y si no que tengo
more worthy than your parents and
más digno que tus padres y
I see fit to respond
yo vea conveniente responder
and
y
stability point [ __ ] is acted thanks
estabilidad punto se actúe gracias
Steve Normal
steve normal
the queries are wrong and it is always that
las consultas mal y está siempre es que
I repeat to you that I am a fun person that I
te repito que yo soy un divertido que yo
I am not a creator of how you are
no soy un creador de cómo tú eres
Anonymous, you can go to the missing sites
anónimo puedes ir a los sitios faltantes
packed and enjoying the people
repleto y disfrutando a la gente
that
que
admits
admite
someone you don't even know because you don't even know
alguien a quien ni conoces xq ni sabes
that you start criticizing
que te pongas a criticar
words more than Javi's age he has
palabras mas da la edad de javi el tiene
the fortune of doing a job that
la fortuna de hacer un trabajo que le
makes you happy
hace feliz
something that not many achieve was seen to be
cosa que no muchas logran se vio que fue
then very sad because you are
después muy triste dio porque estás
seeing you are in a place you don't like
viendo estás en un sitio que no te gusta
and you start insulting people because
y te pones a insultar a la gente porque
you don't like the shape they don't have the same
no te gusta la forma no tienen la misma
opinion or because they have messed with your
opinión o porque se han metido con tus
favorite youtuber
youtuber favorito
that I'm not from YouTube
que yo no de youtube
I mean
o sea
but what is really
pero lo que de verdad
which is necessary if we consult
que es necesario si consultamos
commenting the satire is a fart
comentando queda la sátira un pedo
comment on it no there is no problem
coméntalo no no hay ningún problema
easy I voted for him what he said is a
fácil yo lo voté que haya dicho es un
It's a bit sad that it remains that way.
poco penoso el que eso quede esa
answer is my opinion uncle it seems to me a
respuesta es mi opinión tío me parece un
a little sad that a person
poco triste que a una persona te
criticize something a person a view on it
critique algo una persona un view en lo
that it is and your answer was true
que sea y tu respuesta era verdad lo
do
haga
your son nothing you were youtube was to say
tu hijo nada tú eras youtube era decir
I was your son yes correct it was YouTube
yo era tu hijo sí correcto era youtube
YouTube my past told me in my step
youtube mi pasado dijo a mí en mi paso
young
joven
not long ago, right, and then you go too far
no hace mucho verdad y luego te pasas
transformed and if God you are great
transformada y si dios eres un grande
got it uncle
conseguido tío
Congratulations, you liked the poor boy.
enhorabuena te ha gustado el pobre chico
He doesn't realize that he is your
no se da cuenta de que él es tu
content x to attract two served for
contenido x de atraer dos servidos para
that they donate to you and the mountains
que te donen y los montes
to delete and to the channel yes
a borrar y al canal si
the people from what was your ticket channel
la gente de lo que era tu canal ticket
of criticism
de críticas
based on what
basado en qué
you will know what
se os va a saber qué
you indicate to those in which I contributed
indicas a las que en las que yo aportaba
my own to look at the
mi propio a mirar al
channel is basically about doing
canal se trata básicamente hacer
content reviews that I saw
críticas de contenido que yo veía yo
and my own twist
y mi propio giro
I was on the floor with the video that didn't
estaba en el suelo con el vídeo que no
It was based on letting them run
se basaba en dejarse a los correr
towards him he said who is this guy
hacia él dijo quién es este tío
Gervasio
gervasio
[Laughs]
[Risas]
you've had the balls or the goat of
tú has tenido los huevos o chivo de
coming here should come here well
venir aquí debiera de venir aquí de bien
you are left to play the moralist
queda a darte las de moralista
when you have tried to succeed in the
cuando tú has intentado triunfar en el
world of sanse or
mundo del sanse o
clown but with all the letters
payaso pero con todas las letras
but the very tall cowardly [ __ ] shot
pero los altísimos cobarde tiro
Let's see what happened to your channel, tell us about it.
a ver qué pasó con tu canal cuéntanos el
empty
vacío
[Music]
[Música]
your channel was more of an enemy to see in
tu canal era más propio enemigo a ver en
that your channel cannot be recovered
que no se puede recuperar el canal tuyo
not having, I don't know if with turbo that the
no haber no sé si a con turbo que los
will take a little bit of your channel
sacará un poco de tu canal
[Music]
[Música]
your character when it was your own you died
tu carácter cuando fue propio te moriste
of Jesus Christ by salsa singer Javi Ya Ya
de jesucristo del salsero javi ya ya
but this situation
pero esta situación
it's not for anything or that is
no es para nada o sea
for
para
his friends
sus amigos
He went with his friends writing with his
iba con sus amigos escribiendo con su
verified channel so that some
canal verificado para que para que algún
One day I was truly reminded of what is happening here.
día me volvió de verdad lo que pasa aquí
In these live shows they are the best, that is to say
en estos directos son los mejores o sea
you who want this
tú que tú quieres este
don't be your judge and I came to talk to you
no sea tu juez y me vine a mí a hablar
of your own content when you arrived
del contenido propio cuando tú llegaste
to 100,000 subscribers
a los 100.000 suscriptores
making salsa and when you try to make
haciendo salsero y cuando intentas hacer
Fornari's content but yours died
contenido de fornari pero se te murió el
geo channel
canal geo
Hamburg but that Sanse has used
hamburgo pero que el sanse ha utilizado
and that having made no salt opposes
y que haber hecho ningún sal se oponga
I became known by commenting on videos
yo me hice conocido comentando vídeos
funny that is to the ceo to see what videos
graciosos que es al ceo a ver qué vídeos
funny you commented
graciosos comentaba tú
You became acquainted with Elsa Liceo and
tú te hiciste conocido con elsa liceo y
both me and the nautical
tanto yo como el náutico
we found some
encontramos algo de
something of yours
algo tuyo
cowardly and hypocritical youtuber
youtuber cobarde e hipócrita que
you
tú
the criticisms in order you for example do not
las críticas en orden tu por ejemplo no
I tell you, it's not your own content, no, yes
te digo contenido propio no es eso no si
It is a correct criticism
es una crítica correcta
the difference
la diferencia
difference between
diferencia entre
easy channels now I understand why there is no
canales fácil ahora entiendo que no haya
I put the camera on too, I tell you
puesto la cámara de también te digo
they doubt your channel
dudan al tu canal
basically it is erectile failure
básicamente es haya fracasado eréctil
that guy has a rich father
que tiene un padre con dinero ese tío
he thinks he's better than me
cree que mejor que yo
by the way you didn't do it
por cierto no te hiciste
Thank you very much for the news you met
muchas gracias noticias te conocido
increasing funny videos you made
aumentando vídeos graciosos te hiciste
known and your channel but making videos
conocido y tu canal pero haciendo videos
of winding ir
de winding ir
of own content super content
de contenido propio contenido super
trophy so they can see the hypocrisy of
trofeo para que vean la hipocresía de
the good things are made of you or
los bien quedan hecho de ti o
of the clowns in fact did not have much of
de los payasos de hecho no tuvo mucho de
your channel but uploading videos the wind
su canal pero subiendo vídeos the wind
in order that we have all done and then
en orden que hemos hecho todos y luego
trying to
intentando que
you can't be heard if you try to speak
no se te escucha si intentas hablar
talking
hablando
again
otra vez
you go to college with this
tú vas a la universidad con esta
education there I am finishing has the
educación ahí estoy terminando tiene la
university as you are worth not as much as me
universidad como tú vales no como yo
but Gervasio claimed charisma and
pero gervasio pretendió carisma y la
People have loved me and they still follow me
gente me ha querido y yo me siguen
seeing what the people carry
viendo a la lo que carga de la gente del
video because it is in the stands and for
vídeo porque está en las gradas y por
what the face of good mix comes out and for that
qué sale la cara de buen mix y por esa
Scourge, don't play, be normal, they don't see you
lacra don't play se normal no te ven
because you are not so ranking above all and
porque no eres tan ranking sobre todas y
I
yo
everything analyzed but what does it stop us for?
todo analizado pero para que nos para
for millions of things xd if you were to be
para millones de cosas xd si eras al ser
verified
verificados
I brighten up the night, you don't know how much
me alegra la noche no sabes cómo me
I'm glad to
alegro de
that you are a liar and why
que lo mentiroso que eres y por lo que
I didn't want to show my face
no quería dar la cara
he doesn't listen to you
no te escucha
Listen, Gervasio, look at the liars
escucha gervasio fíjate los mentirosos
who were trying to win a
que estaban intentando ganar una
discussion because this is not a debate
discusión porque esto no es un debate
saying that you didn't see that you don't see
diciendo que tú no veías que tú no ves a
no one on youtube that you don't know
nadie en youtube que tú no conoces
money and generally your channel was about
dinero y generalmente tu canal trataba
to comment on the YouTube moves
de comentar las movidas de youtube dio
five years ago about supports
hace cinco años sobre apoyos
But because you insult, you don't know how to debate without
pero porque insulta no sabes debatir sin
insult so piqued in fret because you
insultar tan picado en traste porque te
I'm always explaining it because
lo estoy explicando siempre porque
they come in so fired up
entran tan ardido
No, no, I'll answer you, you love me.
no no yo te respondo tú me amas
liar let's say just support
mentiroso digamos solo apoyo
no insults you are a big liar goodbye
ningún insulto eres muy mentiroso adiós
of its content
de su contenido
literally r1 youtube
literalmente r1 youtube
YouTube and Twitter
youtube y twitter
no one on youtube because knowing about it
nadie en youtube porque saberlo del
internet punch or is it that easy
puñetazo del internet o es tan fácil
You're stupid, Javi, and I don't have anything to do.
eres tonto javi ser y nada que hace yo
The hole doesn't scare you, that is all you
no asusta el hoyo o sea todo tu
discussion that has focused me insultingly
discusión eso me ha centrado insultante
and you're going to enjoy it because it was
y te vas a ir disfrutando porque estaba
making a fool of yourself listen mind 11 you
haciendo el ridículo escucha mente 11 tú
You think that doesn't reach a person
crees que eso no le llega una persona
What do you think I see against YouTube?
que tú crees que yo veo contra youtube
It is highlighted that one we threw there was
se resalta que uno tiramos había
content so that the whole punch of
contenido para que todo el puñetazo de
This man
este hombre
No
no
HE
se
finish and say it's you tomorrow you will
acaba y di que eres tú mañana te a
Serving Peje X would have been better.
servir a el peje x hubiera sido mejor
that there was grain season started by
que hubiese de grano estacio inicio por
The least serious thing does not make content
lo menos de grave no hace contenido de
Salt thinks that a guy is coming to
sal se cree que a venir un tío a
complain about the sanse or an uncle who grew up
quejarse del sanse o un tío que creció
literally making windy videos and
haciendo literalmente vídeos de windy y
then when he won the followers he took
luego cuando ganó los seguidores cogió
the plate tried to change content and
la placa intentó cambiar de contenido y
to get into shape that was
ponerse a guardar forma que era
really what you like but there it died
realmente lo que te gusta pero ahí murió
on the channel
en el canal
only him
solamente le
supports
apoya
everyone in the world of jumping listens
todos los del mundo de salto escucha
all of all of hello in
todos los de todos los de hola en
YouTube
youtube
this
este
is
es
a video
un vídeo
where there is a video listen to this had a
donde hay un vídeo escucha esto tenía un
video so we can see your face to see
vídeo que podamos ver tu cara para ver
what is your content doing
qué es lo que haciendo tu contenido
own and that your ratio is then normal
propio y que tu ratio entonces es normal
that you now try to throw the ball at me
que tú ahora intentes tirarme la está de
that I also do, I also made salt
que yo también hago yo también hacía sal
SEO and such it is normal that you do it but
seo y tal es normal que lo hagas pero
Well, my channel and I are complicated.
bueno complicado estoy yo y mi canal
YouTube didn't have to rebuild everything.
youtube no tenían a que reconstruir todo
the tour and shantala farts
el tour y shantala se tira un pedo el
video works but can you tell me some
vídeo trabaja pero puedes decirme algún
place where we can see you
sitio donde podamos ver tú
where you can see if you have a machine
donde se ve a tu si tienes una máquina
the weather would be rainy
del tiempo estaría aguayo
men some critical video that
los hombres algún vídeo de crítica que
you remember that they have made you where
tú recuerde que te hayan hecho donde
a screenshot of your channel appears
aparezca captura de tu canal
and
y
what you dedicated yourself to but tell me why
lo que tú te dedicaste pero dime por
that
qué
but if I after that I after
pero si yo después de eso yo después de
make the switch to digital form myself
hacer el cambio a forma digital yo
I'll upload videos again later.
después voy a subir vídeos una vez más
You know a question today Gervasio, you ask me
sabes hoy una pregunta gervasio tú me
you taught the truth about time
enseñaste la del tiempo verdad tú
first I made the video without showing the
primero hacía el vídeo sin enseñar la
face truth no you have no [ __ ] idea my
cara verdad no no tienes ni idea mi
channel of truth or asia videos before with
canal de verdad o asia vídeos antes con
like him like the cry without showing his face
como él como el cry sin sacar la cara
that I started a few videos ago with
que yo empecé hace unos vídeos con
Correct background gameplay is fine
gameplay de fondos correctos vale
So don't tell me I don't know who it is.
entonces no me digas que no sé quién es
why if I know it very well then
de por qué si lo sé de sobra entonces al
evaluate the question I don't have one
evaluar la pregunta no tengo una
You ask all the questions on your channel
pregunta tú en tu canal todas las
miniatures had your face or have the
miniaturas tenían tu cara o tener la
wind's face and the other's face is that of order
cara de wind y la del otro la del orden
I had some miniature friends who were very
unas miniaturas tenía amigas que muchas
miniatures
miniaturas
but
pero
listen but what an ending
escucha pero que final
At the end he says, listen, I half hope that
al final dice escucha medio espero que
It's okay that you know that I think I
no pasa nada que sabe que yo creo que me
you can throw [ __ ] now say metal
puedes tirar ahora decir metal
you made me all secret salt seonae and
toda me hiciste sal seonae secreto y
Look, I follow you, I admit you, I give you the
mira yo te sigues te admito te doy el
that I did the same if there were 15 in the plan
que yo hice igual si 15 en plan hubiese
for 45 videos that were a bit of that
por 45 vídeos que eran un poco de ese
stick of the
palo de los
listen listen listen but I swear
escucha escucha escucha pero te lo juro
uncle of whatever the unemployment of reality is
tío de lo que sea el paro de la realidad
let's go something totally clear happened
vamos a que pasó algo totalmente claro
that to those videos of everything listen to me
que a esos vídeos de todo escúchame
Listen to me or with Frank it costs such and such a value
escúchame o con frank cuesta tal vale
everything everything the girls
todo todo las chicas
but that I on my channel apart from that
pero que yo en mi canal aparte de eso
that I also always gave him a
que yo también siempre le daba un
approach and a reflection of a
enfoque y una y una reflexión de una
criticism
crítica
its content
su contenido
it's called education
se llama educación
Now what you have to understand with me
ahora lo que tienes que entender conmigo
is that now that we are putting a
es que ahora que estamos poniendo un
your video but please let's see a world
vídeo tuyo pero por favor a ver un mundo
I can't hear anything, I don't understand what's going on
que no se oye nada no entiendo qué está
passing here that you wait that I am with you
pasando aquí que te esperes que te estoy
asking him not to speak because he is fed up with her
pidiendo que no hable por lo harto de la
people but
gente pero
you have to understand
tienes que entender
Okay, wait a second please.
vale espérate un segundo por favor
Please wait your second and I'll
espera tu segundo por favor y yo de
true I am I am telling you I am not going
verdad estoy yo te estoy diciendo no voy
waiting for you to watch a video
a estar esperando a que te veas un vídeo
If you have to watch a video, watch it.
si tiene que ver un vídeo de lo mira
then calmly there are some
luego tranquilamente que hay unos
how many summarized on youtube and even on
cuantos resumidos en youtube y hasta en
the problem in summary
el problema en resumen
that I have
que tengo
Me and your video commenting on videos of
yo y tu vídeo comentando vídeos de
third parties
terceros
It's just that it happens that it's four o'clock and
es que es que pasa que son las cuatro y
twenty tomorrow I have things to do
veinte mañana tengo hacer cosas
living together and you will have to do a
conviviendo y tendrás que hacer un
a lot of things with your life that was
montón de cosas con tu vida que estaba
not on a Monday but on a Wednesday at four
un lunes sino un miércoles a las cuatro
and twenty in the morning arguing with
y veinte de la mañana discutiendo con
channels to heaven because I can do it
canales al cielo pues me lo puedo
allow
permitir
because you are rich because you are rich
porque eres rico porque eres rico
the [ __ ] listen to me look right now in
la escúchame mira ahora mismo en
screen we are watching two of your videos
pantalla estamos viendo dos vídeos tuyos
okay okay
bueno vale
If we are not here, we have times of
si no estar aquí hemos unos tiempos de
History has done enough, man.
la historia ya ha hecho suficiente tío
Listen to me, this is a promotion.
escúchame estás promoción o sea
literally this video of yours
literalmente este vídeo tuyo
what are you promoting
qué estás promocionando
the page of a betting site
la página de una página de apuestas
a betting page of the SS Go project
una página de apuestas de ss go proyecto
and in this video he will show his face in the
y en este vídeo mostrará su cara en la
miniature
miniatura
This video has
este vídeo tiene
to remember that I had had correct
que recordar que tenía tenían correcto
okay and in this other one
vale y en este otro
That video is already more original than
ese vídeo ya es más original que
any video your channel because it is
cualquier vídeo tu canal porque es
literally that is literally ha video
literal o sea literal ja vídeo
but we wait for your moment
pero esperamos en tu momento
an optimal moment
un momento óptimo
Well before starting the video then
bueno antes de empezar el vídeo pues
I want to comment that this is not really
quiero comentar que realmente este no es
the type of videos you will find
el tipo de vídeos que vais a encontrar
on my subway channel to see what's there
en mi canal del metro para mira que hay
here in the capture of your politician
aquí en la captura de tu político
do it this way
hacerlo así
and that you can follow it, it is worth it that you can
y que lo podáis seguir vale que podáis
follow the criticism, criticism is worth it
seguir la crítica la crítica vale
I really just come to talk and criticize
realmente sólo vengo a hablar a criticar
to no one
a nadie
please
por favor
on the part
por parte
from heart and leaving you here invites you to a
de heart y dejarte aquí invita a una
reaction by listening to the reaction
reacción mediante escuchas a la reacción
yellow but listen to me
amarillo pero escúchame
says you only made a wind video and
dice que sólo lo hiciste un vídeo wind y
22 I want to remember but I don't think more
22 quiero recordar pero no creo que más
I don't think you have more than two videos.
que no creo que más de dos vídeos tienes
a playlist on your channel
una lista de reproducción en tu canal
with 49 videos that was called ask him
con 49 vídeos que se llamaba pregúntale
a wind in
a wind in
What are you saying lying down?
qué dices tumbado
high demand
gran demanda
taught me cs ask the ask website
me enseñó cs pregunta a la web de ask
wind and but I hope you're telling me
wind y pero espero que me estás contando
Uncle, but what about digestion or text?
tío pero que radique digestión o texto
what do you want
que quieres
but Javi really
pero javi de verdad
I hope I stylize my channel so that it
ojalá estilice mi canal para que lo
could see day
pudiesen ver día
see if I have your channel here in the
mira si es que tengo aquí tu canal en la
web machine look you go and your channel in the
web machine mira te vas y tu canal en la
web to machi but we are going to put it in
web a machi pero lo vamos a poner en
screen is that I literally have your channel
pantalla es que literal tengo tu canal
here so we can see it look
aquí para que lo veamos mira
to work now on my accent because you
a trabajar ahora de mi acento porque te
you are making a fool of yourself or always
estás quedando en ridículo o siempre
willy ximo this that you have had your
willy ximo esto que que haya tenido tu
the balls to present yourself as active
los de presentarte activo
to criticize my content by insulting
a criticar mi contenido insultando
will fully take advantage of this
enteramente va a aprovecharse de esto
to make luxury on your channel no no
para hacer el lujo en su canal no no
has to analyze and train what is more
tiene que analizar y entrenar que es más
feasible to spend one more minute
factible que dedicar un minuto más a
This payment is a presentation, a fantasy
este pago una presentación una fantasía
at night look listen to me the worst
de noche de mira escúchame el peor
blond world massage andorra and the
masaje del mundo rubio andorra y la
trash TV
telebasura
Marn yesterday has to stop the best
marín ayer tiene que parar los mejores
players of fort half of each
jugadores de fort mitad de cada
season the biggest bud of forni test
temporada los mayores bud de forni test
but takes all that content of its own
ma toma todo ese contenido propio
champion
campeón
in its own right and in fact if it is only
en su propio y de hecho si únicamente es
that if it is that said site but fort
que si es que dicho sitio pero fort
nylon manufactures it had as the why
nylon lo fabrica tuvo como el por qué
your channel died when starting the end of
murió tu canal cuando empezar el fin de
achieve the end of Logan for that very reason the
logar el fin de logan por eso propio el
eyebrows the castle of the youtubers the
cejas el castillo de los youtubers el
richest and most beloved rat boy on YouTube
niño rata más rico y querido de youtube
Limpul is completely crazy these days
limpul está completamente loco estos
musicals have to stop
musicales tienen que parar
Jordi Wild: It's time to stop YouTube Riva
jordi wild es hora de parar youtube riva
in 2017 visual cancer already or cabrera does
en 2017 cáncer visual ya o cabrera hace
fake jokes you check exploitation of
bromas falsas compruebas explotación de
Kids on YouTube: The Royal Winding Pack
niños en youtube el pack real de winding
go to youtube he sends himself by mail
ir youtube él se envía por correo la
sad situation now I am the man no
triste situación de ahora soy el man no
there's a [ __ ] video that's about you god
hay un vídeo que sea sobre ti dio
the true YouTube god of pizzas
el verdadero dios de youtube para pizzas
in classes this
en clases esto
St. James
st james
thousand degree blade you are idiots
cuchilla mil grados sois
while the children see your moment today
estando que ven los niños hoy tu momento
critical rat on the leading Wii
rata crítica en la wii líder
magician, drug addict, children, rats or bull's-eye
mago drogadicto niños ratas o diana
Vegetable guys have come here youtubers
vegetal tíos han venido aquí youtubers
famous in copy of the blond he has come
famosos en copia del rubio él ha venido
here literally to criticize me that my
aquí literalmente a criticarme que mis
Videos are all from the Willis
vídeos son todos da la willis
and study that is to the pse or the good
y estudio que es al pse o del bueno
millions to be champions criticism
millones al ser campeones crítica
this
este
character farts and you're in and
personaje se tira un pedo y estás en y
It's on your channel, good brother, and here
está en tu canal hermano bueno y aquí
says he has an order already or Cabrera Wind and
dice tiene un pedido ya o cabrera wind y
I was on your trailer channel
estaba en tu canal del tráiler
Javi Javi, do you want me to destroy you in one?
javi javi quieres que te destroce en una
phrase look action by magician of the sun of
frase mira acción por mago del sol de
fairies look how many videos you have of
hadas mira cuántos vídeos tienes tú de
dallas and look how many I have from wind and
dallas y mira cuántos tengo yo de wind y
champion because I will surely have
campeón porque yo seguramente yo tendré
many more but because your face is
muchos más pero porque tu cara que está
dead and yes and because I didn't do it he came out
muerto y sí y porque yo no hacía salió
cheap like you
barato como tú
They tell me I have spoken to him from time to time
me dicen yo he hablado con él de vez en
when I uploaded a video using the word
cuando subía vídeo usando la palabra
cancer in subtitles usually and
cáncer en subtítulos habitualmente y los
own videos used the word
propios vídeos usaba la palabra
autistic retards and such very
subnormal autistas y tal muy
frequently
frecuentemente
look for how many titles there are with the
busca los cuantos títulos hay con la
word canceled and of an electron then
palabra cancelada y de un electrón pues
there we have seen a couple of them here
ahí hemos visto un par de ellos aquí me
sending a screenshot of another
mandando una captura de otro
but well, a lot, but that is,
pero bueno pues un montón pero o sea el
autism seems like an insult to you
autismo a ti te parece un insulto
Autism doesn't even make me a [ __ ].
el autismo a mí no me hace ni
funny but at that time I was 2016
gracia pero yo en ese momento tenía 2016
I was a kid and I recognize that there are
era un chavalín y reconozco que hay
things that were wrong, that's what you
cosas que estaban mal eso te lo
I recognize completely and not in a
reconozco completamente y no de una
way to do it
forma de hacerlo
then I was [ __ ] ashamed in
entonces estaba vergüenza en
youtube no
youtube no
but I didn't want to come to that conclusion
pero no quería llegar a esa conclusión
There is a step from subnormal that today is not
de subnormal hay un paso que hoy día no
stop saying [ __ ] takes all the
para de decir subnormal lleva toda la
night I wonder why why you
noche me pregunto por qué por qué te
autism seems like an insult and [ __ ] is not
parece autismo un insulto y subnormal no
in any case, you hear about the end of it
en todas formas escucha de acabarse la
crime question the cai no tiguere you
pregunta crime el cai no tiguere te
you end up in the province but because those
acabas en la provinica pero porque esas
that you want to get out of those that create the
que queráis salir de esas que cree el
cry's channel and it came out after my channel
canal de cry y salió después de mi canal
no champion in just a little bit you
no campeón en apenas un poquito te
I repeat
repito
in fact cry started pawning my videos
de hecho cry empezado empeña mis vídeos
before but yes
antes pero si
their titles will never surpass that level of
sus títulos jamás superará ese nivel de
originality
originalidad
These fig balls welcome the trash
estas bolas higos bienvenidos la basura
from tigger or so your secondary channel
de tigger o sea que tu canal secundario
still active
sigue activo
your secondary channel is still active
tu canal secundario sigue activo
but
pero
me
me
I deserved a treat and you ate a [ __ ]
merecí grata y te comiste una
[ __ ] being content that wasn't
siendo contenido que no era
talking about other YouTubers and their garbage
hablando de otros youtuber y sus basuras
of
de
literature that is a marvel
literatura que es una maravilla
main a pearl
principal una perla
[Music]
[Música]
since you criticize my white hair so much
ya que criticas tanto mi pelo blanco
We are going to make criticisms about the hair
de críticas por el pelo vamos a hacer
one thing
una cosa
Okay
vale
living relatives
familiares vivas
I was watching a video of a review of
estaba viendo un vídeo de una crítica de
gold around May 2016 in another channel
oro hacia mayo del 2016 en otro canal
let's see let's see screenshots and
vamos a ver vamos a ver capturas y
works offend let's capture to see
trabajos ofender vamos a capturar a ver
no no but javi but it's not
que no no pero que javi pero que no es
offend is that it's half past four and
ofender es que son las cuatro y media y
you are trying to find arguments
estás intentando encontrar argumentos
to mess with me because you don't know what
para meterte conmigo porque no sabes qué
happens
pasa
Gervasio who
gervasio que
what an original way to do it
vaya manera original de hacer el
ridiculous
ridículo
totally it is that without knowing who he was already
totalmente es que sin saber quién era ya
you are becoming more like the product and the guy
estás quedando más al tío el producto y
It has been already knowing who was uncle has
ha sido ya sabiendo quién era tío ha
already been the [ __ ]
sido ya la
but for
pero para
He insulted people so much by telling them
tanto insultaba a la gente diciéndoles
albino ape
simio albino
original
original
[Laughs]
[Risas]
I mean I'll tell this kid hey
o sea le havre md a este chaval oye
white ape such was you very soon
simio blanco tal te era muy pronto
ha ha ha
jajaja
listen but but what are you doing watching a
escucha pero pero qué haces viendo un
feedback video
vídeo devolutivo
capture your channel to see the videos
captura de tu canal para ver los vídeos
that followed and so on
que seguía y demás
Well listen carefully this is very
bueno escuchar atentamente esto es muy
easy to watch a video, ale, don't let me
sencillo a ver un vídeo ale no me dejas
talk because no one follows you alone
hablar pues nadie os sigue tú solito
listen
escucha
that is, you stop to grow
o sea tú para para crecer
you put extra suits the glasses put
ponías extra trajes los vidrios ponían
in which they filled the description of
en las llenaban la descripción de
YouTube names and put tags on
nombres de youtube y ponía etiquetas en
the videos with a thousand things javi javi you
los vídeos con mil cosas javi javi te lo
I explain they are called labels, they are for what
explico se llaman etiquetas son para que
the classes the labels would be weird look
las clases las etiquetas sería raro mira
I didn't download that information from YouTube.
a mí no me baje ese dato de youtube las
labels lady candid are still
etiquetas señora cándida quietas son
so that people who are looking for the
para que la gente que buscando las
tags this here is champion but
etiquetas esto de aquí es campeón pero
put 800 youtube names in the
poner 800 nombres de youtube en la
description are not labels are extra
descripción no son etiquetas son extra
tags and it is prohibited on YouTube okay it is
tags y está prohibido en youtube vale es
God bless you or they won't put me in
que dios te bendiga o no me van a poner
the channel to nukem the hamburg we are already
el canal a nukem el hamburgo ya estamos
watching the nursery the nursery
viendo la guardería la guardería
Castile to here fame of others
castilla para para acá fama de los demás
and what nursery to scratch fame I find it
y que guardería a rascar fama me lo
you made a main and free javi said
hiciste un javi principal y libre dijo
willis son of willy re the son of willy
willis hijo de willy re el hijo de willy
re girlfriend of equals girlfriend of Williams
re novia de iguales novia de williams
willie de ports languages willy de
willie de puertos idiomas willy de
I go to the Aurum Play channel without having to
igorre al canal aurum play sin tener a
what to see
que ver
versed does not let you talk you know what happens
versado no deja hablar sabes qué pasa
that more people enter your channel by
que más gente entra en tu canal por
dallas which is a bit of a stretch to say the least
dallas que por decir esto es un poco
sad
triste
nothing really gave me that I understand that
nada dio de verdad que yo entiendo que
it bothers you normally
te moleste normal
And here at the end I want to give you the topic
y aquí al final le quiero dar el tema
As settled, he already looks at several options that
como zanjado ya mira varias opciones que
It would be like throwing [ __ ] out of my other life
sería echar de mi otra vida
wonderful nights means something else
maravillosa noches quiere decir algo más
and the last thing I'm going to tell you in the
y el último que te voy a decir en el
secondary channel is about but I tell you
canal secundario se trata pero te digo
It's that this wonder no one yours
es que es que esta maravilla nadie tus
cheap sal channels
canales sal se o barato
You practically don't give any kind of garbage
basura prácticamente no das ningún tipo
if you don't contribute anything, that is to say, it is a
de no aportas nada es decir es una
person who gives the charges and you
persona que da las cargas y tú lo
you comment on a video by
comentas en un vídeo por
Here I'm going to sleep, brat.
aquí voy a dormir niñato
with what intention did you make your videos
con qué intención hacía tus vídeos a
where I wanted to stop with your videos
donde quería hacer alto con tus vídeos
I wish the best, nothing if I started to go up
deseo lo mejor nada si yo empecé a subir
videos because I had fun I gave you
vídeos porque me divertía yo te de
Shlomi so that he could enter by going up
shlomi para que podría entrar subiendo
Keep uploading videos of satire
sigue subiendo vídeos de queda la sátira
a fart of a bastard place has [ __ ] and of
un pedo de cabrón place ha cagado y de
that Windows has already operated on the tits, so
que windows ya operó a las tetas pues lo
that served true more or less there is no
que servía true más o menos no hay
uploaded videos of wind and criticizing
subidos vídeos de wind y criticando
were that we have seen 45
fueran que hemos visto 45
keep lying
sigue mintiendo
javi javi keeps putting in a list of
javi javi sigue metiendo en una lista de
Javi's reproduction Javi finds in
reproducción de javi javi encuentra en
five of my videos the wind and I repeat
cinco vídeos míos the wind y te repito
I've made two YouTube videos in my entire life.
ha hecho dos de youtube en toda mi vida
without issuing generally designed it for you
sin emitir generalmente te lo diseñó
worth it look
valia mira
to
a
the Japanese in the description uncle of
los japoneses en la descripción tío de
still from the place to the secondary
todavía del lugar al secundario
I mean, what the [ __ ]
o sea qué
This is making videos for the 18th June
esto es hacer vídeos para los 18 jun es
look on the secondary channel uncle look at it
mira en el canal secundario tío mira lo
what does this [ __ ] description say?
que pone en la descripción esto ha
served to entertain you your video is
servido para divertirte tu vídeo se
called if you laugh you die but in the
llamaba si te ríes muere pero en las
tags puts videos random editor
etiquetas pone vídeos random editor de
youtube impossible to try not to laugh at
youtube imposible intentar no reír de
yolo
yolo
on the leadership tag page
en el liderazgo page de etiquetas
popular uncle congratulations and I am
populares tío enhorabuena y de yo lo soy
I am a channel, I don't know, I don't even know who
yo es un canal no sé no sé ni quién no
I don't even know what you do, label it
sé ni qué haces etiqueta lo
that we know is not the museums about desire
que sabemos no es los museos sobre ganas
We're watching the hub and laughing our heads off.
estamos viendo al hub y descojonándose
Host but very good but you and I say
pero buenísimo pero tú y yo digo
great video I love it a lot
buenísimo vídeo me encanta muchas
Thank you for the donation, thank you very much.
gracias por la donación muchas gracias
We go for the donation, he hasn't made me the
vamos por la donación no me ha hecho la
night of truth the truth is that it makes me
noche de verdad la verdad es que me hace
Your reaction is very funny and you yes you yes
mucha gracia tu reacción y tú sí tú si
your shitty points that I feel like throwing away
tus puntos de que siento tirarme
quite
bastante
but never know like the one you try
pero jamás saber como el que tú intentes
put your channel at the level of my channel
poner tu canal a mi canal al nivel del
yours no no no taste more tells us everything
tuyo no no no sabor más nos dice todo
when when I won
cuando cuando yo me ganó
in the message and give a message
en el mensaje y dar un mensaje
in
en
your channel is not at the level of mine
tu canal no está al nivel del mío el
yours is dead and closed and mine is
tuyo está muerto y cerrado y el mío está
active and
activo y
making a lot of money
ganando mucho dinero
I think I earned more than you
creo que ganó más yo que tu
channel those channels really or rather that
canal esos canales de verdad o sea que
I understand that your instinct creates you
yo entiendo que tu instinto te creas
Now, well, no one is more successful.
ahora bueno más exitoso no pasa nadie
literal
literal
literally
literalmente
to be closed and dead and mine very
para estar cerrado y muerto y el mío muy
active and increasingly
activo y cada vez más
you are no longer successful
no tienes más éxito
on YouTube
en youtube
no no on youtube
no no en youtube
Listen to me on YouTube, congratulations.
escúchame en youtube enhorabuena tiene
life your parents support you and no no
la vida tus padres te mantienen y no no
no no no you don't need it in college and
no no no necesitas en la universidad y
What happens is that your parents support you?
qué pasa que tus padres te mantienen no
that has whatever money you have for
que tiene lo que tengas de dinero por
your parents
tus padres
for your parents if your father has
por tus padres si tu padre ha
[Music]
[Música]
been able to pay for studies and place but
podido pagar los estudios y colocar pero
if I don't have a job if I don't have a job
si no tengo trabajo si no tengo trabajo
and they tell me Loranca that you were dedicated to
y me dicen loranca que te dedicabas con
your verified channel do you are in others
tu canal verificado hacer estás en otros
pitiful channels god
canales lamentables dios
[Music]
[Música]
of lamentable reliability that is that you
de fiabilidad lamentable que es que te
a person comments spam with verified
comenta una persona spam con verificado
and already in the plan of a person with a colleague
y ya en plan una persona con colega de
Loranca, a colleague from years ago, Mehsud or
loranca un colega de hace años mehsud o
I support whoever comments on that and you no longer
apoyo a quien se comenta eso y tú ya no
You automatically take that as true.
automáticamente lo tomas como cierto eso
You demonstrate the journalistic rigor that
demuestra tu el rigor periodístico que
you have to be practically non-existent
tienes que es prácticamente inexistente
electric practically non-existent if
eléctrico prácticamente inexistente si
he feels like a non-existent god for nothing and
se siente dios inexistente para nada y
I really notice that we are here
yo de verdad fíjate tú que estamos aquí
in a debate in which he has been humiliated and
en un debate en el que se ha humillado y
I expected
esperaba
because
porque
evil
mal
prepared and all things knowing
preparados y todas las cosas sabiendo
that you are going to come to you, look what
que tú vas a venir a ti fíjate lo que
we do with you
hacemos contigo
why why why is there one day left
qué por qué por qué queda un día
exactly
exactamente
completely
completamente
without knowing who your arguments were already
sin saber quién era tus argumentos ya
They were painful and could not be sustained by
eran penosos y no se sostenían por
nowhere has been able to
ninguna parte no ha sido capaz de
to be able to argue and be able to explain to a
poder argumentar y poder explicar a una
because he comes in to see if he doesn't talk too little
porque entra a ver si no habla poco
I'm talking uncle really is very
estoy hablando tío de verdad es muy
rude that is a lack of
maleducado eso es una falta de
total performance to the people we are going to
rendimiento total a la gente vamos a
arrive everything sounds worth it sell
llegar todo suena vale venda
I am applying because it has been done
estoy aplicando porque ha hecho el
ridiculous if you were to explain it to people
ridículo si usted lo explicará la gente
in the comments of this when it
en los comentarios de esto cuando lo
go up
suba
to the stage if you want it happened to you from one
al escenario si quieres te pasó de una
thumbnail to see if it gets any views
miniatura a ver si le sacan visitas
although I doubt it very much, champion
aunque lo dudo mucho campeón
of the world
del mundo
why not
porque no
I wanted to come and show my face as if it were the
quería venir a dar la cara como si la
recognized the memories of today will be
reconocieron los recuerdos de hoy será
In the minute of fame we are familiar with sos of
en el minuto de fama nos suenan sos de
Spain has 40 thousand visits in total and
españa totalmente tiene 40 mil visitas y
40 thousand views is little, I don't like it
40 mil visitas es poco no me gusta
garbage points then yours
basura puntos pues entonces el tuyo de
way that I had a thousand had had a
forma de que tenía mil tenía tenía un
million visits hundreds of thousands of visits
millón de visitas cientos mil visitas de
Those videos that speak to me the most were those
esos vídeos que más me dice fueron esos
They watched the turbo plan video.
miraron el vídeo de turbo plan el vídeo
turbo pose is to continue with the
turbo plantear está de seguir con el
video that made you turbo plan
vídeo que te hizo turbo plan
You know that friends of friends would never be
sabes que amigos de amigos nunca sería
friend of a person like you give friends
amigo de una persona como tú das amigos
true friends, nothing happens
amigos de verdad no pasa nada
continues is 40 years old and has 21 videos of
continua tiene 40 años y 21 vídeos de
dallas but it seems like it again
dallas pero otra vez lo parece
I wish you the best in life, uncle.
te deseo lo mejor en la vida tío con
west but really at 40 years old no
west pero de verdad con 40 años no
will be waiting to see what happened to him
estará pendiente de que le ha pasado a
dallas uncle but be careful because with
dallas tío pero ten cuidado porque con
40 years old, your father may not be able to do it for you.
40 años lo mismo tu padre no te puede
maintain but I repeat if you are married
mantener pero te repito si casado tu
Father has been able to solve your life
padre te ha podido solucionar la vida
Now that he is a brat but when he is
ahora que es un niñato pero cuando tenga
40 years since a couple has passed but
40 años desde que un par ha pasado pero
If I pay my parents things, uncle, what?
si le pago ya mis padres cosas tío que
you have no [ __ ] idea that you are a
no tienes ni idea que eres un
[ __ ] one who speaks without knowing cadet
subnormal del que habla sin saber cadete
the [ __ ] mother of mine from live the trio
la de madre mía de live el trío
you are a hick you have to talk without
eres un paleto tiene que hablar sin
knowing also is that it is very funny and
saber además es que es muy gracioso y de
truth to me yes from place
verdad a mí sí de sitio
You have a very bright future
tienes un futuro muy brillante por
ahead in which, well, I hope so
delante en el cual pues eso espero que
in 10 years in all your successes
dentro de 10 años en todos tus éxitos
subscribers here seeing that the past
suscriptores aquí viendo que la pasada
tables
tablas
If Dallas dies, you have a problem.
como se muera dallas tienes un problema
I'll let you know it's broken too.
yo te lo voy avisando está roto también
keep sucking from the bottle, it's still a
sigue chupando del bote sigue siendo un
parasite and still contributes nothing to the
parásito y sigue sin aportar nada a la
society more than abortion
sociedad más que al aborto
entertainment friend but knows how to know
entretenimiento amigo pero sabe saber
to argue something with logic that is not
argumentar algo con lógica que no sea
insult
insultar
[Music]
[Música]
before you laugh that I laugh 200 I don't
antes te ríes de que me río 200 yo no me
repeat is like a thing the accent that
repite es como una cosa el acento que
one has because he was raised in a
uno tenga porque se haya criado en un
site and something else that says that you believe
sitio y otra cosa que hable que te creas
from the Bronx' when I don't know if you're from
del bronx' cuando no sé si eres de
Alicante or some common center that
alicante o de algún centro común que
like the Bronx that says that
como que de el bronx que dice que de
Bronx witness now a bastard but yes
testigo del bronx ahora cabrón pero si
you are doing what you criticize now
te estás haciendo lo que criticas ahora
same to see you are going to compare my
mismo para ver tú vas a comparar mi
way of speaking and my way of expressing
forma de hablar y mi forma de expresar
me with yours that is disrespectful
me con la tuya que faltando al respeto
all time
todo tiempo
but shut up brooks javi when he's 60
pero callan brooks javi cuando tenga 60
years and comment on the daughter's toilets
años y comentes los aseos de la hija de
Will and Rex will follow us here.
will y rex aquí seguiremos nosotros a
Portland, to be clear, says that it doesn't have
portland a ver claro dice que no tiene
the future and tomorrow you play with the [ __ ]
el futuro y mañana juegas con el
Blondes, that's what I call success.
rubios yo a eso lo llamo triunfar
totally but oh well what would you give me?
totalmente pero bueno que me daría
baby with the blond who plays put
guagua con el rubio que jugar poner
failed is fun wait for me
fracasado es divertido espérate que me
They have sent an audio that there is this
han mandado un audio que hay este
moment the house says [ __ ] good
momento la casa dice subnormal buen
exercise in 2018 to scientists in a way
ejercicio en 2018 a científicos de forma
he's doing pretty well
le va bastante bien bastante
spectators and everything that happens that sometimes
espectadores y todo que pasa que a veces
I had people like Agustn and that's why you know
tenía gente como agustín y por eso sabes
shut up and stop insulting people
cállate y deja de faltar a la gente tiró
some sea and rain let's go gay
algo de mar y llodio vayamos de
has said
ha dicho
Seriously, that's the level of [ __ ].
en serio ese es así el nivel de
but he said a [ __ ] voice
pero ha dicho voz de
if he has a voice a bit like a rat's voice
si tiene un voz un poco una voz de ratas
disgusting
asquerosas
a [ __ ] a disgusting rat second
un una rata asquerosa segundo
that person is a disgusting rat wow
esa persona es una rata asquerosa guau
Well, let them express themselves later, Valeria.
bueno déjalos expresarse valeria luego
had at your level okay
tuvo a tu nivel vale
It's a very boring day
es muy aburrido día
the workshop and a friends when also with
el taller y un amigos cuando también con
verified trying already the best
verificado tratando ya lo mejor se
found their way to many viewers
encontraban sus para muchos espectadores
with the songs
con las canciones
come and when writing it was very noticeable
venir y al escribir se notaba mucho al
be verified and there wasn't so much there
estar verificado y ahí no había tanto
just like now that it happens that the whole
cabal como ahora que pasa que toda la
people suddenly show off from live to live
gente de repente se exhiba del directo a
your channels and this already has that
sus canales y esto ya tiene eso
constantly because they are not only
constantemente porque no son de sólo
family and I know I have to capture that
familia y sé que tengo capturar eso
because that's when I started
porque o sea en ese momento me empezado
finishing positions people tests
terminando puestos personas pruebas
with their verified channels here
con sus canales verificados acá les
[Music]
[Música]
and that when because
y eso cuando porque
no one has notified to scratch
nadie ha notificado a rascar
I really don't think it's bad at all.
realmente realmente no me parece mal lo
what he did and what he knows and what he put
que hacía y que sepa y que pusiera
but I
pero yo
You can talk to me, you have to literally
me pueden hablar tienes que literalmente
Do you think he's giving an image of being cool or
te crees que está dando imagen de guay o
something of the sort
algo por el estilo
of a little boy when he is being
de un niño chico cuando le están
giving up and is thinking about a
rindiendo y está pensando en una
tantrum and
pataleta y
I am 40 years old
tengo 40 años
I wouldn't mind at all if
no me parecería mal del todo que
I will try to find a way to make a living by doing my own thing.
intentara buscarte la vida haciendo su
cleaning as you did at 180 wind videos and
aseo como hacías a 180 vídeos de wind y
I knew well making Nord videos
conocía bien haciendo videos de nord
was doing everything he was doing that
estuvo haciendo todo lo que hacía que
you would like to address the problem on other channels
quisieras en otros canales el problema
of wine
de vino
trying to give us content classes
intentando darnos clases de contenido de
own content uncle is doing
contenido propio tío es haciendo
comments their content is garbage and
comentarios su contenido es basura y
This lack of personality is
esta falta de personalidad es
literally one came out cheap and people
literalmente un salió barato y la gente
It doesn't fit in at all now nor for you very much
no entra por todo ahora ni por ti muy
easy then nothing you continue you know
fácil entonces nada tú sigues sabes
You know very well what I'm telling you
sabes de sobra lo que te estoy diciendo
in
en
I really wish you the best.
total en verdad te deseo lo mejor te
keep fighting to get ahead
sigue sigue luchando por sacar adelante
to your family that you are very successful and
a tu familia que eres muy exitoso y
I'm sure he earns more than me
seguro que gana más que yo
from my parents for what you told me
de mis padres por lo que me has dicho
before
antes
but the education of a batch of children
pero la educación una tanda de niños
for 23 year old boy combs bald shop
para niño 23 años peina tienda calvo
Well
bueno
I think the best thing is that I'm having
yo es que lo mejor es que estoy teniendo
I am left with nothing that you just take and
quede sin nada que tú sólo te coges y
t&amp;t that's defining dude for real
t&amp;t que está definiendo tío de verdad
Seriously, you keep fighting.
en serio que tú sigue sigue luchando
try to take [ __ ] from others is that
intenta sacar a los demás es que
In the end, that's your channel, you know, that's it.
al final ese es tu canal sabes es esto
to see your work by chance javi no
a ver tu trabajo por casualidad javi no
literally fixes your work and your
fija literal se sature tu trabajo y tu
way to make money like this inside if I pine
forma de ganar dinero así dentro si pino
You keep asking around, they tell you
tú sigue preguntando por ahí te dicen
I ask you nothing, I ask you, you are
nada te lo pregunto a ti yo tú estás
I was dedicated to dropshipping no
dedicaba el dropshipping no
and mouths
y bocas
but well the point of equality 4 without
pero bueno el punto de igualdad 4 sin
search because because it is because you
buscar porque porque es porque te
you are dedicated to dropshipping
dedicas al dropshipping
if thinking
si pensando
Well, keep asking your colleagues
bueno sigue preguntándole a tus colegas
Javi, congratulations, dwarf, you are a
javi enhorabuena enana que eres una
very successful person you are 40 years old
persona muy exitosa tienes 40 años
you have a daughter what we reached 36 and
tienes una hija lo que se nos llegó 36 y
the real negative and you're there
el negativo de verdad y estás ahí
sitting right now looking for videos of
sentado ahora mismo buscando vídeos de
A review, well today they gave it to me
una crítica bueno hoy me la regalaron
YouTube has given away the man's money
youtube ha regalado el dinero de hombre
has given away
ha regalado
the money from
el dinero de
I really enjoyed it afterwards
verdad he disfrutado bastante luego
buy to buy the pacifier buy yourself
comprar a comprar el chupete cómprate
something of me or I wouldn't be surprised if you bought it
algo de mí o no me sorprendería compra
rich or what
ricas o qué
so I think you're going to have them in your
así que creo que los vas a tener en tu
life so nothing I hope it goes well for you
vida así que nada espero que te vaya muy
well and that you continue to search for that
bien y eso que sigas sigas buscando que
last time on the internet and that's even though my
la pasada las en internet y eso que mi
channel is not at the level of was not at
canal no está el nivel de no estaba al
level of seeing your natural channel level of the
nivel de ver tu canal natural nivel del
south side to the exeo that follows the prison or
lado sur al exeo que sigue a la cárcel o
channels services the empty campus your
canales servicios el plantel vacío tu
channel is not at the level of mine
canal no está al nivel que el mío
mainly because it has no channel
principalmente porque no tiene canal no
I have a program and I have no problems.
tengo programa me y no tengo problemas
not having a channel no I don't want a channel
no tener canal no no quiero un canal
right now not mentioning them
ahora mismo no haciendo mención ellos
although they would also like to have the channel
aunque quisieran también tener el canal
It is forbidden, you have to do as much as possible
está prohibido tenéis que hacer cuanto
before what you are what you are not
antes lo que tú es lo que tú no
You understand that I stopped uploading videos on
entiendes que yo deje de subir vídeos en
my channel and most of it is now because the
mi canal y la mayoría es ahora porque la
People stopped seeing you not because I'm
gente dejó de verte no porque yo esté
This video was not uploaded for four months
esto estaba sin subir vídeo cuatro meses
you understand four or five months went up a
entiendes cuatro o cinco meses subió un
video and had 60 thousand more views than you
vídeo y tenía 60 mil visitas más que tú
now that you upload every day so
ahora que subes todos los días así que
It's okay, man, try to leave me more.
no pasa nada tío intenta dejarme más
slow and that you would tell me about SEO and continue
lentas y que me canarias al seo y sigue
criticizing makes me very lucky in life
criticando me tiene mucha suerte la vida
and [ __ ] you, you already have one
y que te den por culo ti ya tienes un
channel that is very boring and that you know
canal que es muy aburrido y que te se
base the contents of others you are
basan los contenidos de los demás eres
A parasite and the day Dallas dies
un parásito y el día que se muera dallas
you run out of content that God gives you
te quedas sin contenido que dios te
bless
bendiga
beautiful tonight family
guapísima la noche de hoy familia
be it in my wanting this comes out for us
sea en mi queriendo nos sale esto
not even wanting to, uncle
ni queriendo tío
no but it is not that he has been humiliated
no pero no es que haya que ha humillado
Let's see, it's not about that, it's about
a ver es que no se trata de eso es que
I who spoke to him about education
yo que hablando le contó la educación
of the world in a plan believing that it was a
del mundo en plan creyendo que era un
simple hater a simple random was already there
simple hater un simple random ya estaba
looking bad because he was not able to
quedando mal porque no era capaz de
argue nonsense and enjoy it
argumentar las tonterías y los disfruto
and the nonsense he was saying that
y las chorradas que estaba diciendo que
You are 40 years old and you can't be a salsa dancer.
tiene 40 años no puedes hacer salsero
because he's 40 years old and that's sad
porque tiene 40 años y eso es triste
because your content in their own
porque tu contenido en los propios
device and without knowing who it was, he already knew
device y ya sin saber quién era ya se
would have been humiliated
hubiera ido humillado
I walk from the outside entrance and after a while
yo ando de entrada exterior y al rato
squid game, damn, let's see what the
juego del calamar a ver que a la
next debate with Jesus Christ how good
próxima debate con jesucristo qué bueno
that it's over because I have to go to
que ya acabó porque tengo que ir a
take a bath javi see you hehe theobroma
bañarme javi nos vemos jeje theobroma
look look man that's not
fíjate fíjate tío que no
be first and then gave us some good ones
esté primero y luego nos dio unas buenas
laughter to say the typical nonsense
risas para decir las típicas tonterías
What a way to complain about being told
vaya forma de quejarte de que te digan
coward and then insult like that for free
cobarde y luego insultar así de gratis
Calm down, Javi is just commenting.
cálmate que javi sólo está comentando
consolation of the anxious miniature
consuelo de la miniatura ansiosa lo de
the miniature literally gave me
la miniatura dio literalmente me ha
criticized down to the miniature
criticado hasta la miniatura
when he had a channel like mine
cuando él tenía un canal como el mío
but yes no
pero sí no
I mean, really good guy, damn, I forget
o sea buenísimo tío se me olvida
I forgot to send you successes for the video
se me olvida mandarles éxitos el vídeo
shot that we have to edit today [ __ ] me
tiro que tenemos que edita hoy me
I curse you are a great guy
cago en la sea buenísimo tío
Javi, never leave the internet for
javi nunca te vayas de internet por
Please, I won't do it, uncle, for things like that.
favor no lo haré tío por cosas como la
Today I pay for the internet, they are great and
de hoy pago internet están buenísimos y
Don't you realize what's going on?
es que no os dais cuenta de la movida
I think it has been one of the best debates
creo que ha sido de los mejores debates
It has been the great strength that remained
ha sido la vigor que quedaron
God tells of one thing
cuenta de una cosa dios
amazing how people hate
increíble como la gente que odia a
Dallas remains arid and does not accept that
dallas sigue árida y no acepta que le
is going well neither to him nor to those who do it
esté yendo bien ni a él ni a los que lo
They supported us but you give us
apoyaron pero es que usted nos dan
He tells the story as it is, okay now.
cuenta de la movida bien como es vale ya
I'm going to leave it because I don't even know if
lo voy a dejar porque es que no sé ni si
we are going to
vamos a
I don't even know what miniature to put on it
es que no sé ni qué en miniatura ponerle
really
de verdad
I mean, I would put this one no
o sea yo le pondría a esta no
I would put this one on it but I would put a nose on it
yo le pondría está pero le pondría nariz
of a clown ied on the nose at least
de payaso ied en la nariz por lo menos
It is but clown nose is that you do not
está pero nariz de payaso es que no os
You realize on air if you watch the video of
dais cuenta al aire si mirar el vídeo de
turbo planet of gervasio in form and os
turbo planet de gervasio en forma y os
you will find out about the move and what happened
enteraréis de la movida de lo que pasó
in the end it is
al final es
I was already looking badly humiliated but
ya estaba quedando mal humillado pero
we would have left thinking it was a
nos hubiéramos ido pensando que era un
hater and period a hater [ __ ] without
hater y punto un hater sin
education and a half a ball with that with
educación y medio un bolo con esa con
That way of thinking, this is worth it.
esa forma de pensar esto el rollo vale
We would have already left without ever knowing
ya nos hubiéramos ido sin saber jamás en
the life that was him
la vida que era él
Okay, we wouldn't have gone and never in the
vale no hubiéramos ido y nunca en la
life we would have known it was him
vida hubiéramos sabido que era él
Do you understand me, we would have left and that's it?
me entendéis nos hubiéramos ido y ya
It is but it is the best in the world
está pero es que la lo mejor del mundo
has been discovering that it was the one that when
ha sido descubrir que era el que cuando
when I found out who he was
cuando yo me enterado que era quién era
when I found out who Seman was
cuando yo me enterado de quién era seman
the sticks of the sowing fell because that
cayó los palos del sembrado porque que
in fact but I know that this guy
de hecho pero sé que este chico
He left YouTube because it failed and he is
se fue de youtube porque fracasó y es
that literally all of you
que literalmente todo todas ustedes
thanks to zero
gracias al cero
without showing your face
sin mostrar la cara
how did you know it was him he told me in
cómo supiste que era el me lo dijo en
YouTube
youtube
Brutal guy, I pay for internet for these things.
brutal tío por estas cosas pago internet
really
de verdad
I pay for the internet for this thing
por esta cosa pago internet
The best thing is that I was recording
lo mejor es que estaba grabando
clear failure
fracasado claro
but and the miniatures are not that you
pero y las miniaturas no es que tu
content is not your own because you do not
contenido no es propio porque tú no
you appear in the thumbnails and how
sales en las miniaturas y como
the thumbnail will show the news that is
la miniatura saldrá la noticia que esté
giving does not come out the news comes out
dando no sale el telediario sale el
Mediaset director on the cover
director de mediaset en la portada no
We get the news from here
nos salen las noticias de aquí es
incredible no
increíble no
a fantasy was born of me like that
nació una fantasía de yo así una
fancy
fantasía
Your 46,000 channel was better than the
tu canal de 46.000 fue mejor que el
totally dream
sueño totalmente
but it's almost [ __ ] up
pero es casi
[ __ ] action night time
acción jodidamente la noche hora de
train to go to hell
entrenar irnos a la
Long live Dallas, I'll be there.
larga vida a dallas hito ahí voy a estar
when javi does the salsa from the
cuando javi haga el salsero desde el
geriatric radiant face with eyes
geriátrico cara radiante con ojos
smiling clear how we are going to enter 5
sonrientes claro cómo vamos a entrar a 5
the morning paulo
la mañana paulo
and here I'm going to click
y aquí voy a pinchar
but you realize what they are like
pero os dais cuenta de cómo son los
arguments of
argumentos de
if we have to train even though
si es que tenemos que entrenar aunque
be an hour even if it is now goes
sea una hora aunque sean ahora va
we have to train uncle is that we have
tenemos que entrenar tío es que tenemos
that training that is now to you
que entrenar que sean ahora a ti
or if we have to train uncle it is
o si es que tenemos que entrenar tío es
that you have to train, come on, I don't have any
que hay que entrenar venga va no tengo
water dream we train but tele opera
sueño de agua entrenamos pero ópera tele
and Amanda Army
y amanda ejército
the army band what it has to
la banda ejército lo que tiene que
edit is really good dude
editar está buenísimo tío de verdad
[ __ ] turned on
jodidamente prendido
[ __ ] splendid t
jodidamente espléndido t
Let's see, the army is sending her to
a ver es que la manda ejército para
edit
editar
What did Jorge do? Well, look.
qué que hizo jorge ja bueno pues fíjate
that some images have come out, okay
que ha salido unas imágenes vale
a moment when she was needed
un momento que se la mandó a necesitar
but it's not like I made a coke
pero no es que me he hecho una cocacola
created to be able to endure
creó para poder aguantar
babies and the uncle's [ __ ]
guaguas y la tío
so he supports her
así la apoya
On top of that, the guy said he was 23 years old.
encima el tío dijo que tenía 23 años que
I have searched Greve's age on Google.
yo he buscado edad de greve en google no
more because he is 24 haha
más porque él tiene 24 jaja
I swear I used to think it was
te lo juro que llegaba a pensar que era
to believe
de creer
and I thought it was serious or never for the
y pensé que era grave o nunca para la
how old are you
edad que tiene
name
nombre
and Javier's spokesperson comes to think
y llega a pensar la vocera de javier
trending topic let's see a little
trending toppic vamos a ver un poco
the man is an artist, he works
el hombre es artista trabaja
once has passed
una vez ha pasado
42 52
42 52
I go to the medical service in Coca-Cola in
voy al servicio médico en coca-cola en
family this has been wonderful
familia esto ha sido maravilloso
The next step is to debate with salsa
lo siguiente es debatir con salsa
YouTuber for Puig, Hurrah, Backup, Apure
youtuber para puig hurra backup apure
for pure [ __ ] sweat that I wake up not
para puro sudor que despierto no
more bastard left behind don't count
cabrón más dejado tirado no computan
those go up with me live
aquellos subir conmigo en directo
success the tournament in Spain at eight o'clock
éxito el torneos en españa a las ocho de
the afternoon that video is for the lady no
la tarde ese vídeo es para la señora no
you complicate things too much, pretty pretty
te compliques demasiado bonito bonito
Click on it as much as you remember
métele los clic que tú te acuerdes que
you can put the hs effect on them
le puedas meter mete el efecto hs a los
that the mirror effect is something that takes you out
que el efecto espejo algo que te saca
supports but fears about six or
apoya pero teme lo sobre las seis o las
seven in the evening so as not to have to
siete de la tarde para no tener que
be aware of this in the tournament
estar pendiente de esto en el torneo
churri
churri
leaves them lying around in their suitcases
las deja tirada en sus maletas que
I wake up pig and it's not that I came
despierto cerdo y no es que yo venía
It was wonderful last night these are the
ha sido maravillosa anoche estas son las
nights that I like
noches que a mí me gustan
These are the beautiful nights with the family
estas son las noches guapas en familia
I don't know if everything is there but it has thrown me
no sé si está todo pero me ha tirado
Bye, everything, but more abandoned, Paulo
chau todo pero más dejado tirado paulo
Come on to the disc, let's go light now with more
venga al disco vamos ligero ya con más
calm down, congratulations on your growth
calma felicitarte por el crecimiento me
I am glad to have been able to see the improvement and
alegra haber podido ver la mejora y a
where you have arrived, congratulations and
dónde has llegado muchas felicidades y
good wishes that are appreciated every time
buenos deseos que se aprecie cada vez
more that art a hug and now tell me
más ese arte un abrazo y ahora decirme
that I don't deserve a prize from him
que no me merezco yo un premio de el
land
land
ah
ah
Now tell me that I don't deserve a
ahora decirme que no me merezco yo un
Slam Prize for the best debates
premio de slam por los mejores debates
that with Jordi it's cool
que con jordi guay
or the public friend
o la pública amigo
Javi today we are going, we are going for an hour, for an hour
javi hoy vamos vamos una hora una hora
We have one hour and tomorrow we will get in
una hora tenemos y mañana nos meteremos
at noon and until we have no other choice
al mediodía y hasta no nos queda otra al
midday, well midday, that's not for you
mediodía bueno mediodía que para ti no
I know what time it is where I get in the mike
sé qué hora es donde me meto en el mike
the normal ones do not follow the error badly
la normal no se les siguen el error mal
the gray USA no
el gris eeuu no
17.11 17.1 I don't have one I have one 18.1 no
17.11 17.1 no tengo tengo uno 18.1 no
There is that well look do you remember what
hay es que bueno mira recuerdas lo que
we did the other time when you changed
hicimos la otra vez cuando cambiaste de
version yes
versión sí
but I don't have it, you have to do another one
pero no tengo es tienes que hacer otra
new from how we did it last time
nueva de como lo hicimos la otra vez
because when you installed the installer to
porque cuando instaladas el instalador a
It also happened to me that they were deleted
mí también me pasó de que se borraron
all profiles
todos los perfiles
the version of it no no no no no
la versión de ello no no no no no
that is, you already have it installed only
o sea ya la tiene instalada sólo a
Lagarde invalid of new and entering
lagarde no válida de nuevas y entrando
come on okay or ok
venga vale o ok
117 1
117 1
hey
oye
and
y
even I could beat him
hasta yo podía ganarle
great guys
buenísimo tíos
very good but that is the south
buenísimo pero o sea el sur
He leaves you hanging but he's been with Jude
te deja colgado pero ha estado con jude
the bc all afternoon we are watching the
el bc toda la tarde estamos viendo el
direct so that joguet can help each other
directo para q joguet que se ayuden que
being is what has wanted to come to us
ser es lo que nos ha querido venir
with me to comment on the salsa singer already
conmigo a comentar el salsero ya lo
we were commenting on times
estábamos comentando nosotros en veces
wait a moment and do something
un momento te hagas una cosa
with things you calm without nerves or
con las cosas tú tranquilo sin nervios o
where I'm going to put render so
donde voy a poner renderizar por lo
except for the extract where he talked about the
menos el extracto donde habló de los
slam because of course I didn't expect that much
slam porque claro no me esperaba tanto
I didn't expect debate these are the
no me esperaba debate estos son las
things that come out improvisation to see
cosas que salen improvisación a ver
you don't need much either
tampoco te hace falta mucho
training for the first chapter
entrenamiento para el primer capítulo
we could continue training tomorrow
podríamos seguir entrenando mañana
when I finish
cuando termine
but the idea is that you have at least a few
pero la idea es que tengas mínimo unas
bases or because you have not played in
bases o sea porque no has jugado en
how many days 3
cuantos días 3
Even if it is a small crack it is a little bit and
con ser mínima grieta es un poquito y
so you remember the controls for
así ya te recuerdas los controles para
tomorrow yesterday against diamond or no no
mañana ayer ante diamond o no no
We haven't played for two days, wait
llevamos dos días sin jugar espera
We have made renderings to be able to upload
tenemos hecho renderiza para poder subir
in the clear
en la claro
Of course I made it clear because there is no other option
claro la dejado claro por no queda otra
we have to be a little bit the idea why
tenemos que estar un poco la dea por qué
I have to render extracts and no no
tengo de renderizar extractos y no no
I will be able to upload extracts and I tomorrow
voy a poder subir extractos y yo mañana
I have to put you to sleep a little while I was sleeping and
te tengo que dormir algo lo que dormía y
on the couch or something until morning
en el sofá o algo hasta la dio la mañana
knows
sabe
clear at least the same four or
claro por lo menos el mismo cuatro o
I also have five hours of sleep
cinco horas de dormir yo también tengo
that I get up early because before
que levantarme temprano porque antes de
to enter we have to do a practice
entrar tenemos que hacer una práctica
I don't give a damn what you do of the day
del día lo que tú haga me importa una
[ __ ] [ __ ] and as if you don't have to
y como si no tienes que
sleep in a native week right
dormir en una semana nativa verdad
far away
alejado
Well, we'll see who materialized the
bueno veremos quién te materializó el
squid
calamar
I hope you don't have me saved anymore
yo espero que no me más tengo guardado
because bully guards
porque matón guarda
it's going to be a problem it is a problem
va a ser un problema es un problema
fat truth
gordo verdad
and it's sticking to me
y es que se me está quedando
elementary got caught has proof
elemental quedó pillado tiene constancia
but I don't sell, pitiful, pitiful
pero no vendo lamentable lamentable
total
total
ok that's it now
vale ya está ahora
how am I going to be rendered I'm going to be
cómo voy a estar renderizado me voy se
uploads junk and
sube trastos y
without and without dogs but it takes him to go up
sin y sin perros pero lo ocupa subir
very early roll or already a worker
muy temprano rollo o sea ya obrero
in front of
delante
Of course, the CNDH stadiums or something like that
claro lo de la cndh estadios o así
There were some without interaction with others.
los hubo sin interacción a otros el
secondary channel is garbage
canal secundario es una basura
let's go let's go
vamos vamos
Come on, not even plus salsa reaches that far
vamos ni plus salsa llega hasta tan
garbage
basuras
and follows
y le sigue
clear
claro
people agreed that tomorrow at 8 to
gente acordaron que mañana a las 8 al
final not at 10 okay
final no a las 10 vale
friends see where you are
amigos ven dónde estás
sometimes you chest behind you
a veces te cofre atrás
some boyfriend is calling me
me está llamando algún novio
I am saying
estoy diga
say
diga
really and all kids
de verdad y todos chavales
I opened them and saw everything inside
abre los y vi a todo lo que adentro
all yes
todo sí
Okay
vale
ok look I'm going to tell you the sword
ok mira te voy a decir la espada la
you have in light
tienes en luz
ok
ok
I'm going to forget
voy a olvidar
you put the sword in the 1 the bow in
la espada te lo pones en el 1 el arco en
2 the blocks in 3 and the food in
el 2 los bloques en el 3 y la comida en
the 4 ok and the shield then in the other hand
el 4 ok y el escudo pues en la otra mano
to the list if look let's practice
a la lista si mira vamos a practicar
something very simple that is
algo muy simple que es
killing bugs basically I think it is
matar bichos básicamente yo creo que es
a better way to practice aim
una mejor forma de practicar la puntería
that being poured out on us you remember
que estando volcarnos tuyo recuerdas
how to hit the truth
cómo golpear verdad
now yes for example
ahora sí por ejemplo
again and again
una y otra vez
lear
lear
another other
otro otro
incredible the area killed them well
increíble el área de los mató bien
because they don't attack my chick
porque ellos no me atacan el pollito
incredible now I'm going to seem like a
increíble ahora te voy a parecer un
enemy monster that is what it was
monstruo enemigo que es lo que era
careful careful
cuidado cuidado
you run towards the incredible having
auto corras hacia el increíble haber
kill another remember you can cover yourself
mata otro recuerda que puedes cubrirte
with the shield but you don't run peacefully
con el escudo pero no corres paciel
commit yourself to see that it is approaching you
comprome veas que se te está acercando
press s and you move away from the graphic that
pulsa la s y te alejas de él gráfica que
how am I going to make him wait
como yo lo voy a hacer esperar
to see you are seeing
para ver estás viendo
but it's that easy to see
pero así de fácil vers
Ok now I'm going to give you a more difficult one.
ok ahora te voy a poner uno más difícil
but they can close this one because if not
pero este lo pueden cerrar porque si no
it escapes us
se nos escapa
I want you to cover yourself with the shield
quiero que te cubres con el escudo
and leave or rather it will not be anything for you
y deje o sea no te va a ser nada por las
arrows
flechas
that's the pattern for more or less killing
ese es el patrón para más o menos matar
the skeleton you cover and hit when
al esqueleto te cubres y golpea cuando
you see that he is shooting, notice that there is
veas que está disparando fíjate que hay
another toy when you see them shoot you
otro juguete cuando ves que disparan te
you approach and hit him
acercas y lo golpean
is
es
incredible ok now another one
increíble ok ahora otro
Look, this one is a little complicated.
mira fíjate este es un poco complicado
stick spiders on it, the spider is not by day
pégale arañas la araña por el día no es
aggressive truth then but what
agresiva verdad entonces pero lo que
It happens with the law that is very small
pasa con la ley esté muy chiquita
ah
ah
incredible
increíble
the hardest of all, huh
el más difícil de todos eh
there you go
ay te va
regrettable
lamentable
but look
pero mira
I'll give you another key
te pongo otro key
to the
al
come on come on or you can cover yourself too
ándale ándale o te puedes cubrir también
with the joke you copper with the shield the
con el chiste cobres con el escudo el
shield protects you from 100% of damage
escudo te protege el 100% del daño hacia
wherever you are watching
donde estéis viendo
how I covered it with the fork shield
como me lo cubrí con el escudo tenedor
clear bow but imagine you have it
arco claro pero imagínate que lo tienes
very close you don't have time to load the
muy cerca no te da tiempo a cargar el
bow
arco
But look, I demand that you show something long, right?
pero mira te exijo enseñar algo largo no
I can make it raw
puedo ponerle crudo
Of course, but for example if you have
claro pero por ejemplo si tu tienes
near a clipper better take cover with it
cerca a un clipper mejor cúbrete con el
shield and I have to be
escudo y yo tengo que ser
poor
pobres
Yes, but that's what we're going to practice.
ya pero sea lo que vamos a practicar
right now it's like this is that living a
ahorita es como este es eso vivir una
night so you can learn to aim at
noche para que aprendas a apuntar a
things in motion and as they are not very
cosas en movimiento y como no son muy
intelligent because it is a good
inteligentes pues es un bueno de
practice but take care then teach a
práctica pero cuidar luego enseñar un
trick of how if I join them and putting you in
truco de como si les uno y poniéndote en
front of the creepers because the will survive
frente del creepers pues sobrevivirá el
Be careful, look, I'll put a block on it.
cuidado mira yo le pongo un bloque
in front of
delante
It doesn't do anything to me anymore but tomorrow I'm not going to
no me hace nada ya pero mañana no voy a
have weapons already already already but that is text
tener armas ya ya ya pero o sea de texto
saying what we are going to practice
diciendo que lo que vamos a practicar
right now it is this
ahorita es esto
besides I had never had any
además no había tenido nunca ningún
episode I think I don't think we're going
episodio creo no creo vamos
man but for the pity in the end
hombre pero para la pena al final
remember that in the series these knives
recuerda que en la serie estas cuchillos
Okay
vale
follow me, let's go hunting
sígueme vamos a cazar
the spider that you are killing them
la araña que los vais matando
cover yourself when you see that he is
cúbrete cuando ves que te esté
shooting
disparando
hit him hard
pégale fuerte
good good
bien bien
let's go let's go
vamos vamos
kill everything for all this old lady too
mata todo para toda esta vieja también
It was incredible everything you see everything
fue increíble todo lo que veas todo lo
that you see but be careful with this
que veas pero cuidado con esto
that red octopus
ese pulpo de rojo
me
me
remember when in the hearts
recuerda cuando en los corazones
to the skeleton
al esqueleto
let's go let's go
vamos vamos
He's shooting at Mitu, kill him
está disparando mitú mátalo
aid
ayuda
Yo
i
to the truth of art
a la verdad de con el arte
but go ahead
pero dale
sometimes they take you from behind, they had to
a veces te llevan por detrás tenían por
behind, careful behind
detrás cuidado por detrás
I have
yo tengo
it
lo
what have I done
que he hecho
stretched by things careful
estirado por las cosas cuidado
incredible
increíble
Madrid
madrid
careful and let's go to the
cuidado y vamos a la
wait
espera
from a serious blow
de un golpe grave
let's see, we chased well.
a ver bien persigue metimos
let's go this way
vamos por aquí
let's see if he is able to follow a support
a ver si es capaz de seguir a un apoyo
from YouTube
de youtube
[Music]
[Música]
but let's go look for enemy monsters
pero vamos a buscar monstruos enemigos
that they attack us but the joke
que nos ataquen pero el chiste
look look look some flames like Levante
mira mira mira unas llamas como levante
quality
calidad
Those who attack care spit on you
esas que atacan el cuidado te escupen
a stupid person may have
un estúpido puede haber
nothing
nada
and we run out of sea
y se nos acaba el mar
in six months
en seis meses
there are loans in a sea
hay préstamos en un mar
wait a second while he kills
espera un segundo mientras va matando
things
cosas
while I go to another place for
en lo que yo me voy a otro lugar para
that more bugs appear because here
que aparezcan más bichos porque aquí
we are in a sea
estamos en un mar
and this is where I found a desert
y esto encontré un desierto
Let's see, but wait, lost, not what I
a ver pero espera perdidos no lo que yo
I went to another place so that there is
me fui a otro lugar para que ahí hay
football a game of spaces
fútbol un juego de espacios
Ready artists, be careful with the crossings and
listo artistas cuidado con los cruces y
theories spoken of a helmet sticking
teorías hablado de un casco se pega
we won well
bien vencimos
the dwarf goes on, he is very fast
el enano dale que es muy rápido
thought out but hit hit hit hit
discurrido pero a golpear dale dale dale
now
ahora
well and remember if you want to eat
bien y recuerda si quieres que comer
how to recover the first one
cómo recuperar el primero
Okay, let's go
bueno vamos
up to the green line that is
hasta de la línea verde que es
because the green line the green line
porque la línea verde la línea verde
under the hearts
debajo de los corazones
This is an experience bar that
a esto es una barrita de experiencia que
It's not going to help you in the game of
no te va a servir para el juego del
squid I guess but basically with
calamar supongo pero básicamente con
This enchants things and when he
esto encanta las cosas y cuando él
you sing things because they are more powerful
cantas cosas pues son más poderosos
and when you kill monsters it fills up
y cuando matas monstruos se te llena a
TRUE
verdad
there may be behind
puede haber por detrás
the truth of your sport helps us
la verdad de tu deporte nos ayuda
incredible let's see let's go to the kripper let's go
increíble a ver vamos al kripper vamos a
say but how do you kill it here it is
decir pero como lo matas aquí está
I also
también me
up to the top careful careful careful
hasta arriba cuidado cuidado cuidado
but
pero
regrettable
lamentable
for me not for me
por mí no por mí
is called
se llama
the truth is
la verdad es
The debate was really good, it really was.
buenísimo el debate la verdad que sí ha
It's been incredible, so it's closing, right?
sido increíble o sea q va cerrando no de
that it can be seen and it seems that it was Randolph
que se vea y que parece que era randolph
but I do not forget
pero no olvido
There are some acquaintances
están algunos conocidos
and I swear to you that I have arrived at
y yo te lo juro que está he llegado a
fall media convinced that it could be
caer medios convencido de que podría ser
serious but because it was going to be and it doesn't have
grave pero porque iba a ser y no tiene
sense and I don't watch the video
sentido y yo no me tiro el vídeo
yes but why
ya pero por qué
Of course it is attacked and it is the sea in
desde luego que se agrede y es el mar en
the time when it started because there is yes
la época cuando inició porque hay ahí sí
it resembles the voice
se parece a la voz
very high
muy arriba
and of this
y de esto
keep it and short loose
mantenlo y short sueltas
a little further down
un poco más abajo
sell follow me follow me here sayings
vender sígueme sígueme por aquí dichos
be careful with the pinchas
cuidado con los pinchas
age
la edad
ah
ah
careful
cuidado
Yo
i
quality
calidad
let's see why there are spiders
a ver porque hay arañas
Remember that if you occupy hearts eat
recuerda que si ocupas corazones come
There will be the two clippers that are trying
habrá los dos clippers que hay intenta
kill a kripper if it has length like this pp
matar un kripper si tiene largo así pp
you hit him and what do you do back you hit yourself
le pegas y qué haces para atrás te pegas
and you go after hitting and even after having
y te pasas tras pegar y hasta tras haber
try with him he sticks chairs to him
intenta con él se le pega sillas para
back you hit the legs must be worn out
atrás tu pégale las patas debe gastarse
backwards
para atrás
come on come on you stuck back
dale dale te pegaste para atrás
It's incredible but always here
es increíble pero siempre acá
the truth is that from afar
la verdad es que desde lejos
ah
ah
more good
más buena
good
buena
ah
ah
some more
un poco más
go down between let's continue let's continue
baja entre sigamos sigamos
although traction come over here behind
aunque tracción ven por acá atrás
It is almost politicization that supports it
es casi la politización apoya la apoya
wanting it does not come out is that the turkey has
queriendo no sale es que el pavo ha
arrived from a woman, they prepare not because you
llegado de mujer alistan no porque tu
content in the same
contenido en el propio
I mean, imagine if you had, as you say,
o sea imagínate si hubieras como dices
you imagine it serves has been prepared
tú imagínate sirve ha estado preparado
The first one is equally prepared
la primera está preparado igualmente
The debate was already such without knowing what it was
ya el debate era tal sin saber que era
he
él
doing a while
haciendo un rato
Being an agent the day was funny
siendo un agente el día estaba gracioso
to the debate because the arguments were
al debate porque los argumentos eran
pitiful
penosos
Of course when he is wise that he was already there
claro cuando sea sabio que era el ya ha
has been supporting her
sido la apoya
I have left quite a bit
yo he partido bastante
usual
habituales
incredible let's continue
increíble sigamos
good
bien
hurry up there
apure hay
because because I came out with the sword
porque porque salí con la espada
or you hit and go backwards and get closer
o pegas y hacia atrás vegas y acercas
There are important things to remember, look, press
hay importantes recuerdas mira presiona
f5
f5
on the way
de camino
but those under pressure to leave
pero las presionados para que partan de
maybe this way you can see for example if
a lo mejor así puedes ver por ejemplo si
you are approaching someone because
se te está acercando a alguien porque
you can see a little higher
puedes ver un poco más alto
so no why why for example
así que no por qué por qué por ejemplo
Imagine that right now you have a clip
imagínense que ahora mismo tiene un clip
then you won't be able to hit it well
entonces no vas a poder pegarle bien
because you don't have the cross
porque no tienes la cruz
I can hit it well but because I know
yo puedo pegarle bien pero porque yo sé
where am I looking
dónde estoy viendo
instead you look try to hit the 1st
en cambio tú mira intenta pegarle al 1er
[Music]
[Música]
It's good, good, but when the game
está bueno bueno pero cuando el juego
from America is one of the dolls like this
del américa es uno de la muñeca así
there is even because if you are in the one of the
hay incluso porque si estás en el de la
doll, well they exist normally you can see
muñeca pues existen normalito puedes ver
better this one in front of you today
mejor este que hay enfrente de ti hoy
why not bitter squid
por qué no amargo del calamar
but I can't change it right now but yes
pero no puedo cambiarlo ahorita pero si
you want us to give each other things and fight each other
quieres nos damos cosas y peleamos entre
both
los dos
However, we continue killing bugs.
como quiera ser seguimos matando bichos
or we fight among ourselves
o peleamos entre nosotros
but I see the GDP because that's how you
pero yo veo del pib porque así te
you tend to fight badly
acostumbras a pelear mal
Look how you've already got him by the piquillo pepper
fíjate cómo ya le agarras del piquillo
Well
bueno
But if you want to fight me or continue killing me
pero si me quieres pelear o seguir matar
but
pero
But I'm not going to have fights with you.
pero lo mismo haber peleas no te voy a
win if you want, let's fight now
ganar si quieres peleamos ya
good to look at
bueno mirar
what's more we have a few more and when
es más tenemos unos pocos más y cuando
Let's finish killing a little more and fight
terminemos de matar un poco más peleamos
keep one thing in mind diet
ten en cuenta una cosa dieta
Yeah
si
bathtubs to a test if bathtub passes
bañeras a una prueba si paso bañera
we can continue training
podemos seguir entrenando
If we already see that we are reaching
si ya vemos que estamos llegando hasta
the end then we will have to train
el final entonces tendremos que entrenar
the fight was very hard
muy duro la pelea
mind
mente
Tomorrow's test is easier for
la prueba de mañana es más liviana para
that almost everyone passes
que casi todos pasen
It may be the man, it may not be
puede ser el hombre no puede ser
for example the first insurance insurance
por ejemplo la primera seguro seguro
it's surely his
seguro es la de él
the red light green light but the second one
la de luz roja luz verde pero la segunda
They will be invented tests, they will not be
serán pruebas inventadas no van a ser
only those in the game
sólo las del juego
to see you the fire the squid and its light
a verte el fuego el calamar y su luz
red because that's what squid is called
roja porque el calamar así se llama el
fire and red light because it's like the
fuego y luz roja porque es como que la
more iconic and it is very good yes but the
más icónica y es muy buena sí pero las
Besides, although it is not worth five tests, nothing
demás aunque no vale cinco pruebas nada
Well yes, it is six days
pues sí son seis días
if it were a day if there were five but they are
si fuera un día si había cinco pero son
There are six days, there won't be five
son seis días no va a haber cinco
There will be many more tests than without 20
pruebas habrá muchas más que sin 20
games or something
juegos o algo
for this last one kill him and we move on to
para este último mátalo y pasamos a
fight among others then tomorrow
pelear entre otros entonces mañana
it will be simpler
será más simple
let's go simple to fall someone but no
vamos simple caer a alguien pero no
It will be so difficult for them not to fall
serán tan tan difícil para que no caigan
so many
tantos
Well, heal everything and be realistic when you're done
bueno cúrate todo y realistas cuando ya
have with the hearts and the party 26
tengas con los corazones y el fiesta 26
okay fight
okey pelea
1 2 3
1 2 3
and [ __ ] great
y madre
ah
ah
to
a
Yo
i
burns
arde
I really understand
entiendo de verdad
I just don't understand why it kills me so much
es que no entiendo por qué me mata tan
fast
rápido
because I hit you with criticism
porque te pego críticos
but look, he took my shield away
pero mira me quitó el escudo m
Well, something else would be there
pues algo más sería allí
If you take off your shield too
si tú te quitas el escudo también
but
pero
go
voy
ok ready but
ok listo pero
ha ha ha
jajaja
it would be ideal
sería ideal
but of course he won't be able to
pero claro no va a poder
Of course, if I'm live, it's not possible.
claro si estoy en directo no se puede
download it
descargar él
the direct that was rendering me the
el directo que me fuera renderizando el
debate and such but no no
debate y tal pero no no
view
vista
We're going to stop in Tripoli every day.
vamos a parar de trípoli todas las
ads
anuncios
but Peru
pero el perú
Well, it's been a tremendous day
pues ha sido tremendo día
It's just that these are the things that happen to us in
es que son las cosas que nos pasan en
This channel is
este canal es
Currently the things that happen to us that
actualmente las cosas que nos pasan que
They don't show on this channel, they don't show on
no pasan en este canal no pasan en
no one said
ninguno dijo
ouch
ouch
rough
áspera
but
pero
Okay
vale
come up because it's fallen
sube que está caído
or that looking at memories what I teach you
o que mirar recuerdos lo que te enseño
of critical hits when you jump and hit
de golpes críticos cuando saltas y pegas
When you're falling you hit me and make me
cuando estás cayendo me pegas y me haces
more damage
más daño
but go on like this
pero dale así
try another try and see what comes out
intenta otro intentado fíjate que salen
those little things
esas cositas
and
y
last
último
history
historia
then you can do that but how
entonces eso lo puedes hacer pero como
it is more complicated
es más complicado
bastard bastard the kicks
cabrón cabrón las patadas
let's see, ready, prepared
a ver listo preparado
prepared
preparado
Balearics
baleares
No
no
ah
ah
that's [ __ ] leather
eso es cuero cabrón
eat eat
come come
This rich one I titled it like this
esta rica la titulé está como
the bike is nice, nice for the bus
está rica la bicicleta rica para bus
and
y
and I think this is impossible
y es que yo creo que esto es imposible
you you you have to trust which
tú tú tú tienes que confiar los cuales
what is the probability that you
cuánto es la probabilidad de que te
touch with someone who is bad or is
toque con alguien que sea malo o sea
how many bad people and the mail is
cuánta gente mala y el correo es
quite a few people are bad, more than 50 of course
bastante gente mal más del 50 claro
let's see, ready, ready, the truth is
a ver listo listo la verdad
Look, I'm going to be covering myself and you
mira me voy a estar cubriendo y tu
tries to hit me from behind
intenta golpearme por detrás
the potato
la papa
Valera
valera
[ __ ] branch
rama
next to good
al lado de bueno
let's see, we're back to normal.
a ver volvemos a la normalidad está
Ready out here come eat remember to eat
listo out here come come recuerda comer
let's see now ready prepared
a ver ahora listo preparado
yes to read now
sí que leer ahora
and
y
and that is impossible he said
y es eso es imposible dijo
for Blair it is that I can't maybe not
para blair es que no puedo puede que no
May it be so with the shield and all of Abertis I fear
sea así con escudo y todo abertis temo
not the circuits only with armor and with
no los circuitos solo con armadura y con
sword and bow
espada y con arco
this is coming out
esto se sale
and
y
We are already improving, she is giving more
ya vamos mejorando ella va dando más
hits but it's trying to move so much
golpes pero es intentando moverte tanto
Because although it is good to move, I think that
porque si bien es bueno moverte creo que
It is the fact that it is moving sometimes
es el hecho de que esté moviendo a veces
focus more on hitting
concentre más en golpear
go go
dale dale
Yo
i
ah
ah
today
hoy
after winning the fight it is impossible
luego de ganar la pelea es imposible
you have to trust because you and
tú tienes que confiar porque tú y
practice because it may not be your turn
practicar porque puede que no te toque
against someone outside
contra alguien fuera
can't touch me but of course what
no puede tocarme pero claro qué
eat eat eat
come come come
can touch me most likely
puede tocar me lo más probable es que
touch someone who is called bad clear
toque a alguien que se llama malo claro
Yeah
sí
With practice, maybe
ya con la práctica pues a lo mejor
you can beat him another think it is
puedes ganarle otra piensa que es
a matter of having
cuestión de tener
achievement which is to have good luck and
logro que es tener buena suerte y
obviously have as knowledge or
obviamente tener como conocimiento o
experience knowing how to play is also
experiencia saber jugar también se
values for example the game of which
valora por ejemplo el juego de la que
you hardly know how to move you come
casi no sabes tú moverte vienes
stop because you're going to lose in the one of the
detenerte pues vas a perder en el de los
you're going to have a lot of crystals
cristales vas a tener muchísima
good luck to win
muchísima suerte para ganar
because respect is not what you say
porque un respeto no es que tú digas
you see the crystals and say there is this
veas los cristales y digas hay este
jump and not in this one because there are two
salto y en este no porque son dos
There are no crystals, there is not much difference
cristales no hay no hay mucha diferencia
since the first birds
desde los primeros aves
or the last imagine that you want the
o de los últimos imagínate que deseas el
last and you can't jump because
último y que no puedes saltar porque
you have to wait for it to be removed or we'll go
tienes que esperar a lo quita o vamos
let's play squid game what
vamos jugar juego del calamar lo que
It happens that it will take me a few minutes
ocurre es que voy a tardar unos minutos
in putting it to save a lot for a few minutes
en ponerlo de guardar mucho unos minutos
how much is it
cuánto es
I don't know exactly how long it will take me
no sé exactamente cuánto voy a tardar la
TRUE
verdad
But if you want, I'll upload it and we can play.
pero si quieres lo subo y jugamos
[Music]
[Música]
but I'm going up so you stay calm and
pero estoy subiendo o sea tú tranquilo y
nervous me
nervioso yo
tea
te
I said it would take a little while
dije que iba a tardar un poquito
come now
venga ya
to read
a leer
you calm nerves
tú tranquilo nervios
Look carefully at what is said there
mira tú bien atrás ahí lo que se dice
the things that have to go up but
las cosas que tengan que subir pero
give them out at least main
dales a salir de al menos principales
closed
cerrado
that is, calm down, good euros
o sea tranquilo bien euros
1st
1a
verdial and loading
verdial y cargando
and there your calm self is rising
y allá se está subiendo tu tranquilo
father dad mashed potatoes mashed potatoes
padre papá puré de papas puré
the debate
el debate
I mean, how would you have reacted, yes yes
o sea cómo hubiera reaccionado tú sí si
I really would have thought it would have been
realmente hubiera sido creo
Damn, forget if he supports it too.
pues olvida si lo apoya también
Of course, because it would have already happened.
claro porque es que ya lo hubiera
definitely marked would have been the
marcado definitivamente hubiera sido la
Yes, let's see, it would be very unfortunate indeed.
sí a ver sería muy lamentable en verdad
I wish I wasn't getting into that anymore
quisiera eso ya no me estaba metiendo
with serious
con grave
I'm sorry to put the only thing a long time ago
lamento poner hace mucho tiempo lo único
some try but come on
algunas intenta pero vamos
but I was messing with him but
pero me estaba metiendo con él pero
unfortunate, he gave it that good, he said
lamentable dio así buenísimo dijo
Tonight we sleep like babies, Javier.
de esta noche dormimos como bebés javier
it has been very good
se ha sido muy bueno
totally has more than so many
totalmente tiene a más de tantas
we have to get the game started quickly
tenemos que echar rápida la partida dio
I have to
me tengo que
cut them must download more than
recortarlos debe descargar más de
director cut it time to be able to
director recortarlo tiempo para poder
upload it, come in now, come in now
subirlo entra ya entra ya
You can now enter, but little is said
ya puedes entrar pero pero poco se habla
from the pass I gave you there easily
del pase que te he dado ahí de fácil
the channel
el canal
incredible
increíble
Furthermore, it cannot be among others
además no puede ser entre otros
but you're not moving ok 9
pero estas no te mueves ok 9
we have to wait 5 4 3 2 1 enters
tenemos que esperar 5 4 3 2 1 entra el
30 but we have no delays at the beginning
30 pero no tenemos demoras al principio
because I agree that it is in red light mode
porque acuerdo que está en modo luz roja
now when it is put in place
ahora cuando se ponga en lugar
red light
luz roja
green light moves and moves
luz verde mueve y mueve
I'm going to see left
voy a ver izquierdo
but not now
pero no ahora
regrettable to be able to not have you
lamentable para poder no te has
died faster and [ __ ] up again
muerto más deprisa y todo otra vez
once again once again he gave me
a otra vez otra vez más me dio
precisely arrested because of you but
precisamente detenido por tu culpa pero
But because it's going to be my fault, it's true.
pero porque va a ser mi culpa es cierto
was playing with your mind as well as the
estaba jugando con tu mente así como los
others are going to play with yours I am you
demás van a jugar con la tuya te estoy
preparing psychologically clear
preparando psicológicamente claro
Now we'll have to see how that goes
ahora habrá que ver como aquello
How is it that he has to see if he has
como es que aquel a ver si tiene
counter of that one above or whatever it has to
contador de esa arriba o lo que tiene a
see this serious counter I because it has
ver esta grave contador yo porque tiene
that is, by sound, that is, by sound, let's go
o sea por sonido o sea por sonido vamos
screwed
jodidos
is that this one has no sound because I think
es que este no tiene sonido porque creo
that can't make any sound if it doesn't
que no puede meter algún sonido si no lo
does well and like the most fails time that
hace bien y como el más falla vez que
it is poorly done
está mal hecho
Look here, she doesn't even have a doll
fíjate aquí ni siquiera tiene muñeca
That's why there won't be any positions tomorrow.
por eso no habrá puestos de mañana
You'll have a doll if you live in the trailer
tendrá muñeca si se vive en el tráiler
believe
creo
dolls and there because they were Tyler
muñecas y hay porque estuvieron tyler
people extra sounds of sex sound
gente extras sonidos de sexo sonido
also because that is, it is not, it is not
también porque o sea no es no es
I'll download any of this guy's maps.
cualquier mapa de este tío me descargo
It's something that comes in handy, the paper prints
es algo viene bien los grabados papel
but it will have sound, it will have an indicator
pero tendrá sonido tendrá indicador
visual also to see sound I don't know
visual también a ver sonido no sé
sounds I think if it enters it enters
sonidos yo creo que si entra entra
ok done
vale hecho
remember to open the inventory
recuerda a abrir abres el inventario
Okay
vale
select the arrow and then
seleccionar la flechita y luego
select the yellow boxes and
seleccionar los cuadros amarillos y
oranges until they put you all in
naranjas hasta que te pongan todos en
red wins
rojo ganas
It will be like this, theirs was a negative drug
será así el de ellos era droga negativa
It may be otherwise, it will be otherwise
puede ser de otra manera será de otra
It's going to be a big coincidence that
manera mucha casualidad va a ser que
inside not because or this is it, notice that
dentro no porque o sea éste fíjate que
It's like that difficult I know it's difficult to
es como que difícil sé que es difícil de
do this why
hacer esto por qué
there is death try again yes that
hay la muerte intentarlo otra vez sí que
It's me who hasn't won it, incredible man.
es yo no lo ha ganado increíble hombre
Well, I was telling you that I know what it is
bueno pues te decía que sé que es
difficult to make impossible as you
difícil hacer imposible como que tú
whether you go scratching or doing shoulders enter
vayas rascando o haciendo hombros entra
again
otra vez
kill you kill you wait for this lesson
mata te mata te espera que esté lección
Paraguay
paraguay
not impossible
no imposible
I don't know what happened
es que no sé qué ha pasado
but well you are already selected the
pero bueno ya estás que seleccionó la
third
tercera
which one is this
este cuál es el de
stadiums
estadios
But we play this or we commit suicide
pero esto lo jugamos o nos suicidamos
because I don't think that between the two of them
porque no creo que entre los dos no
we are not going to win either one or the other because it has
vamos a ganar ni uno y otro porque tiene
to be among more people
que ser entre más personas
You believe it, well, they are, look
tú crees tú pues es que son fíjate
but you have to go up and for that
pero tienes que subir arriba y para que
Winning one like this doesn't take you out of the quick fire
gane uno así no saca del fuego rápido
temperature
temperatura
Today I can't move either.
hoy es que yo tampoco me puedo mover
now we wait 5 4 3 2
ahora esperamos 5 4 3 2
1 let's see the message in theory
1 a ver en teoría mensaje
Paula has fallen into the void
paula se ha caído al vacío
Let's see the fourth one if I'm not mistaken it's the
a ver el cuarto si no me equivoco es las
marbles the fifth bar but central
canicas el quinto bar pero central
fifth
quinto
but I am
pero estoy
There will be a room out there that we will choose
allá fuera habrá una sala que elegiremos
team something
equipo algo
I guess let's see, first things first.
supongo a ver yo primero es lo primero
dead
muerto
we have practiced both parts
hemos practicado tanto partes
like even getting on a train
como incluso entrar en tren
offers everything tomorrow there
ofrece todo de mañana allí
give it to me
dale
wait
espera
so you're making my way
así que me estás haciendo el camino
agreement
acuerdo
lamentable for deer at its worst
lamentable para venados en lo mã s
come in come in
entra entra
Let's see, I'll jump first.
a ver yo primero salto
here mark here back here
aquí marca acá atrás acá
pitiful dad
lamentable papá
go on, give it your soul
dale dale tu alma
but
pero
but you savior we can continue
pero te salvador podemos seguir
doing it
haciéndolo
which knew what to do
la cual sabía cuál debe actuar
never
nunca
let's see let's see
a ver a ver
or incredible
o increíble
Imagine that this is the game here
imagínate que este es por aquí el juego
of truth and the last one is falsified
de verdad y se falsea la última
Imagine
imagínate
bo has been amazing
bo ha sido increíble
is 50% god
es el 50% dios
Of course we continue doing that, we move on to
claro la seguimos haciendo esa pasamos a
the
la
so good everything let's see let's see eta
tan bueno todo a ver a ver eta
to the first
al primero
every time it is very bad luck that you
cada vez que es muy mala suerte que te
touch is the first is god
toquen es el primero es dios
It's very good luck that you get 15
es muy buena suerte que te toca 15 el
God first
primero dios
Let's see, look, you jump and I'll go, I'll go
a ver mira tú tú salta y yo te voy yo te
if you're going to fall
si te vas a caer
You can rest assured that you are protected
tú tranquilo estás protegido
let's see this
a ver esta
clue
pista
cereals
cereales
because I am saving you whether I
porque yo te estoy salvando sea si yo me
I fall, we both put on
caigo nos ponemos los dos
either
o
dead air we die friends
aire muerto morimos amigos
No
no
to berbegal last last of these and
a berbegal última última de estas y
we move on to the final night
pasamos a la noche final
the final night
la noche final
come on, go on
venga va
I hope not
espero que no
he is not dead
no está muerto
but but no don't go into three yet
pero pero no no entres todavía en tres
I still want to remove a resistor
todavía quiero quitar una resistencia
so you don't die
para que no te mueras
the practice of jumping but you
la práctica del salto pero os
I also tell you but very good luck
también te digo pero muy buena suerte
that touches you
que te toque
the first uncle
el primero tío
how many jumps are there
cuantos saltos son ahí
They are like about ten six maybe
son como unos diez seis puede ser
let's see now so much
a ver ahora tanto
s
s
Let's see, the stories are 1 2 3 4 5 6
a ver dejar los cuentos son 1 2 3 4 5 6
7 8 9 10 here here are 10
7 8 9 10 aquí aquí son 10
each one will be much more
cada uno será mucho más
high and I greet you for what
alta y yo te saludo para qué
and
y
is that youtube is saved from waiting
es que youtube es salvado de espera
either
o
give it the law
dale darle la ley
because look, that is the problem with these
porque fíjate o sea el problema de estos
Note that it is that you are wrong but
fíjate que es que tú te equivoques pero
what you're doing is that you're not
lo que estás haciendo es que no estás
jumping
saltando
clear
claro
the dam has passed me
la presa me ha pasado
there will never be a time
alguna vez no va a haber
It is one of the latest games in theory because
es de los últimos juegos en teoría por
at least in the series of the last 20
lo menos en las series de los últimos 20
if this is the last one if it is in 350
si este es el último si es en 350
you pass it
te lo pasas
but
pero
and
e
not many will come here
aquí no van a llegar muchos
most likely
lo más probable
ah
ah
lamentable day
lamentables dig el día
and
e
reality you have little left
realidad ya te queda poco
Obama's value
valor de obama
given why
dado por qué
because the race
porque la carrera
and what was it
y cuál era
Well, there is no need to address it
pues no hay abordarlo
One morning we might play a game but
un mañana igual echamos una partida pero
in the morning I can't see in the morning
por la mañana no puedo ver por la mañana
would have to be would have to be very
tendría que ser tendría que ser muy
early
temprano
in plan
en plan
Tomorrow we'll see if we start tomorrow
mañana vamos a ver mañana si empezamos
We the 8 I will start the live
nosotros las 8 yo empezaré el directo a
7:30 is not enough time for anything
las 7 y media no nos va a tiempo de nada
a little game a couple of hours before
una partidita un par de horas antes
by
por
us
nosotros
Yes, because opening is only for that
sí porque abrir es únicamente para esa
clear tomorrow
mañana claro
Right now for me it's 9:48 in the morning
ahora mismo para mí son las 9 48 de la
night we are talking you talk to me and I
noche vamos hablando tú me hablas y yo
I tell you if I am or I am not ok it's a
te digo si estoy o no estoy ok es una
stuff
cosa
check the thing for
revisa la cosa para
I have a meeting at
que tengo una reunión a la
From 6 to 7 we have it bolio uncle
de 6 a 7 lo tenemos bolio tío
but after eating the best you can
pero después de comer lo mejor puedas
some
algunas
Well, I'll tell you when I'm awake and
bueno yo te digo cuando esté despierto y
when I can guide the blind we square
cuando pueda guía el ciego cuadramos
family, thank you very much for the company
familia muchas gracias por la compañía
Paula Gracia Rey tomorrow we talk about o
paula gracia rey mañana hablamos de o
we see several milestones
nos vemos varios hitos
family see you tomorrow it's worth a lot
familia mañana nos vemos vale muchísimas
thanks for the night it's been a night
gracias por la noche ha sido una noche
magical 5 almost 5 hours of live for
mágica 5 casi 5 horas de directo para
all poorly paid kg and elements at 8
todo mal pagados kg y elementos a las 8
around 7:30 to open it, okay?
sobre las 7 7 y media abrir ella vale
about seven thirty and seven and
sobre las siete y siete y media y le
I open so family a big hug
abro así que familia un abrazo muy
big
grande
[Music]
[Música]